<dataset>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The saddest aspect of life right now is that science gathers knowledge faster than society gathers wisdom.#WHY
</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Fantastic pacing, an excellent performance by Gyllenhaal and smart storytelling make this a wonderful film</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content> Much richer, much deeper and much more moving than its 'monster movie' premise might suggest.
</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Visually stunning with video game violence, this is Hollywood's answer to The Raid.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>A cute, but meandering story of growing up alone and having to fend for oneself even when there's help to be received.
</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>A smart and inventive thriller, Inception is one of the year's best movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Mildly amusing is the best I can say for the film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Lovely to look at and mildly funny but tries with sweaty desperation to be the next Pirates of the Caribbean.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>An epic silent version of the Robin Hood legend.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>It's enjoyable to see a quality superhero dynamically and enthusiastically rendered.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>A perfect roller coaster blend of horror and science fiction. Sigourney Weaver was an amazing discovery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>It may be a second-tier Romero film, but hell, it's still a Romero film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Every so often, it's time to re-boot Batman.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>less a film than a memorial: handsome, stately, well-meaning and dramatically inert.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>A  flashy movie that's more like a video game.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Bears the stamp of its director, Guy Ritchie, much more so than that of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle </content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Everything Angelinos love and hate about their city is here, as well as anything a movie fan could possibly wish for</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>This sci-fi epic would be a masterpiece if judged solely on its technical merits.
</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>While it's not in the same classic league, the movie has a nice Back to the Future vibe to it.
</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Not Jonah Hex bad...but almost.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>This inception app is stupid</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>"Shrek Forever After" feels more like a direct-to-video release than one that should have been put in theaters.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Like too many horror franchises, a premise that was once scary has evolved into something campy and self-aware.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>The Final Destination - The instalment sees the franchise go 3D which improves the look but not the premise. Disappointing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Painfully funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Another third installment, another arrested adolescent gone wild
</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>In the absence of the first film's rhythm, wit, and novelty, it's a typically lazy, diminishing-returns sequel.
</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>A minor improvement over its nigh abominable predecessor</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>[A] gigantic chunk of scat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Doesn't have the originality of the first film and feels a little boring as such.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>This franchise, like its villains, has become more machine than man</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>More than half an hour shorter than The Lost World, so at least there's a lot less of it to suffer through.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Grotesque carnage, vile characters; steer clear.
</content>
</item>
</dataset>