<dataset>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The Expendables - Stallone gathers a motley crew of action stars and crafts an entertaining, albeit silly movie. Plain old-fashioned fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Source Code: A clever, intricately paced modern sci-fi thriller. Smart visuals, strong performances and a great twist make this a winner.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Super 8: Spielbergian nostalgia with a touch of Abrams flair. An update and an homage to the classic sci-fi films of the 70 and 80s. Awesome.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Dredd 3D: Epic hardcore actioner. Top quality special effects, effectively utilised 3D, and a stellar turn from Urban. Brutally brilliant.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Beasts of the Southern Wild - A film of quiet power and grace with extraordinary central performances. Breathtaking and so heartbreaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Inception - Christopher Nolan dazzles, mystifies and manages to produce a truly extraordinary, intelligent summer blockbuster. Brilliant.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The A-Team - A brand new gang assembles for this 80's TV classic remake. It's unbelievably stupid but it's just incredibly fun. Nostalgic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time- Amazing visual + cool parkour + Jake Gyllenhaal - dreadful dialogue = good old-fashioned family fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Robin Hood: Scott and Crowe team for the 5th time in an imaginative retake on the English legend. Great action and acting but a bit slow. </content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Iron Man 2: Tony and his big metal suit return for more of the same. Great action scenes but lags during the middle. A missed opportunity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Iron Man - Light, breezy and oh-so-much fun, Iron Man is the antithesis of "Darker is better" superheroes. Downey Jr is Tony Stark. Great</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The Crazies - Eisner's remake of the Romero classic is a tension filled humdinger of a movie, let down a little by the ending. Surprising.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Batman Begins - Christopher Nolan reboots the franchise and breathes new life into an icon. Bale is wonderful. Visually superb. Fantastic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Invictus: Eastwoods take is not quite as inspiring as the real-life story. Fine performances let down by a muddled script. Sadly uneven.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Batman Forever - Garishly  bright. Carrey is remarkably solid as Riddler, while Kilmer's brooding suits Bruce's tortured soul. Underrated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Sherlock Holmes - Guy Ritchie's imaginative take on the iconic detective is a fantastic buddy comedy, but it's more actioner than puzzler.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>L.A. Confidential - Ellroy's book was meant to be too difficult to adapt but Hanson made an epic movie of sweeping scale, style and majesty.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Avatar: The burden of expectation was huge but Cameron's movie matches it. One of the best looking films ever. Immersive and breathtaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The Informant! - Steven Soderbergh directs a puffy Matt Damon in a very odd, very enjoyable take on an outlandish true story. Odd but fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Green Lantern - Top-notch effects and a strong performance by Reynolds are undermined by a woeful script and a rushed ending. Lacklustre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Sucker Punch: Imagine Inception remade by a demented 12 year old hopped up on sugar and having gone 3 days without sleep. Just appalling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Shrek Forever After - The big green ogre returns for the 4th and 'final' time. Enjoyable but ultimately forgettable. A missed opportunity. </content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>The Final Destination - The 4th and final instalment sees the franchise go 3D which improves the look but not the premise. Disappointing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Batman and Robin - How the mighty have fallen. Schumacher brings the franchise to an shuddering halt. No saving graces, everyone is rubbish.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Bedazzled - Lame remake of the faustian classic. Hurley, out-acted by scenery, is a suitably hot devil. Tame script and few laughs. </content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Spider-Man 3 - Three is not the magic number. Bloated and leaden. Emo spidey is rubbish. Venom wasted. Action packed but lacking. Average.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Men in Black II - The boys are back but sadly the comedy and originality got mislaid. Dawson is a revelation. Rip Torn is superb. Lacking.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Transformers Revenge of the Fallen: Pyramid sized MacGuffin provides convoluted plot. Copious pyrotechnic porn. Visually amazing but messy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Land of the Lost: Lost in Space meets dinosaurs. Crude jokes for a movie aimed at kids. Ferrell is more OTT than normal. Stunningly awful.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian - Long on title, short on quality. Some good moments for kids, but lacks crossover appeal.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Terminator Salvation - Visually amazing but crippled by a languid script and poor direction. Bale is sadly lacking gravitas. Unsatisfying.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Jurassic Park III - New director and no book as a basis equals an uninspired sequel. Casting is suspect. Looks great. Enjoyable but lacking.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Alien Resurrection - A shoddy script lets down another good director. Surprising considering Joss Whedon was involved. Simply unnecessary.</content>
</item>
</dataset>