<dataset>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>A light-hearted classic kids' sports movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Very lame ice-hockey flick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>It's all pretty bland.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The absence of innovation can easily be forgiven.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>The exclamation point on a great run of classic Disney animation...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>It was, is and always will be a true Hollywood classic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Misbegotten mess of a not family-friendly movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>...a dumb miscalculation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>The humans are little more than dress-extras for the mechanics.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>This film does cause shivers, creeps, scares, and jumps.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>A friendly, if decidedly featherweight, feature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>It's sweet natured and brightly played.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Ouch. Lame Sandler attempt at holiday humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Outstanding family film features glorious music.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Inspiration is pretty fallow after about half an hour.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content> Don't think too hard, just enjoy a zombie movie with a twist to go with its 'Walking Dead' charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>The film is dominated and destroyed by Mr. Cage's chaotic, self-indulgent performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Raunchy, funny, and not for younger kids.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Yet another example of therapy masquerading as documentary</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Show me a director better suited for a movie about magic than Christopher Nolan and I'll show you... a magician?
</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Lots of overacting. Lots of cliches. Lots of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Just when you think things can't get any more farcical, they do: The Hangover is the Crank of comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Inappropriate and wrongheaded interruptions reveal the fragile nature of the plot and prevent it from working.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>DIE HARD is a classic film. Simply put, every single thing works.
</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>So much more than a football movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Shoddy musical tale with some scary stuff and hammy humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Under Vincente Minelli's crisp direction, the fun rarely lets up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Horrid, Tim-Allen-was-not-available treacle</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>It would be easy to underrate the deceptively effortless master acting class that Meryl Streep puts on here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>Strictly for fans of the TV show or sci-fi buffs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
	<content>The film seethes with misdirected and unrecognized anger.
</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>It's a hysterical, well acted, and wonderful glimpse at impending parenthood from a man's perspective...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
	<content>Kung Fu Panda is a colourful, extremely enjoyable if workmanlike animated romp.</content>
</item>
</dataset>