<?xml version="1.0"?>

<dataset>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though some scenes come off fairly well, Mitchum is poker-faced from start to finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With so much dissecting in his picture -- and so much of it being good -- it is too bad that Mr. Kramer couldn't have done a little on his characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The exceptional cast helps to while away the platitudes and pieties, provided you can accept the likes of Mitchum, Sinatra and Marvin as somewhat wrinkly students.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>That's a reasonable message, but it might feel more resonant if the script were a little fairer to both sexes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Laughter through tears is director Bill Duke's M.O., and he hits the bull's-eye of that modest target.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[It] has the saving grace of a lively sense of humor that certainly helps the spiritual medicine go down.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not Easily Broken isn't perfect, but it is persuasive in its portrait of a husband and wife who must decide whether their frayed marriage is worth fighting to save.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A well-crafted message picture disguised as soap opera.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It turns out, though, that a woman can save any marriage with a little home cooking and extra sex.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like some marriages, it has its flaws, but perhaps it's the good stuff that's worth focusing on.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not Easily Broken is well-acted and involving, though this relationship drama may put some people off with its overt sentimentality and moralizing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not Easily Broken exerts an unmistakable appeal, thanks to an absorbing story and fine performances from Morris Chestnut and Taraji P. Henson.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A queasy mix of comedy, melodrama, and self-help spirituality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For most of Not Easily Broken, I wondered why the movie wasn't worse. Then I remembered it was directed by the veteran Bill Duke, who applies ample TLC.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The pigeonholed characters constrict Chestnut and the usually good Henson from portraying fully developed adults; the same dilemma hits most of the supporting cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not Easily Broken is not easily dismissed. For one thing, the cast is excellent, and for another, its intentions are serious and generous.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Remarkably the movie, like the couple at its center, isn't easily broken.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's predictable but ultimately moving; a glimpse of a bond near-broken yet straining to become whole again.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Has] a reasonable message, but it might feel more resonant if the script were a little more fair and balanced in the battle of the sexes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not Easily Broken is a marriage-in-crisis melodrama baked from the Tyler Perry recipe.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Blanchett has also recently appeared in The Good German and Babel, but this represents far and away her best work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Richard Eyre's direction merely plays up the melodramatic aspects of Zoe Heller's novel, screenwriter Patrick Marber's acidic dialogue occasionally slips into the overwritten, and the rest of the cast gamely chews table scraps.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Bill Nighy is stunning in the small but pivotal role of Sheba's devastated husband, and Dench locates the desperate pathos in Barbara's malevolence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This compact, fierce and frightening domestic thriller is the most violent film in many a day. The rage is in the angry words, the deepest thoughts of its 'heroine,' and the fear about what might come from those words is palpable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While Glenn Close played her Fatal Attraction character's 'I will not be ignored' psycho-obsession out front and out loud, Dench does it as subtext, making it all the more insidious, frightening ... and fascinating.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In England, it seems, actresses have nothing to fear from age. They can simply wait for writers to create fresh work for them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Patrick Marber's adaptation of the Zoe Heller novel improves upon the promise of the [Dench/Blanchett] pairing with a story that wastes no time on preliminaries as it descends -- gleefully -- into pitch-black comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notes on a Scandal emerges as a remarkable character study: difficult to watch, impossible to look away.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notes on a Scandal's resolution is a bit less challenging than the finale of Heller's novel, but for the most part it's equally scathing, a nasty little peek into the worst of human behavior.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dramatic overstatement saturates just about every piece of this production. Even that master of orchestral pop minimalism, Philip Glass, managed to write a score that slinks into the dark shadows of old gothic witchery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Almost unbearably tense as the relationship between cat and mouse takes completely unexpected, if completely believable, turns.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notes on a Scandal may not always be deeply illuminating, but [director Richard] Eyre adds enough pathos and emotional realism to keep the movie from curdling into a snide joke.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The writers and the actors have just enough sympathy for their characters to keep Notes from deteriorating into a comedy of horrible manners.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ms. Dench is scary good, a collection of withering glances and quiet delusion accentuated by a wickedly funny voice-over. Ms. Blanchett matches her step for step.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie serves as a convenient locale for Dench and Blanchett to showcase their abilities, but it could be more involving.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a thrill to see powerhouse actresses lock horns in an emotional battle royal, and Notes on a Scandal gives us two of England's finest in pitched combat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a poison bonbon tastier than just about anything else out there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The skillful Patrick Marber adapted this gripping drama from a novel by Zoe Heller, and it's both literate and urgently plotted, with a voice-over from Dench that cuts like broken glass.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The screenplay has a bracing tincture of Grand Guignol, and nothing is simple when the two women are played by a couple of superlative actresses who clearly delight in one another.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notes on a Scandal won't be everyone's cup of tea. But if you like your films strong, this one is not to be missed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is a psalm to those who, far from pursuing the path of the Rolling Stones, stayed trapped under a rock.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This film could have been -- should have been, even -- something special. But it's not.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The period details are spot-on and the soundtrack is great.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yes, it's about rock and New Jersey, but it's also about getting a life going and dreaming, and that's timeless, classic stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Well-observed but occasionally disjointed, it's a film that's more about thematic tone, sound and images than it is driven by plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are plenty of laughs along with the melodrama as the band and its members struggle through young adulthood.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie that feels at once deeply personal and more than a little confused.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rock and roll is here to stay. And David Chase gets some well-deserved satisfaction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mostly, Not Fade Away is a hit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ultimately a disappointment - this is a movie easy to watch and even easier to forget.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The performances and music are a pleasure, and Chase's affection for the period is palpable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Somewhat autobiographical and worth seeing despite its somewhat muffled quality ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Chase has captured this one for all time. He delivers on the movie's title.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a \"personal\" movie that, in some ways, seems impersonal. Everything seems a bit too varnished and staged and overly familiar.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What makes this movie unique is that it's not just one more story of a band that got big in a hurry.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The acting is OK, but none of the leads has the kind of sizzle that might have turned this into something as special as another film set roughly in the same era, \"Diner.''</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>By focusing on musicians who are talented but finally not good or persistent enough to succeed in the big time, \"Not Fade Away\" offers a poignant, alternative, antiheroic history of the big beat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Alas, Not Fade Away is far less pungent than the period it attempts to evoke.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Contains a plot full of twists that can be seen coming from some distance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not Forgotten is weighted down by obvious creative choices that mar what might have played out like a telenovela episode of Twin Peaks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not effective on any level.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>From the start, it's clear there's a riddle to solve...I'm just not sure you'll care about the solution.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie that's more convoluted than satisfying.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not Forgotten overcooks just about every ingredient in its narrative chile con queso.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The title almost suggests manhood as something trifling. The film, however, confirms it's a mighty hard ideal to reach.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its historical import as a peripheral civil-rights document can't be understated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Roemer] and his collaborators create images and sounds, characters and situations, that embody the title's existential affirmation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sincere, intelligent, and effectively acted independent feature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are some standout performances from some young stars on the rise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Harmless, predictable, contrived -- if those are the best things you can say about a movie I think you should definitely skip it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With help from a lively cast and a twist on the formula, it seems fresh and enticing -- like a Christmas present you didn't know you wanted but are delighted to receive.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While there may well be nothing like the holidays, there's a lot that is dully familiar about the movie of the same name.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the turf is well-traveled, the characters' camaraderie and their palpable sense of ethnic pride trumps the predictability and makes for a tale that is pleasantly appealing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The ensemble cast boasts some of the finest actors in the business. They do their best to breathe life into the stereotypes, but they simply don't have enough to work with.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The whole thing's a little like the meals it spotlights. You know, while you're guiltily indulging, that it's no good for you. But that doesn't keep you from feeling full afterward.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>'God is punishing me,' says the matriarch. Not just you.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sometimes it's fun to unwrap a present even if you already know what's waiting inside.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Rodriguezes are dealing with divorce, a war injury, cancer and even Christmas, but these setbacks are all played for jokes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's the latest entry in the dysfunctional family holiday genre... that dark blossoming group of films that remind us how thoroughly messed up life is even at special times before concluding that family makes it all worthwhile.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Beyond the movie's seasonal familiarities of resentment and reconciliation are plenty of sweet-funny details of Latino life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's not really interested in originality, though. Instead, it wants to wrap the old seasonal homilies in the warm specifics of time and place and ethnicity. At that, it succeeds.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An efficient home-for-Christmas ensemble comedy trimmed with plastic teardrops.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like fruitcake, movies like this are ubiquitous at this time of the year but rarely are they devoured with great relish or enthusiasm.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Familiarity is part of the pleasure of holiday movies, and Nothing Like the Holidays gets by not on originality, but on chemistry and warmhearted charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ay Caramba, the holiday season can be difficult enough, but think how much worse it would be if you lived in a family full of movie stereotypes?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast, including Luis Guzman and Jay Hernandez, is strong and attractive but ultimately hamstrung by artificial situations and a hackneyed ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If the conflicts feel warmed over and the resolutions obvious, the performances, particularly those of Rodriguez, Ferlito, Messing and Pena, are so warm and winning that director Alfredo De Villa makes it a tasty entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A bumpy buddy romp that's mildly winning thanks to its stars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This thematic 'lesson' is served up with non-didactic grace complemented by tiny bursts of humour.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This alternately sad-funny film sneaks up on you. Its ability to grab us is surprising because it does so little, because it's so spare -- so unadorned and unpretentious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For Chinese viewers, this film will play as a human drama. For Western viewers, there's almost equal interest at the edges of the screen, in the background, in the locations and incidental details that show daily life in today's China.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With Not One Less, Zhang Yimou has fashioned what feels like an uncannily accurate portrait of a culture where Communist ideology has vanished like a brief dream, as traditional community values clash with the burgeoning cult of money.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite its deliberate austerity, Not One Less is extraordinarily rich.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Chinese director Zhang Yimou has a rare gift for dramatizing highly theatrical stories in highly naturalistic settings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Small movie, big impact.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's an excellent movie for kids, because it is about how amazing children can be.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This film may seem slow, and its concerns distant to many American viewers. But Not One Less is a movie whose humanity is irresistibly, even joyfully, accessible.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As mainstream hip hop becomes ever more predictable, so do the biopics about its stars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even if we miss the thinking that went into the creation of Wallace's B.I.G.-ger-than-life alter ego, the movie's performances are exultant.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie leaves us with the sense that, twelve years after Biggie Smalls's death, a lot of people are trying to extract whatever profit or pride they can from the chaotic life of a young man who was, as he well knew, a work in progress.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For a hardcore fan of his music and his life, it rings true.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Notorious is like a piece of well-crafted bling. It looks good, and facets of it shine, but behind the gilded facade there's not much there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This tale of triumph and tragedy within hip hop's elite is intelligent, gripping and far less sensationalistic than anyone could have expected.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The best thing about Notorious is its across-the-board, excellent cast, especially the soulful Woolard and Mackie's mesmerizing work as the complex Shakur.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It must have been an act of great restraint for Sean Combs to resist titling this film, about Chris Wallace, his close friend turned rapper and cultural icon, The Notorious B.I.G. -- The Sean Combs Story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notorious is surprisingly and pleasantly unflashy, a straightforward picture that makes a distinction between classiness and bling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Tillman Jr.'s film may follow the well-worn path of many a musical biography. But spot-on casting, a light touch around the edges and affection for its subject makes this warts-and-all look at the big man with the big hits a winner.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script lets too much slide, and director George Tillman Jr. -- whose biggest films have been Soul Food and the Barbershop franchise -- abets it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Closer to Scorsese than Scarface, Notorious gives a heartfelt yet clear-eyed sendoff to the late Brooklyn rapper Christopher Wallace, aka Biggie Smalls aka the Notorious B.I.G.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's unlikely there will be a better dramatization of the Biggie Smalls story than this one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Notorious obviously loves its protagonist, but the movie can't get past its own starstruck awe.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notorious has a fine time along the way, with Woolard channeling the rapper's sweetness and wit as comfortably as his pathos.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A vivid biopic of the larger-than-life rap star that doesn't require you be a big fan of the genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This flick smoothes out the roughest edges, drains off the rawness and blandly retraces the narrative arc of every musical biopic since The Jazz Singer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Notorious is a game of dress-up, the Greatest Hits version of Biggie's life. But in the end, it fails to present a convincing argument of why we should care.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Notorious, directed by George Tillman Jr. with a sentimental touch, seems torn.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The ending is happy and ironic in equal measure, but most of the fun is just getting there with the right chemistry and compatibility.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>t's an agreeably slick affair, with decent support performances, elegant camerawork, and several impressive set pieces.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An exceptionally guy-friendly chick flick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lately, romance comedies have expanded in running time, doubtless to compensate for their shrinkage in charm, and this is no exception -- it's way too long for something far too slight.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film's romantic core is impervious to problems.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Roger Michell uses technical flourishes sparingly but to lovely effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie has lots of glossy charm!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The winning romantic comedy every summer not only awaits, but counts on!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie-star-playing-a-movie-star-who-wants-to-be-a-real-person conceit also has an odd, chilling effect on Julia Roberts, whose appeal, overwhelmingly, is based on her seeming just like the rest of us.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Notting Hill is about as enchanting as movies get these days!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Smart, sometimes pissingly funny!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With Notting Hill, you've got a romantic comedy that makes falling in love with a movie easy as pie!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Blithe and exhilarating!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is bright, the dialogue has wit and intelligence, and Roberts and Grant are very easy to like.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With lead actors like that, Notting Hill doesn't need a cast of annoying supporting characters, but it's got them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's funny, sympathetic, mostly smart, and it boasts a likable cast of characters led by two performers who have star power and know how to use it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The romance is tepid.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>All the other supporting players are British television stars and all rise to the occasion of this big-budget feature film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Attempts at pathos fall with a resounding dud!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nothing new. And nothing much.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Now and Then is successful, but only now and then.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A very convincing nightmare, and if Hackman gives too rounded a performance to approach the omniscient evil of Laughton's original, Patton assumes the mantle as Brice's henchman, while Costner confirms his arrival as a star.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's so effective, in fact, that when it's all over, you might want to sit through the beginning again just to see if the end is justified by the means. I suspect that it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film makes such good use of Washington and builds suspense so well that it transcends a plot bordering on ridiculous.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A superior example of the genre, a film in which a simple situation grows more and more complex until it turns into a nightmare not only for the hero but also for everyone associated with him.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In thriller terms it's close to irresistible and enormously entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taylor-Wood has specialized in video installations and off-kilter portraits, and it was tempting to hope that her take on Lennon would unsettle and provoke. Instead, she stays resolutely on-kilter, as if awed into numbness by her subject.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The events chronicled are all longstanding Beatles legends, though director Sam Taylor-Wood manages to stage even the most portentous moments without making you feel a celestial choir is in order.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More love triangle than musical, the effective and often sweet Nowhere Boy offers a sense of the time and tension that produced John Lennon.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This portrait of a Beatle as a young man also gives filmmaker Sam Taylor-Wood, working on a thoughtful script by Matt Greenhalgh, creative room to manoeuvre, introducing us to John just as he and rock 'n' roll discover one another.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although he doesn't look much like Lennon, Johnson captures that essence perfectly; the future icon is here a confused, hurt boy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie succumbs to maudlin sentiment and melodrama that Lennon himself might have dismissed with one of his signature cutting remarks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It relishes its myth-making enterprise without getting too cute about it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taylor-Wood captures the sounds and textures of Liverpool and Blackpool, where a new beat is playing in the cafes and clubs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Sam Taylor-Wood weaves this tale with elegance, spot-on costumes and production design, and finely tuned casting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>To watch Nowhere Boy is to appreciate anew both the anger that drove Lennon and the strength of character it took for him to overcome it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The reason to see Nowhere Boy is the charismatic Johnson, who effortlessly nails Lennon's strut, anger and sensitivity. Anybody seeing the movie could surely spot a star in the making.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A Great Man biography gone comically wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nowhere Boy is fully accessible for everyone, not just fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taylor-Wood stresses the universals rather than the specifics of John's youth. So don't go expecting a Fab Four origin story. The word Beatles is never uttered. But do go.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As sympathetic and well-turned as it is, Nowhere Boy only gives us more mythology.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>We reflect that even if all you need is love, that isn't always all you get.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As the story of a young man struggling to find his own identity, Nowhere Boy would work even if its protagonist hadn't grown up to change the world.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story of Lennon's early years is dramatic and painful enough to survive an imperfect retelling, even if you're already familiar with the stations of the cross.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Johnson does a terrific job of capturing Lennon's mannerisms without coming across like a puppet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taylor-Wood has specialized in video installations and off-kilter portraits, and it was tempting to hope that her take on Lennon would unsettle and provoke. Instead, she stays resolutely on-kilter, as if awed into numbness by her subject.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The events chronicled are all longstanding Beatles legends, though director Sam Taylor-Wood manages to stage even the most portentous moments without making you feel a celestial choir is in order.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More love triangle than musical, the effective and often sweet Nowhere Boy offers a sense of the time and tension that produced John Lennon.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This portrait of a Beatle as a young man also gives filmmaker Sam Taylor-Wood, working on a thoughtful script by Matt Greenhalgh, creative room to manoeuvre, introducing us to John just as he and rock 'n' roll discover one another.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although he doesn't look much like Lennon, Johnson captures that essence perfectly; the future icon is here a confused, hurt boy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie succumbs to maudlin sentiment and melodrama that Lennon himself might have dismissed with one of his signature cutting remarks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It relishes its myth-making enterprise without getting too cute about it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taylor-Wood captures the sounds and textures of Liverpool and Blackpool, where a new beat is playing in the cafes and clubs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Sam Taylor-Wood weaves this tale with elegance, spot-on costumes and production design, and finely tuned casting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>To watch Nowhere Boy is to appreciate anew both the anger that drove Lennon and the strength of character it took for him to overcome it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The reason to see Nowhere Boy is the charismatic Johnson, who effortlessly nails Lennon's strut, anger and sensitivity. Anybody seeing the movie could surely spot a star in the making.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A Great Man biography gone comically wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nowhere Boy is fully accessible for everyone, not just fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taylor-Wood stresses the universals rather than the specifics of John's youth. So don't go expecting a Fab Four origin story. The word Beatles is never uttered. But do go.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As sympathetic and well-turned as it is, Nowhere Boy only gives us more mythology.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>We reflect that even if all you need is love, that isn't always all you get.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As the story of a young man struggling to find his own identity, Nowhere Boy would work even if its protagonist hadn't grown up to change the world.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story of Lennon's early years is dramatic and painful enough to survive an imperfect retelling, even if you're already familiar with the stations of the cross.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Johnson does a terrific job of capturing Lennon's mannerisms without coming across like a puppet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is flash in the service of nothing, the proverbial sow's ear doing an indifferent imitation of a silk purse.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film often churns with the pleasure that visual stimulation can provide and more affection for the bang-bang techniques than you're likely to see in the movies of music-video directors simply making the jump to the big screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reveals that in Lee Myung-Se Korea has a filmmaker with enough razzle-dazzle and visceral appeal to rival Hong Kong's -- and Hollywood's -- John Woo.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee can't tell a story to save his life, but he's something of a visual magician, laying out glittering piles of goodies that you instinctively want to follow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nowhere to Hide may not be devoid of substance, but beneath the virtuoso finish it's rotten to the core.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A relentlessly corny and shamelessly derivative vehicle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When Van Damme is doing what he does best -- narcissistically displaying his body and thumping the bad guys -- the film works reasonably well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Several members of the Astor Plaza audience yesterday afternoon could not contain their merriment when, in the middle of the film, Mr. Van Damme's character identified himself as a lawyer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Except for a few short bursts here and there, and one extended scene during the climax, the film is mostly talk. And since Van Damme's range as a dramatic actor is marginal at best, this is a problem.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While it boasts better supporting actors and technical credits than other Van Damme projects, the film nonetheless founders, a victim of its own lugubrious pace and misguided efforts at turning the bulging Belgian into a romantic lead.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is the kind of movie that is so witlessly generic that the plot and title disappear into a mist of other recycled plots and interchangeable titles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A peculiar and neglected early Hitchcock stage adaptation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plotting is half-baked and the special effects are so crude that they make the back projection in Marnie look like the last word in verisimilitude.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A peculiar and neglected early Hitchcock stage adaptation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plotting is half-baked and the special effects are so crude that they make the back projection in Marnie look like the last word in verisimilitude.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The actors hold the movie together, particularly Ms. Zellweger and Mr. Freeman, whose characters achieve a remarkable intimacy in a most unlikely situation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In his third, most accomplished film, LaBute puts aside the inquiry of misogyny that dominated his previous work and immerses himself in a lighter romantic fable about the collision of fantasy and reality, with a terrific performance from Renee Zelwegger</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Almost every emotion and action on view is presented as false, idiotic or superficial.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>LaBute didn't write Nurse Betty, but his fierce comic touch is, luckily, all over this movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As with all good uses of enchantment, Nurse Betty deposits us, in the end, back where we started -- but different, changed, with new ways of looking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Zellweger is the best she's ever been.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This oddly cheerful, decreasingly dark comedy actually works and can boast some of the most enjoyable performances of the year.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[The actors'] nimble comic timing is hampered by truly ugly, amateurish production work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This fantasy-tinged romance leaves a distinctly bitter aftertaste.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nurse Betty is never going to be confused with Mary Poppins, but as of now, it's LaBute's crowd pleaser.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nurse Betty is one of those films where you don't know whether to laugh or cringe, and find yourself doing both.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Whether or not Betty sustains her character, the movie fails to maintain its own. The scenario falls apart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>LaBute, as always, has put together a great cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A masquerade that doesn't work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If Nurse Betty is any indication, these slightly more commercial movies won't be mere digressions or artistic sellouts; they'll be worth the wait, even if they aren't as distinctive or as sure-footed as his more challenging personal projects.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The flip side to LaBute's cheapjack cynicism, as it turns out, is a cheapjack romanticism. They're equally counterfeit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The actors are so expert and so congenially cast, and LaBute is so good at maintaining his agile, jokey tone, that his tale has an exhilarating flow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nutty Professor II: The Klumps is a waste of a brilliant actor</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Maybe even worth a return visit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sherman is no longer a fresh creation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Murphy] seems to be in a new flowering of his career.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is bloated by empty, unhealthy and unnecessary calories.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Never manages to feel like a sustained story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite the shameless laughs, it's still a disappointment.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>Jackson hasn't acted since making her feature film debut seven years ago in Poetic Justice.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An amazing cinematic feat of makeup and special effects.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nutty Professor II is neither funny nor endearing enough to conceal the fact that, like its star, it fills the screen with a lot of padding.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's no denying the comic genius Murphy displays again as the title character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lark for everybody concerned, including the audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This wholly enjoyable entertainment sees Soderbergh setting himself a new challenge - the hi-tech robbery procedural - and relishing the cliches even as he freshens them with a dab of polish, wit, pace and a light touch of irony.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It can, at times, be forgettable in a fun way, especially when its funniest performers are caught in Soderbergh's spinning crosshairs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fun-loving, carefully crafted romp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Forget Oscar, Ocean's Eleven is the coolest damned thing around.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] triumph of style and story...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite dashes of droll dialogue from screenwriter Ted Griffin, the remake aims for cool but instead gets chilly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Buzzes along at a mildly entertaining pitch from start to finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soderbergh's crisp, funny heist flick makes out like a bandit. George Clooney and Elliott Gould steal the show.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The perfect movie for New Year's Eve.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite a lot of snappy dialogue supplied by screenwriter Ted Griffin, Ocean's Eleven bogs down in technological minutiae, pointless set pieces that aren't very funny and by indulging the urge to constantly sell itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pure Hollywood moonshine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The new Ocean's Eleven is altogether different -- it isn't content to let star power, shtick and easy camaraderie carry the day; it works for your money.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To be sure, Soderbergh has proved his entertaining point, and done the Rat Pack one better, converting a paltry failure into a paltry success. But just how cool is that?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Vigorous, involving entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Admittedly, little of Ocean's Eleven is likely to hang around in your head past closing time. But that only gives you a good excuse to see it again.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I think it's time for Soderbergh to be leaving Las Vegas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It didn't shake me up and I wasn't much involved, but I liked it as a five-finger exercise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Top-of-the-line studio eye candy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A brand-new ride, complete with humor, action, explosives, good-looking men in tuxedos and high-tech toys.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Was Cruise trying to beat out fellow Scientologist John Travolta for the honor of starring in the dumbest sci-fi epic ever?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If nothing else, \"Oblivion\" will go down in film history as the movie where Tom Cruise pilots a white, sperm-shaped craft into a giant space uterus.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the sci-fi movie equivalent of a pretty damn good cover band.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Glossy, derivative, ambitious and fatally underpowered.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story eventually devolves into a grab bag of sci-fi tropes but, as with so many other Cruise productions, the sheer scale of everything is so mind-numbing that you may not notice.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The sly, surprising and visually magnificent Tom Cruise vehicle that has forced me - and many other people, I suspect - to revise my first opinion of director Joseph Kosinski.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oblivion is an okay blockbuster, a multimillion-dollar exercise in competence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kosinski offers plenty of action here, and he lets the plot reveals bleed out slowly (explanations keep coming right to the end). Yes, a great deal is derivative, but it's fast-moving derivative.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie that combines a lot of different films, yet somehow remains less than the sum of its parts ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More adventurous than your typical Hollywood tent pole, \"Oblivion\" makes you remember why science fiction movies pulled you in way back when and didn't let you go.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you're able to forgive and forget, Oblivion isn't a bad place to start loving Tom Cruise all over again.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Joseph Kosinski focuses on cool visuals but stints on a compelling plot. It's a dazzler, but the story lacks the impact of the futuristic look.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The mystery posed by \"Oblivion\" as a whole is why its mysteries are posed so clumsily, and worked out so murkily.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The agony of being a longtime Tom Cruise fan has always been a burden, but now it's just, well, dispiriting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Cruise] oversees some pretty impressive stuff here, from the drones that ping-pong around in the air to the bubbleship that Jack uses to go to and fro to that awesome house with its panoramic views.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kosinski's personal commitment to gorgeous artifice above all other considerations only harms the film so much.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Oblivion gives us stars in the cast, stars in our eyes and it even tweaks a brain cell or three.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is rife with elements from its finest predecessors - Kubrick, Lucas, the Wachowskis and Pixar could be listed as creative consultants - but it has the spirit of a love letter to classic sci-fi, not an opportunistic mash-up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Playing spot-the-influence is the most fun you'll have during this expensive-looking, slow-moving plod through familiar territory.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So \"Top Gun\" has become \"Wall-E.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After making what are still probably their two best features, the Coen brothers came up with their worst, a piece of pop nihilism.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Great dialogue, superb 'Scope camerawork from Roger Deakins, and a genuinely wondrous deus ex machina are among the delights.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Coens' usual arch deliberateness isn't quite as deliberate, and there's an appealing shagginess to some of the episodes and performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is a melange of so many clashing ideas, as well as a reference-tribute to so many moments in movie history.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a wild, whacked-out wonder.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Leaves a sour taste.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A roller-coaster ride with a goofy fun-house spirit, it's full of clever pranks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You have to admire how deep and irreverently O Brother goes into our culture to find its material.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>O Brother itself is just frustrating, mostly because we know what the Coens are capable of when truly inspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A flattening pile of artifice and conceit disguised as a road comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Devilishly delightful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Praiseworthy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An especially elaborate variation on Hee Haw.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A giddy merriment blessed with the Coens' skewed signature wit and the year's best soundtrack.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mixing dark humor with high spirits, the brothers take some wild risks that pay off surprisingly well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The surprise is how much fruitful digression such plotlessness makes possible. With no particular place to go, this hobo of a movie is free to roam the damnedest places.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A Coen brothers' also-ran is better than some filmmakers' best.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Joyously unhinged and outrageously inventive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Before it's all over, the real siren songs of time and place turn the visual kitsch into a distilled Americana that's unexpectedly stirring.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Bracing, bleak and berserk, this is a film which laughs in the face of American intolerance, and comes up punch-drunk and grinning.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I don't think it's much of a comedy. The darkness overpowers everything.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You don't relate or enjoy watching Seth Rogen's character on screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It falls short of brilliant but it's a lot more daring than what passes for 'dark comedy' these days, and it reminds us that 'feel bad' comedies may not always be as funny as 'feel good' ones but, when they work, they can ultimately be more satisfying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Observe and Report is a lot better when it's being funny than when it's rummaging in the shadows.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I don't want to oversell it, but Observe and Report is the sort of offbeat studio movie that should be encouraged.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In the end, Observe and Report falls in the somewhat confusing middle -- guaranteed to annoy the mainstream while not quite delivering the final twist and bitter irony the true comic cultists crave.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A few of the less repeatable lines hit their marks, but the whole affair has the pasty-faced desperation of shoppers trapped in fluorescent light.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The tone of the film wavers queasily, though intentionally, between slapstick and shock.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Writer-director Jody Hill is obviously trying to accomplish something here. But just what is none too clear.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The whole thing is calibrated to wow us with its weirdness, even as it assumes an air of 'Who, me?' guilelessness. I've seen slick, glossy Hollywood thrillers made with less knowing calculation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Meet mall cop Paul Blart's evil, unfunny twin.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aggressively mean and even more aggressively stupid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I've observed this Seth Rogen comedy, and I can report that it's not very good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Observe and Report strikes me as a comedy in perfect pace with this moment. It's funny and uncompromising, offering laughs without denial.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[T]he upbeat ending--which comes on the heels of a genuinely shocking climax--is so incongruous that, as with The King of Comedy, it almost seems we're being dared to question whether it is real or delusion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Director] Hill evidently intends his film to be satirical. But satire requires intelligence to succeed. Observe and Report has a moronic sense of humour, trading in racism, sexism, profanity and violence at every predictable turn.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A potentially brilliant conceptual comedy that fizzles because its writer and director, Jody Hill, doesn't have the guts to go with his spleen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A silly, contrived film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Elba and Larter are actually pretty good. Beyonce, through, strikes one note throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Don't think that exploiting female paranoia and the promise of Knowles throwing punches is enough to make up for your unabashed B-movie hitting the skids at the halfway point.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As far as the crazy-stalker-chick genre goes, Obsessed isn't horrible. It's just intensely simple-minded.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Spends much time spinning its wheels and making auds practically beg for an explanation to all the madness and obsession.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If the producers had done their work properly on Obsessed, I would not now be wishing I could reclaim the two hours I wasted on this tepid, sexless, thrill-free melodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Great-looking actors, glossy locations and a knock-down, drag-out girlfight still don't make Obsessed anything more than a predictable and tawdry Fatal Attraction-style guilty pleasure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Obsessed takes far too long to get cooking, and it works so hard at not being exploitation that it loses sight of its reasons for existing in the first place.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One doesn't expect a movie of this type to be plausible, but this one stretches the plausibility factor past the snapping point to the unintentional-laughter point.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Obsessed, is short on dimension and subtlety, but it turns into a mess believable enough to keep us invested.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Until Beyonce and Ali Larter duke it out at the climax, this is one dull film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Obsessed is a safe, dull morality play. The most that can be said on its behalf is that, unlike Fatal Attraction, no bunnies were boiled in the picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This biracial entry in the psycho-bitch stalker sweepstakes is inept and stupid but not without its base pleasures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I'd call this stenchcloud 'Fatal Attraction meets The Temp,' but that would insult those movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More like Delayed Frustration than Fatal Attraction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Obsessed, a clanking, low-rent imitation of Fatal Attraction, lacks both the original film's imagination and moral ambiguity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's doubtful that Obsessed will stick in the popular imagination for more than two weeks, because the movie is borderline ludicrous, and it jams its characters into rigid slots.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its notion of American artificiality runs so deep that the film begins and ends at a man-made surfing beach in the middle of the desert.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lark for everybody concerned, including the audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This wholly enjoyable entertainment sees Soderbergh setting himself a new challenge - the hi-tech robbery procedural - and relishing the cliches even as he freshens them with a dab of polish, wit, pace and a light touch of irony.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It can, at times, be forgettable in a fun way, especially when its funniest performers are caught in Soderbergh's spinning crosshairs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fun-loving, carefully crafted romp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Forget Oscar, Ocean's Eleven is the coolest damned thing around.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] triumph of style and story...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite dashes of droll dialogue from screenwriter Ted Griffin, the remake aims for cool but instead gets chilly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Buzzes along at a mildly entertaining pitch from start to finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soderbergh's crisp, funny heist flick makes out like a bandit. George Clooney and Elliott Gould steal the show.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The perfect movie for New Year's Eve.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite a lot of snappy dialogue supplied by screenwriter Ted Griffin, Ocean's Eleven bogs down in technological minutiae, pointless set pieces that aren't very funny and by indulging the urge to constantly sell itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pure Hollywood moonshine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The new Ocean's Eleven is altogether different -- it isn't content to let star power, shtick and easy camaraderie carry the day; it works for your money.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To be sure, Soderbergh has proved his entertaining point, and done the Rat Pack one better, converting a paltry failure into a paltry success. But just how cool is that?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Vigorous, involving entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Admittedly, little of Ocean's Eleven is likely to hang around in your head past closing time. But that only gives you a good excuse to see it again.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I think it's time for Soderbergh to be leaving Las Vegas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It didn't shake me up and I wasn't much involved, but I liked it as a five-finger exercise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Top-of-the-line studio eye candy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A brand-new ride, complete with humor, action, explosives, good-looking men in tuxedos and high-tech toys.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lark for everybody concerned, including the audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This wholly enjoyable entertainment sees Soderbergh setting himself a new challenge - the hi-tech robbery procedural - and relishing the cliches even as he freshens them with a dab of polish, wit, pace and a light touch of irony.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It can, at times, be forgettable in a fun way, especially when its funniest performers are caught in Soderbergh's spinning crosshairs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fun-loving, carefully crafted romp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Forget Oscar, Ocean's Eleven is the coolest damned thing around.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] triumph of style and story...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite dashes of droll dialogue from screenwriter Ted Griffin, the remake aims for cool but instead gets chilly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Buzzes along at a mildly entertaining pitch from start to finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soderbergh's crisp, funny heist flick makes out like a bandit. George Clooney and Elliott Gould steal the show.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The perfect movie for New Year's Eve.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite a lot of snappy dialogue supplied by screenwriter Ted Griffin, Ocean's Eleven bogs down in technological minutiae, pointless set pieces that aren't very funny and by indulging the urge to constantly sell itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pure Hollywood moonshine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The new Ocean's Eleven is altogether different -- it isn't content to let star power, shtick and easy camaraderie carry the day; it works for your money.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To be sure, Soderbergh has proved his entertaining point, and done the Rat Pack one better, converting a paltry failure into a paltry success. But just how cool is that?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Vigorous, involving entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Admittedly, little of Ocean's Eleven is likely to hang around in your head past closing time. But that only gives you a good excuse to see it again.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I think it's time for Soderbergh to be leaving Las Vegas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It didn't shake me up and I wasn't much involved, but I liked it as a five-finger exercise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Top-of-the-line studio eye candy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A brand-new ride, complete with humor, action, explosives, good-looking men in tuxedos and high-tech toys.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When a movie keeps you this entertained without insulting your intelligence, it's hard to complain.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a great looking movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Flat, abstruse, predictable and unable to raise your pulse rate higher than a blip on an EKG.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You get what you came for, namely the usual suspects breezily hamming it up and a lot of forgettable banter going down incredibly easily.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An entertaining night out at the movies. Have some popcorn.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though it takes a little while before it really takes off, this slick bauble of a movie qualifies as the best of the summer 'threequels\" -- at least thus far.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An exercise in stylish bravado that is as substantial as a catfight between supermodels.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Something seems to be off when the actors onscreen are having a better time than the audience. Just like the first Ocean's film, this isn't so much a movie as a private party.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all its forced twinkle, Ocean's Thirteen leaves you with no real warmth, like a croupier who's just cleaned you out before he wishes you a nice day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ocean's Thirteen is hack Hollywood garbage, the sort of film that thinks so little of its supposedly sure-thing audience that it never breaks a sweat. That's not cool; that's lazy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lightweight but altogether entertaining romp-reunion that seems like nothing more -- or less -- than a do-over for the Steven Soderbergh-George Clooney Gang's ponderous, too-hip-for-the room Ocean's Twelve.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Hollywood's version of Vegas, I'll have the surf, and the turf, and the vegetarian, and anything else Soderbergh wants to serve me.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Why put so much sheen on a movie that warrants and provokes nothing more than mild diversion? It's like serving sloppy joes on fine china.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This might be the first piece of escapism to have a whiff of public service at its heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Thematically, though, this is an improvement on its forebears, mainly due to the way it deals - much like Scorsese's best work - with the archaic nature of the criminal set.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hilarity-free.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's time to send the Danny Ocean franchise out to sea, for good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With Ocean's Thirteen, the gang's all here, looking fighting trim and Hollywood beautiful, at your disposable pleasure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Some of the bits are hysterical, but others fall flat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It does the hard work of being a light, smartly turned-out amusement, the sort of thing that's becoming more and more rare on the movie landscape these days.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In this sprawling oglefest, such things as 'narrative' and 'story' are remote little abstractions indeed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The whole thing is a piffle of fluff or a fluff of piffle. About halfway through you'll get an incredible hunger to see a movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In keeping with his general distaste for sequels -- this is his first, in fact -- Soderbergh has subverted all of the usual conventions, making the movie far more interesting than it has any right to be.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Much of the movie feels improvised, with laid-back actors tossing off one-liners that work far more often than they don't.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The pleasures are entirely in the digressions, which are silly and often delightful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rarely has crime seemed so glamorous, what with these mostly well-dressed, largely attractive, immature scamps languishing in posh surroundings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This slickly entertaining sequel is all about savoring eye candy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>How many movies recapture the blithe spirit of Frank Sinatra and his Rat Pack, plus a sense of old-school star glamour?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the movie's lack of pretentiousness is refreshing, there's also a nagging sense of laziness to it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ocean's Twelve feels like a lark, a dashed-off confiture that isn't so much a movie as an excuse for a bunch of old friends to hang out in Europe with somebody else paying the bill.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ocean's Twelve lacks the courage of its star-driven convictions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hey, these boys and girls just want to have fun. This time, though, it is at our expense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"October Baby\" looks and feels like a Lifetime movie waiting not to happen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The odds that this has happened in the real world approach those of being struck by lightning and eaten by a shark at the same time. With a winning lottery ticket tucked in your swimsuit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[An] earnest, faith-based drama, which lacks sufficient entertainment value to make its message go down more palatably.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"October Baby\" doesn't even meet the standards of decent propaganda. It is, in fact, indecent propaganda.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"October Baby\" may be well-intentioned, but it's as obvious and inert as a spoonful of mashed potatoes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Extended scenes are dominated by heavy dialogue, while the lighter moments are relegated to montages of prancing across a beach, for example, which simply aren't that effective at buoying the drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like the bloodied placards brandished by demonstrators outside women's health clinics, the film communicates in the language of guilt and fear.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The closer Hannah gets to her goal, the more insistent the sermonizing becomes. By the time she confronts the woman who rejected her (a careerist lawyer), we are neck-deep in Lifetime TV bathos.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A film whose poignancy is hard to deny whatever side of the abortion debate you fall on.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Directors Andrew and Jon Erwin, who also contributed to the story, rarely let their film get didactic, instead going for a more low-key approach.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film as a whole is amateurish and ungainly, can't find a consistent tone, is too long, is overladen with music that tries to paraphrase the story and is photographed with too many beauty shots that slow the progress.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A slick piece of pro-life propaganda, it has relatively luxe production values, painfully earnest performances, and a drippy \"inspirational\" score.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The TV movie subject matter is infused with genuine feeling for the value of learning as a passport to freedom, and an authentic regard for the honest graft of working men.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A professionally crafted family film that reserves all its challenging moments for its characters, letting the audience bask comfortably in the approach of a predetermined warm and fuzzy ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Immensely entertaining and unabashedly inspirational!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the best in recent years!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As adapted by Lewis Colick, the screenplay shifts busily among the boys' rocket exploits, Homer's family, conditions at the mine and the influence of a dedicated science teacher, but each of these subplots plays out in familiar ways.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweetness is too rare in movies these days, so audiences can feel lucky about the earnest dose of it in October Sky. This film is family.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another Universal Pictures paint-by-numbers feel-gooder!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Believable, subtle, and consistently intelligent!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is a film that treats its teen-aged hero and his pals as distinctive, sentient human beings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>October Sky will go straight to the heart of any man who recalls looking up at the night sky as a boy and getting stars in his eyes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This movie has deep values.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>October Sky is a sensational character-driven story with a strong narrative and great visual style.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A must-see for every student, parent and teacher in the country!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film remains an interesting oddity rather than entertaining or illuminating. Indeed, watching it today can seem hard work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Much of the montage is reductive and static, but some of the action scenes are genuinely stirring -- when he wasn't editorializing, the man really could cut film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Glen's willingness to give the action sequences a certain weight and seriousness produces some genuinely exciting moments, yet his work is everywhere undermined by the flatness of the characterizations and the uncertain architecture of the plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Film's high points are the spectaccular aerial stuntwork marking both the pre-credits teaser and extremely dangerous-looking climax.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bond had degenerated into a male model, and something of a genial anachronism.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The action sequences are tighter, the visual gags more inventive, and if the plot is no great shakes, the whole thing is served up with a decent approximation to the old panache.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Makes no pretense of being based on anything except the Ian Fleming character and the high good humor and wit of the film makers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a fine line between wit and absurdity, and this particular movie too often falls on the wrong side.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie has a vaunted place in the context of British cinema, and deservedly. Today, what Odd Man Out most suggests is a desperate endgame, the potentials of a long life snuffed out in a moment of impulsiveness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This may be Reed's most pretentious film, but it also happens to be one of his very best, beautifully capturing the poetry of a city at night.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Carol Reed has made his film with deliberation and care, and has achieved splendid teamwork from every member of the cast. Occasionally too intent on pointing his moral and adorning his tale, he has missed little in its telling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Carol Reed's first great postwar film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Odd Man Out is a picture to see, to absorb in the darkness of the theatre and then go home and talk about.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ichikawa's more straightforward narrative method doesn't do justice to all the ironies, but this is a still a singular and memorable movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of his most striking films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film cannily shifts through different points of view.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The point is made early; the rest is perversity without passion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A taut, downbeat, New York-shot bank heist thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ambitious but mainly unsuccessful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pasolini both humanizes the classical legend and reaches deep into the modern psyche to find its origins in ancient agonies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's not always necessary to understand Pasolini to be riveted by what he does.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pasolini's working of the Sophocles tragedy, though not wholly successful, has its very definite strengths.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the most underrated, neglected, and powerful of Pier Paolo Pasolini's features.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Frequently uproarious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A take-this-job-and-shove-it movie about the crushing malevolence of the corporate environment, it's on the verge of being really good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Some horrible Monday, why not cut work to see it?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The gags about the daily grind and what happens when a drone forgets how to be submissive make for beautifully low-key satire.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Judge's sense of the ridiculous serves him well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When Peter actively rebels and is ironically rewarded for his efforts by the head honchos, the picture loses its bite -- what began as discomfiting satire soon devolves into silly farce.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Judge may not be fully aware of how wildly talented he is, which, in a Hollywood culture swarming with talentless blowhards, makes him something of an anomaly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A surprisingly good-natured comedy about the suppressed rage and paranoia of unappreciated employees.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A nice meat-and-potatoes comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A forgettable, undistinguished movie!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As an update on eternal verities of life near the bottom rung of the corporate ladder, it's both knowing and amusing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's dialogue is smart. It doesn't just chug along making plot points.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Grasping and aimless!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fails to sustain its comic momentum or high energy level.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's essentially a series of shorts linked together, but this doesn't deny the movie's deft examination of the insane minutia that plague contemporary workers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Uproarious, cunning!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It has the loose-jointed feel of a bunch of sketches packed together into a narrative that doesn't gather much momentum.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A wily, inventive workplace comedy that's a scream in its finest moments and consistently amusing otherwise!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its plot may be a standard-issue office drone's revenge fantasy, but its characters and its nowheresville setting are uncannily realized.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Well-mounted and very traditional, Of Mice and Men honorably serves John Steinbeck's classic story of two Depression-era drifters without bringing anything new to it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's hard ... to believe Malkovich's shamble and gape, a simian variant on Dustin Hoffman's Rain Man.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Of Mice and Men is a mournful, distantly heard lament for the loss of American innocence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Happily, director/star/co-producer Gary Sinise has approached it not with the awe of an English professor, but with the practical eye of a craftsman: Here are solid characters, a taut and emotional story, a beginning, a middle and a wrenching end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I would not have thought I could believe the line about the rabbits one more time, but this movie made me do it, as Lennie asks about the farm they'll own one day, and George says, yes, it will be just as they've imagined it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The great pleasure of this movie is in what performers Sinise and John Malkovich, Ray Walton and others do with it; what director Sinise does with it; and, perhaps most important, what screenwriter Horton Foote does with it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The new film version of John Steinbeck's Of Mice and Men is lyrical, stirring, and beautifully acted -- a seamless adaptation of a novel many will recall with almost too much familiarity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An uneasy amalgam or inconsistent attitudes, without enough humor or zaniness to divert attention from its questionable premise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Carl Reiner's Oh, God! is a treasure of a movie: A sly, civilized, quietly funny speculation on what might happen if God endeavored to present himself in the flesh yet once again to forgetful Man.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>George Burns seems to be warming up for a good Second City sketch on God's return to earth as a rumpled vaudevillian, but it soon becomes clear that director Carl Reiner isn't kidding -- he really thinks this movie is going to save the world.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Shows few signs of life, and many signs of depressing modernism.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a total miscalculation from beginning to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Witty, playful, romantic, tragic, Park Chan-wook's I'm a Cyborg, but That's OK is a whole chocolate box of emotions in a highly decorative but absolutely characteristic wrapping.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is imbecilic hooey of the rarest breed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's kind of a funny story. Actually it isn't. And not much in this movie is, unless you like to watch elderly dogs urinate, middle-aged movie stars overact wildly, and Seth Green get hit in the groin by a golf ball.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This imbecilic, mean-spirited farce, which sneers at adults, leaves you wondering: where are the Three Stooges when we really need them?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>We have reached a point in our moviegoing life where the two most horrifying words a studio can mutter are \"Robin\" and \"Williams.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Old Dogs does to the screen what old dogs do to the carpet. It's unfortunate that only the latter can be taken out and shot.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>Travolta, who delivers an impressively enthusiastic performance, seems to have no idea that he's stuck in one of the year's worst movies. The perpetually pained expression on Williams' face, however, suggests he knows otherwise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The great thing about comedy these days is that few people are making movies like Old Dogs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfunny and uninspired, this dog deserves to be put down.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The ploy of pairing John Travolta and Robin Williams, whose salaries probably represented most of the budget, is the only pedigree Old Dogs has going for it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The timing of the comic set-ups is consistently amateurish, as if scenes were edited with hedge clippers, with the actors mugging frantically, waiting for the take to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>Is any of it believable for even one moment? Of course not. Do some of the jokes work? Sure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Only the irrepressible Luis Guzman, stuck in a walk-on bit as the stereotypical mooching Hispanic, is able to milk this cash cow and exit with his dignity intact.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A total train wreck.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Old Dogs is no fun whatsoever, just a collection of stale kibble.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Old Dogs seems to have lingered in post-production while editors struggled desperately to inject laugh cues. It obviously knows no one will find it funny without being ordered to.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though no animals were harmed in the making of Old Dogs, the lead actors were defanged. But like a pair of Labradors, they have a playful rapport.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is an irredeemable affair.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Old Dogs isn't the absolute worst movie either star has appeared in, it's close enough to count.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Phillips confesses to frat membership in his youth, and even made a documentary on the subject. So why is this not funnier or more outrageous?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Only fitfully funny, except when Ferrell is onscreen -- then you won't stop laughing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A flatland of lowest-common- denominated retro-collegiate wackiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a raucous frat-school comedy that's dopey, degrading and disgusting -- and consistently hilarious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An extremely funny and, of course, socially unredeemable comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie's enough to give you a big fat Greek dreading.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This year's kinder, gentler Animal House.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Unlike most of the lowbrow comedies in theaters these days, this one isn't quite a carp.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Has about a dozen funny moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Old School has all the ingredients of an uproarious campus comedy, but it lacks a boisterous short-order cook who could whip up a food fight or three.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's no school like this Old School, and this one earns high marks for hilarity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An unkempt clearinghouse for cheap, throwaway laughs. For those who regard that as a recommendation, two words: Grow up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sloppily made, frustratingly inconsistent, purposely lowbrow, blatantly derivative and never once enlightening in even the slightest way, Old School is also undeniably howl-out-loud funny at times.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This School is cool.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Old hat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is not a funny movie, although it has a few good scenes and some nice work by Ferrell as an apparently compulsive nudist.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Phillips has made a movie that should qualify as a date movie for guys who want to make sure their girlfriends understand just how immature they really are.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It comes from Disney's thoroughly proved mother lode: movies for the kids that adults will stay to enjoy themselves.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sentimental, yes, but also sturdy as a hickory stick.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The animation is fairly unexciting though serviceable, and the overall mystification of class difference would probably have made Dickens shudder, but kids should find this tolerable enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even as a cartoon poodle, Bette Midler stops the show.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Much cornball adventure ensues, punctuated by healthy helpings of singing, dancing and general merriment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film offers a fanciful, lush urban setting, unusual for Disney animated features, and a couple of good songs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Take the kids. Have fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The animation is fairly unexciting though serviceable, and the overall mystification of class difference would probably have made Dickens shudder, but kids should find this tolerable enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even as a cartoon poodle, Bette Midler stops the show.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Much cornball adventure ensues, punctuated by healthy helpings of singing, dancing and general merriment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film offers a fanciful, lush urban setting, unusual for Disney animated features, and a couple of good songs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Take the kids. Have fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's noble, high-minded and safe, and I can't help thinking that I would have preferred an audacious but honest failure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Great expectations are unavoidable when Roman Polanski takes on a Charles Dickens classic. Alas, his version of Oliver Twist fails to live up to them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A grounded and unusually matter-of-fact adaptation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Poignant and primal, Roman Polanski's splendid adaptation of the Charles Dickens classic pricks the heart and the conscience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In Oliver Twist, it's the viewer who is punished.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Oliver Twist is a lovely, tony picture, but it isn't exactly essential.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nitpickers may squawk over missing elements, but the film doggedly hits on the book's big themes: the power of innocence, the cruelty of class.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oliver Twist as presented by Roman Polanski is pretty much the same as Oliver Twist presented by anyone else, except perhaps it's a bit duller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As handsomely made, well-acted, dramatically unflinching and heartfelt as it is, Polanski's Oliver is a movie more admirable than emotionally affecting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Polanski's Oliver proves surprisingly uninspired, taking nearly the entire movie before it belatedly springs to life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is worth seeing, but it won't hold a cherished place in your moviegoing memories.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's as though Polanski had set the story's foolproof motor on cruise control and left the room; the tale is well told but told without personality.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Technically sound and surprisingly faithful to its source material, Roman Polanski's version of Oliver Twist comes across as uninspired and flat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Perhaps it will take a school trip to encourage kids to see Oliver Twist, but that's one permission slip parents should sign.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Seeing Polanski's version of this most Dickensian of all Charles Dickens' tales, I felt full and wanted no more versions (please, sir!), having now seen the definitive one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is high on production values but short on heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Polanski's Oliver Twist is craftsmanly and relatively unsentimental.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Polanski's film is visually exact and detailed without being too picturesque.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No less than an epic look at society is created in Lindsay Anderson's third and most provocative film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>O Lucky Man! is a disappointment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>O Lucky Man! clearly has a number of things on its mind, but as a movie, it is a very mixed bag.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I thought it was mischievous and witty and amusing and I was just sort of drawn into it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's not enough to compensate for the computer-game-style plotting, which is largely based on us picking up narrative nuggets that mechanically slot into place later on.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Chris Columbus has brought together the modern and mythical spheres with sharp pacing and a nifty sense of fun that atone for the film's dippier moments. It's his most enjoyable effort since Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dutifully Potteresque it begins, and dutifully Potteresque it ends.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Has all the CGI sorcery of a Harry Potter pic, but none of the magic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Percy Jackson, you are no Harry Potter. You are not fit to walk in a hobbit's wake.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Harry, Ron and Hermione: Relax. You could whip Percy Jackson and his pals with your wand hands tied behind your backs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film toggles between high camp and deadly earnestness, all the while threatening to drown in an ocean of not-so-special effects.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Likable as Percy may be, it's not lightning he's stolen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a kids' movie: Parents can either get into the silly-suspenseful spirit of it or play Rummikub on their iPhones.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like its stars, the film is genial good company.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, the movie lacks that good old Potter charm, trading Harry's dark whimsy for a handful of CGI magic beans.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When the movie slows down to catch its breath, there's very little of the heart and soul -- and wry wit -- that make the Riordan books so beloved.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Although the standard allegorical bases for mythical-quest movies are dutifully covered, the obvious similarity of Percy Jackson to the Harry Potter movies inevitably makes it feel somewhat secondhand.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You don't even have to be familiar with the first book in Rick Riordan's popular fantasy series to enjoy Chris Columbus' energetic adaptation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is generic filmmaking at its most banal, a simple-minded simplification of a not overwhelmingly complex book.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The fireballs are great but the story feels confused in its tone and direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Kids may well enjoy the adventures of The Lightning Thief on screen, but I think most readers will prefer the movie in their imaginations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An attempt to steal some of Harry Potter's thunder that also stands on its own as a well-made large-scale adventure that works well enough to entertain the teens it's hoping to strike.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With great effects (and a few surprises) it's a fun, Saturday-matinee adventure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The thrills and the effects are cheap, but this is in hard-driving, good-humoured command of its own silliness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This ludicrous actioner strives to be as loud, violent, and patriotic as possible.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fuqua doesn't deliver on what he has set up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Olympus Has Fallen is a disgusting piece of work, but it certainly hits its marks - it makes you sick with suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The carnage is cruel and crude.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A typical slab of Hollywood action in which the White House crumbles under attack, the American flag is tattered and tossed aside by baddies, and cliches rise like gods.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>'Olympus Has Fallen is just too much of a pale 'Die Hard' ripoff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>... the action is often not unengaging, and Butler's better at swinging for faux Bruce Willis ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Given the premise's essential absurdity, it's almost embarrassingly entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Olympus Has Fallen\" goes through plenty of familiar motions, but does them well enough that it gets away with it. There's a reason movies like this die hard.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is a second-rate \"Air Force One\" mashed up with a third-rate \"Die Hard,\" with Gerard Butler striving mightily to be charismatic as the One Man Who Can Save the Day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"Olympus Has Fallen\" at least possesses the frisson of timeliness amid otherwise hoary action-movie cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a solid, simple, more-bang-for-our-buck entertainment that doesn't ask us to think.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A nitwit extravaganza that makes you long for the intellectual depth of Independence Day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It has to be a joke, right?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sadly, Mr. Butler lacks the wit and the range to convey anything other than grouchy belligerence, and the script, by Creighton Rothenberger and Katrin Benedikt, seems intent on squandering opportunities to be clever or interesting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is for those who like their political thrillers far-fetched, far-reaching and filled with pretty people.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While Gerard Butler is no Bruce Willis, his Mike Banning is a better facsimile of John McClane than the guy Willis is pretending to play these days.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"Olympus\" has a strictly director-for-hire vibe; anyone with access to a Roland Emmerich movie or two (namely \"Independence Day\") and a mad-libbed action script could have churned out something similar.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[A] plodding and pretentious historical drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The writing, acting and direction are so amateurish that the only thing you'll care about is escaping the theater.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The director approaches the enormity of his task with an earnest enthusiasm, offering a likable alternative to the assembly-line banality of so many family films.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story behind the making of The Keeper is more inspiring than the film itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ambitious, heartfelt and grand in both its ideas and its pride of place (the Middle East), the film suffers from its virtues.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A reverentially pokey drama that plays less like a conventional movie than a lengthy series of hagiographic historical tableaux.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie's intentions are like the starry constellations that inspire the eponymous hero: out of reach.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In story structure, performances, pacing, and dialogue, the film's the work of a first-timer. In its deep love for an ancestral culture, it shines.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rough around the edges, it's still a formidable movie that's stunning visually.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An accomplished first film that manages to comment on the current situation in the Middle East while dealing movingly -- and in very human terms -- with the importance of heritage and history in contemporary life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An overall satisfying experience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>...the moment The Final Conflict turns to dialogue and a plot, it loses its inspiration.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The bad news is that Damien has a whole movie to get through before he gives up the ghost, and that the movie is a grisly one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This rather overbearing romantic comedy is by no means a disaster.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ethnic romances from Abie's Irish Rose to Moonstruck have traveled similar ground, but few have handled the role of family in a marriage more poignantly than Once Around.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first movie in a long time to leave me speechless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is no there there, just the dead red glow of the beckoning Exit light.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>On the whole Once Around is strangely enervating, proof that family problems -- even those of fictional families -- are often best kept behind closed doors.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sergio Leone's languid, lovely and lengthy ode to Lower East Side mobsters (more specifically, mobster films) ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Leone is less interested in arousing an audience's easier emotions than in presenting, at a dispassionate distance, the horror of two men warily walking toward each other on a tightrope suspended above the snake pit of their , deepest compulsions.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Every gesture is immediate, and every gesture seems eternal.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A disappointment of considerable proportions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While Leone's vision still has a magnificent sweep, the film finally subsides to an emotional core that is sombre, even elegiac, and which centres on a man who is bent and broken by time, and finally left with nothing but an impotent sadness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are times when we don't understand exactly what is happening, but never a time when we don't feel confidence in the film's narrative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As one would expect from Leone, the film is a brilliant stylistic accomplishment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Seeing what Leone always intended is like getting your dirty glasses washed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie of such dark, smoldering intensity that it's easy to forget that half of it takes place in near darkness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A police procedural as existential inquiry, set in a remote dreamscape of mystery and foreboding.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ceylan's visual style is less heightened, more down-to-earth than the more stylised 'Three Monkeys', but still some of the night-time scenes look like careful paintings, such is the precision of their lighting and composition.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ceylan doesn't slap us with big dramatic moments, but allows us to live along with his characters as things occur to them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is epic in its aims and achievements yet modest in its resources: some superb actors, stunning landscapes and a resonant, understated script.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A gorgeously shot crime story with emotionally layered characters and an indelible atmosphere of unease.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This painstaking but gorgeously realized police procedural by Nuri Bilge Ceylan, the Turkish poet of the long take, nods to Sergio Leone's Once Upon a Time in the West.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is colossally, memorably and audaciously boring, but if you stick with it - and I am not advising this - something may happen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ceylan is as calculatedly withholding a storyteller as ever, and as one might expect, Anatolia never comes right out and explains itself, though the men's free-ranging conversations suggest the film has much on its mind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A long, slow haul but for the willing, a haunting journey into the heart of darkness in Turkish Anatolia.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gorgeous to look at, intriguing to think about and, at times, hard to sit through.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A subtle, gorgeous and mysterious allegory that may be Ceylan's masterwork to date.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Turn the movie this way, and it's a police procedural that's tragicomically heavy on minutiae while slyly suggesting that official evidence always lies. Turn it that way, and it's an existential fairy tale set in a nocturnal netherworld.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's too much beauty and ballast in the movie's early stages to dismiss Ceylan's cerebral cop drama, and too much genuine banality in its latter acts to justify a sluggish slouch into the shallow end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is very little overt drama. The camera waits, and watches, like a vulture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Patient viewers will be rewarded, as long as they pay attention.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A metaphysical road movie about life, death and the limits of knowledge, \"Once Upon a Time in Anatolia\" has arrived just in time to cure the adult filmgoer blues.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its real strengths are its choreography, its flashes of wit, and its all-round exuberance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A witty, extravagantly picturesque homage to Sergio Leone.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gets better as it goes along, building up to a prolonged shipboard finale.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the best action-adventure-comedy that Tsui has ever made, hence one of the year's most exhilarating entertainments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A splendid if frankly fake-looking spectacle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More concentrated and svelte than its precursor, Once Upon a Time II also has the benefit of fights staged by Master Yuen Wo-Ping that show Jet Li-another camera-age hero-to even greater advantage.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Giving it a title that suggests an Eastern version of a Sergio Leone epic raises expectations that can't be fulfilled.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie with that many freaks and creeps should be a lot more exciting than this one actually is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A mess of a movie that nevertheless entertains because each individual piece stands high enough on its own merits that it's not necessary to look hard at the nonsensical linking material.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... this proves as the opposite of Cabin Fever, you can spill a lot of blood in a gratuitous, but very entertaining way.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Make no mistake, this movie is a mess. But, wow, what a mess!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Depp, a mere two months after his scene-stealing turn in Pirates of the Caribbean, once again is the best thing about a very silly movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A whiz-bang kick in the pants.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's at once busy and lacklustre, intricately plotted yet indifferently paced, handsomely mounted but made from plastic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Whenever Rodriguez is in a Fairbanks mood, Mexico delivers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite the movie's dark humor, violence and the occasional nonvoluntary facial surgery that will drive away the queasy, Once Upon a Time in Mexico is the most crowd-pleasing film in the series.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A winking exercise in actors acting cool and the amoral joys of trigger- happiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rodriguez's movie aspires to trashy grandeur, and achieves it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A heady mix of Tarantino-esque pulp.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Shamelessly violent and shallow.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I understood the general outlines of the story, I liked the bold strokes he uses to create the characters, and I was amused by the camera work, which includes a lot of shots that are about themselves.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lusty, zesty goof.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Dazzling visuals, ambitious stunts and enough raw action to please the most demanding fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez infused Desperado with style and pulpy energy. Here the bravado is by-the-numbers and way too familiar.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Paying homage to Sergio Leone, Mexico aims too high and, in the process, becomes more like every generic, overplotted drug-cartel- and-revenge flick out there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Depp, who looks and dresses eerily like Michael Jackson near the end, has an appealing breeziness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Once Upon a Time...' now looks like an over-cooked mess of style, metaphor and reference.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Western is dead - or so they tell us. Long live Leone's timeless monument to the death of the West itself, rivalled only by Peckinpah's Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid for the title of best ever made.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is mostly fun for the way it cherishes movie styles and attitudes from the past.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie stretches on for nearly three hours, with intermission, and provides two false alarms before it finally ends.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the greatest face movies ever made.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A gut-grabber from New Zealand ... that stays with you for days.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As often happens when films are intent on getting a message across, Once Were Warriors can't stop itself from overdoing things.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yet familiar as the pattern is ... the film holds because of the acting and because it functions as travelogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The actors, many of them of European-Maori descent, are wonderful to look at. They also deliver authoritative yet sympathetic performances that get at the roots, or rootlessness, of their characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is powerful and chilling, and directed by Lee Tamahori with such narrative momentum that we are swept along in the enveloping tragedy of the family's life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Works, to some degree, on three levels: the visceral, the emotional, and the intellectual, and it is the amalgamation of these that makes this a memorable film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reserve judgment until this raw, uncompromising working-class saga is over, and you might find yourself unforgettably moved -- and grateful for the experience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Violent melodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a vanity production parading as a social statement.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In contrast to his short, sharp fighting style, Seagal's presentation of the human conflicts and underlying issues consists of vague, sweeping gestures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You can't preach about preserving the environment and make movies full of sludge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The less said about Joan Chen, the better. To say that her talents are wasted is to understate the matter.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Martial arts maven Seagal has long been on deadly ground with critics, and this, his directorial debut, is likely to keep him there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's impossibly romantic; Farrell and real-life partner Bachleda exude a tamped-down longing that intensifies as the movie draws to its conclusion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Some complexities of story will be lost on audiences not tuned to the regional Irish brogue that is the mother tongue of this little fishing community. But Christopher Doyle's dark lush photography plucks the green coast of Cork like a harp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Among the film's pleasures is a disarmingly tender performance from the new, improved Colin Farrell.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Silkies aren't the only creatures who can inhabit two worlds. As Annie knows, and as Jordan's film makes clear, stories enable us to step outside the quotidian world and dream, if only for an hour or two.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Jordan starts to tell an intriguing tale about living with fantasy but falls back on plot turns cued to the flashing lights of cops and paramedics.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lyrical, if slight, breeze of an Irish fable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jordan, who also wrote the screenplay, makes some gentle jabs at small-town nosiness and claustrophobia, even as he spins out the shadowy riddles of the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ondine is so good it hurts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The characters' needs are so simple they're almost mysterious, and the story traces an elusive line between fond fantasy and harsh reality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This movie is a one-of-a-kind experience -- blarney carried to rhapsodic heights.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If this movie were a human being, it would be intelligent and sincere but so depressed as to be unable to get out of bed without a forklift.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Full of melancholy and blarney...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Women tend to hide secrets in the original scripts of filmmaker Neil Jordan.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It sort of falls flat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are some interesting secondary characters, but you didn't get I thought a full enough sense of this world and it's dramatic stakes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Ondine, a film about a fisherman and a mythical sea creature, Neil Jordan shows his fondness for fantasy worlds.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is enough saving grace on these craggy shores to let the mists and the legends roll in and envelop you for a while.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Intoxicatingly beautiful...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Why is the dialogue so muffled and clipped that it's hard to understand? Why didn't Mr. Jordan spend more time grounding his self-enchanted script in some semblance of reality?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] bright, occasionally imbecilic teen comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>John Cusack and Demi Moore are such charming personalities that they are appealing even in so silly a setting. There is a good chemistry between them. It would be interesting to see them make a film together, instead of being stock figures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Both lovers are duplicitous creeps -- in a perverse way they're made for each other.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When a chick flick goes wrong -- and this one hits a dead end in hell -- it's a wipeout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This tortured premise to get them together and the things they go through, every minute of it just lies flat on the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Isn't as bad as it looks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Resorts to the kinds of cliches that were so yesterday two weeks ago.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too light on laughs and too heavy on predictable moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For once, here's a screen couple that easily adds up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a movie that never aspires to be anything more than dimwitted fun, then falls on its aspirations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's about as close to French farce as romantic comedies get, and the closer the better.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Button-cute.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Trite, contrived, but often entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After a frothy start, How to Lose (an apt abbreviation) becomes a one-joke comedy of slapstick suffering.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sure delight for both guys and gals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You not only have to be seriously testosterone- deprived to survive this film without embarrassment, you have to buy a romantic premise so ridiculously contrived that even Dr. Ruth might suspect someone was pulling her little leg.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lackluster.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The hottest couple to come down the pike recently has been Frodo and Sam. Hudson and McConaughey rate higher on the spark-o-meter.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One Fine Day is two formulaic hours, but they do illustrate how two attractive leads and a lickety-split narrative can elevate meager material into something this side of bearability.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a lot here. But with a classic like Cuckoo's Nest, too much is never enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One Flew over the Cuckoo 's Nest is an earnest attempt to make a serious film. But in the end the movie backs away from both the human reality and the cloudy but potent symbolism that Ken Kesey found in the asylum.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jack Nicholson stars in an outstanding characterization of Ken Kesey's asylum anti-hero, McMurphy, and Milos Forman's direction of a superbly-cast film is equally meritorious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jack Nicholson plays McMurphy as if he were born to it, and the supporting cast provides fine, detailed performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Set in an insane asylum, the film involves the oppression of the individual, a struggle spearheaded by an ebullient Nicholson, turning in a star performance if ever there was one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even granting the artist his license, America is much too big and various to be satisfactorily reduced to the dimensions of one mental ward in a movie like this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Is One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest not a great film because it is manipulative, or is it great because it is so superbly manipulative? I can see it through either filter.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Hartzell Spence's deeply affectionate biography of his ministerial father, William Spence, the Warners have derived a cheerful and warmly compassionate film, an excellent character study and an adult entertainment on the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A warm and human preachment for godliness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's stiff sense of virtue won it an Oscar nomination, but more impressive is Scott's weirdly distant performance as a woman who impulsively accepts the life of a church mouse and then finds she can't do much for her children.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An avalanche of grating big-hair-and-bad-accent New Joisey caricatures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An ungainly mix of flat-footed gumshoeing and strained attempts at hilarity, all delivered with an unconvincing Joizy vibe.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie has the by-the-numbers efficiency of a decent TV series, and about as much flavor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There have been notable exceptions, but Heigl tends to imbue her characters with an off-putting mix of insecurity and abrasiveness. This film is a prime example.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I guess I can't call the movie sexist as it was largely produced, directed and written by women. So I'll settle for calling it dull, corny and amateurish instead.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is action of a sort -- a car blows up, shots are fired -- and what might pass for witty, sexy banter to someone who once overheard a conversation about an episode of Moonlighting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Imagine an Elmore Leonard movie scripted by a bad Nora Ephron imitator, and you'll have an idea of how dead-in-the-Jersey-water it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Punitively dull.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Everything in One for the Money rings cringingly false.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tedious and tonally inept.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Janet Evanovich's best-selling Stephanie Plum series deserved better than this woefully executed, stillborn attempt at a franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Heigl, sporting tousled brunette locks, gives a busy, unconvincing performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One for the Money is tepidly glib throughout. Even violent murders are followed by wisecracks or another prurient opportunity to ogle Heigl's behind and cleavage.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To compare this mess to a sitcom would be an insult to sitcoms.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A hybrid musical romantic fantasy, lavishing giddy heights of visual imagination and technical brilliance onto a wafer-thin story of true love turned sour, then sweet.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At times the project seems in danger of being scuppered by its own lavishness; the saving grace is a light heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An interesting production but not a good movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's not a moment in One From the Heart when Mr. Coppola isn't after something romantic and glorious, something inexpressibly grand. At times, he even gets what he's after.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[An] often maligned, giddy, superlative romantic musical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A playful, delightfully unfathomable piece of magic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An integral piece of the oeuvre of one of America's great directors.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A bold experiment in style and technique that doesn't work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An ambitious misfire by a brilliant filmmaker.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Underwritten and overdirected.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It still feels like an exercise, but it's a beautiful one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It isn't very good, but at least the highly touted technology is put firmly in the service of the (sometimes painfully sincere) emotions that Francis Ford Coppola wants to communicate, which is more than you can say for Apocalypse Now.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This immaculately made first feature from noted musicvid and commercials director Mark Romanek provides Robin Williams with one of his creepiest, atypical roles, and the comic star responds with an unusually restrained performance...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It has arresting things to say about how the family photo is used less to record than to project, and how far that projection can be from the truth.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sy's scary ordinariness is a species of acting stunt. There's no there there.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not entirely satisfying as either a creepfest or a character study.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Romanek's themes are every bit as distinctive as his visuals. Beyond the cleverness, the weirdness and the pristine camerawork, One Hour Photo is a sobering meditation on why we take pictures.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ranks among Willams' best screen work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Williams's exacting performance -- not a note of it is unconsidered -- makes us feel more for Sy than we'd like to.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It begins by scaring you to death by evoking a monster, and by the end it has seduced you into caring for him.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An impressive debut ... rich with detail and cool-blue style.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Williams absolutely nails Sy's queasy infatuation and overall strangeness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all its merits, One Hour Photo winds up as just another exercise in genre, although an assured and effective one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Romanek keeps adding flourishes -- artsy fantasy sequences -- that simply feel wrong. They cheapen the overall effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Williams finally gets a role so smartly written we forget not only that we are watching Williams the dramatic actor, but that we are watching Williams at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thought-provoking, artful accomplishment by writer/director Mark Romanek, who reveals a powerfully understated vision of the haunting loneliness behind the forced cheerfulness of the discount store.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Williams has now proven that he can play creepy with the best of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are weird resonances between actor and role here, and they're not exactly flattering.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>(Williams) has never slipped this far under the radar, and the result is a spooky, unsettling performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With its mixture of chilling suspense and poignant drama, it will shake your nerves and stir your emotions.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It has Williams -- memorably creepy, chillingly sad.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Dark and unrepentant, this excursion into the epicenter of percolating mental instability is not easily dismissed or forgotten.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One big miss of a horror movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's hard to know what's scarier-the fact that Asia keeps producing these movies, or that Hollywood keeps on remaking them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The best part of the movie is the fact that, at a running time of an hour and a half, it's mercifully short.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Given all the hoopla over the Apple iPhone, it's a wonder that no one has yet complained over an essential missing feature: It doesn't ring you up to alert you that you are going to die.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another demonstration of how certain studios and producers care neither about us nor the skill required to pull off a respectable work of garbage.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A brow-furrowing blend of child abuse and adult trauma, Andrew Klavan's screenplay sacrifices coherence for atmosphere at every turn.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Give this call a miss.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The worst part about this movie is that, even though it's impossible to piece everything together logically, it's easy to see where it's going because there's nothing new here. There's a sameness to all these Japanese-turned-American retreads.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script appears to blatantly rip-off plot devices and story elements from The Ring, but screenwriter Andrew Klavan avoids plagiarism by tacking on an incomprehensible second ending where Ring would have left off.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another mediocre remake of a Japanese horror film in which flashes of computer-generated ghosts are meant to compensate for lousy acting and a banal storyline.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Decent if derivative.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pity this most mysterious 'Can you hear me now?' of all is spoiled by too many answers to too many questions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The deadliest call the cast and crew of One Missed Call ever received was the one from their agent telling them that this was the best work available.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One Night of Love is basically an operatic film. It's the fact that the film is human, down to earth, that helps most.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An enjoyable light diversion, one worthy of the charm and talent of its stellar performer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Watching these people create on little or no sleep offers a delightful window into just how deep the talent pool still is for New York theater.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"One Night Stand\" manages to illuminate something very real about theater, the way each craft contributes to the whole and the sense of community that can develop, even in a day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Why another version of this oft-filmed tale?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie devolves into a talky, static affair featuring a cast with wildly varying accents and acting abilities.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately [O'Toole and Sharif are] separated by five centuries, and never share a scene. For a movie with the most righteous of intentions, that's perhaps the most grievous moviemaking sins of all.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cinematography and sets look great, but the script is a bummer. It's overlong, overwrought and overblown.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In itself, it's a riveting story. Unfortunately, director Michael Sajbel has envisioned an overwrought Lifetime movie of the week, complete with an Esther who could be a cast member of Laguna Beach and a king notable only for his washboard abs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Blessed with abundant production values and a minimum of campy excess, One Night With the King is a surprisingly satisfying attempt to revive the Old Hollywood tradition of lavishly appointed Biblical epics aimed at mainstream auds.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stiles grows into her character and Ledger is effortlessly charming.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stiles nails her feminazi, bound-for-Sarah Lawrence shtick, but just as easily melts into giggles or pulls off a slapstick drunk scene.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie wimped out by blanding down the story and the characters to the point where she isn't really a shrew and he isn't really a maniac.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The notion of a contemporary high school as a hotbed of romantic intrigue is utterly apt, and the performances almost make the update work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As satirical as it is romantic, this is one teen film that is wise enough to span generations in its appeal.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stiles, whose slightly rushed, impatient delivery sometimes recalls the young Jane Fonda, lets enough sweetness seep into her portrayal to lend even the nastiest retort a hint of forgiveness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No one in this film is a big star, but everyone is a capable actor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Miller is outstanding as a father who is utterly convinced that dating is the first step towards instant and complete moral and sexual decay.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The high school romance genre has become so popular that it's running out of new ideas and has taken to recycling classic literature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Debut film director Gil Junger may be a TV veteran making a movie for the Clearasil crowd, but he doesn't sacrifice the story to gimmicky camerawork or overzealous pacing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not only does the use of the song impose a sense of emotional fulfillment upon a conclusion that does not ask for it, but also the use of the song's title for the movie suggests a meaning that is less interesting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The script shifts audience sympathies about quite adroitly, though it's a pity all the men had to be such humbugs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A well-oiled machine manufactured to tap our welled-up ducts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even director Carl Franklin...can't prevent One True Thing from descending into chick-movie hell.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One True Thing demonstrates that the power of simple things, the transcendent nature of the ordinary, can make for riveting filmmaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is the craftsmanship that elevates One True Thing above the level of a soaper.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Meryl Streep is an actress of such transcendent skill and sympathy that she regularly elevates her material, taking it up several notches and giving us feelings, insights, feelings and textures the original writer may have just missed expressing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yes, Meryl Streep is phenomenal again!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Franklin seems ill-suited to this cast and this material.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One True Thing celebrates the very things you don't miss, or even know exist, until they are gone.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Streep's performance makes the movie worth seeing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An emotional drama!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although the plot rarely excels, the actors bring enough to their roles to transform this motion picture into a satisfying weeper.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its strong cast and restrained direction lift it above the Kleenex.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Streep and Hurt, two of the best gestural actors working, let the showboating tics fly fast and thick.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Streep is luminous as the hypermaternal Kate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sensitively written, fluidly directed and expertly acted!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Streep shines!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One True Thing is real enough to be a film you can believe in.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Can a director be arrested for the attempted hijack of our emotions?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Washington demonstrates his really remarkable ability to make us forget he's a movie star and completely believe he's a flawed but noble civil servant.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I was really disappointed by this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Whereas the original, directed by Joseph Sargent, was essentially a well-oiled B movie, the new incarnation, directed by Tony Scott, is bristling with high-tech gimcrackery and over-the-top camera flourishes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Set in a nightmare New York City, the subway hostage thriller batters our nerves like a tom-tom.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film does what a good hostage negotiator does: It distracts us from what's going wrong and pulls us into the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The new Pelham, although no classic, is a lot of fun if you're in the right mood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>We've been waiting too long for a sharp little urban thriller with a couple of tense scenes and one fine, bold performance. Given the time, we'll grab this express train, happily.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Helgeland's story is so formulaic and the characters so stock that we're just sitting there waiting for these guys to perform like circus animals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Most disappointing is the new film's reluctance to even attempt to match the ingenuity of the original movie's celebrated one-two punch ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pelham is not merely a film that may induce seizures in those who are susceptible; it is a film that seems engineered to approximate the experience of a seizure for those who are not.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It ticks along as efficiently as a new clock. The performances are smooth, the car-crash effects remarkable, the pace never flagging.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kinetic director Tony Scott balances his need for speed and flash with fleshed-out drama, making Pelham the best of his recent outings.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At first it's exciting, but as the film progresses, that quick-cut, never-stop pacing seems increasingly desperate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Against all odds and better advice, director Tony Scott, screenwriter Brian Helgeland and main protagonists Denzel Washington and John Travolta take a much-loved genre classic and arguably make it better.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a carefully composed, elegant, sometimes prescient work, a small-scale love story set against a background of tumultuous social and political change.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's like looking for footprints, tracking the master this apprentice was to become.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a 'little people' comedy in the Frank Capra vein</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is a natural rhythm to the film that makes its own quiet, life-affirming statement.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When it sometimes seems the whole society has spiritually decamped for Tinseltown, the movie offers the hope that people can come home again-at least for a visit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Without question, these are major, meaty roles for Katharine Hepburn and Henry Fonda, and there could have been little doubt that the two would work superbly together.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Two of Hollywood's best-loved veterans deserved a far better swan song than this sticky confection.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Watching the movie, I felt I was witnessing something rare and valuable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>On Golden Pond is a mixed blessing, but it offers one performance of rare quality and three others that are very good. That's not half-bad.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cinematic equivalent of shrink-wrapping, in which all of the ideas, feelings, characters, and images are neatly separated and hermetically sealed to prevent spoilage, abrasion, or any contact with the natural world.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Film of break-neck physical excitement and stunning visual attractions in which George Lazenby replaced Sean Connery as James Bond.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Bond films were bad enough even with the partially ironic performances of Connery.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What are Bond's problems now? They're too numerous, as usual, to hold the constant attention of anyone other than a charter member of Her Majesty's Secret Service.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It offers supremely satisfying versions of all the conventions we expect from the series ... and then it does the one thing you don't expect a James Bond movie to do: It breaks your heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too often, it turns out to be a pot-pourri of ravenous eating and blatant sex.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No masterpiece by any means, it's at times overplayed, but it's striking visually, handling swift horizontal movement very well. It's also genuinely erotic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Although his artistic integrity remains untarnished, his driven rustic principals are exotic, sometimes grotesque figures out of medieval Japan, to whom a Westerner finds it hard to relate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a fairly good melodrama, nothing more.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie that exists solely for its fight sequences and to show off its star's muscles and gymnastic grace.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is clumsily assembled and edited, heavy on the slow-mo, and its simplistic story plays like The Kids From Fame armed with very sharp knives.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If only the plot were a little less obvious, the confrontations a little less cliched.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I expected it to be an obligatory late-summer, mindless, plotless action film. I was wrong. It's a late-summer, mindless, plotless action film with a message. I think I prefer this sorts of film when it doesn't try to preach.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I have a sinking feeling that the makers of this film feel it is in some way exemplary and even useful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Casting is the key here, and Ms. Finzi chose wisely.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Finzi's lovingly filmed movie draws viewers into the lives of its two young heroes. You don't have to be a ballet buff to be moved by Isabela's and Irlan's stories.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What's unique to Beadie Finzi's debut feature is what it reveals about the financial, physical and emotional costs of talent.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>British director Beadie Finzi follows both dancers to international competitions, where the difficult questions raised by their struggles are set aside.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A narrative that tries to juggle thriller elements, tons of pop culture imagery, and way too much philosophical baggage.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ultimately, it seems more bland than bad.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Beach, designed to provoke audiences, stops for too many Hollywood moments to get the job done.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Beach is beautiful, everyone has a lovely tan. But it's nothing to write home about.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All the beauty in the world can't camouflage the movie's gorgeous emptiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's Beach Blanket Bingo revisited, but with a Eurocast and more exotic locations.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A dark, muddled, ambitious but derivative piece.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film does not aspire to sociology. It just wants to tell a story. And that it does well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its narrative waters become rather muddy in the late going, and its currents finally don't run very deep.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Beach wears its self-importance on its sleeve, but never truly earns it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie feels like a mixed-up collection of high points from a book.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Structured for an audience more familiar with MTV's Road Rules than with Joseph Conrad's Heart of Darkness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie that tries to take us from heaven to hell but winds up leaving us in limbo: exasperated and dumfounded.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tedious and unsatisfying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The masterpiece of the Disney Studios' postwar style.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The hero and heroine are sugar sculpture, and the witch looks like a clumsy tracing from a Charles Addams cartoon.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mary Costa's rich and expressive voice for the title character gives substance and strength to it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although this rarely achieves the heights of classics like Snow White and Dumbo, it still has its moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The colors are rich, the sounds are luscious and magic sparkles spurt charmingly from wands.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gibson, of course, snaps and snarls and blows out some brains with a joylessness that is thoroughly enjoyable. It's like he never left.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Scriptwriters William Monahan and Andrew Bovell have sadly sacrificed some of the original's cultural specificity and its slow-burn quality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I liked the pace and the pulse of the film, but it launches no genuine surprise and, despite being irradiated with scenes of sickness and morbid one-liners, has little afterglow.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Edge of Darkness is a meathead revenge picture, but it's very satisfying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Campbell and his cinematographer, Phil Meheux, create a pervasive sense of dread, with danger lurking around every corner of Boston and its environs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Edge of Darkness is reasonably well executed, but its competence reeks of fatigue. Another dead kid. Another angry dad. Another day at the office.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gibson looks every bit his age, but he can still bring the fierce determination as well as anyone in the business.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Edge of Darkness is offered as a political thriller, but with real-world politics removed. What we're left with is a familiar mechanism for delivering a vicarious, violent, wish-fulfilment fantasy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The only edge here is in the title. This is indeed your father's thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A conspiracy that extends to the highest levels of tedium and confusion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plotline... is so convoluted, it goes way past silliness; the big reveals are obvious, and by the time they come to fruition, suspense has long since leaked away.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's nothing especially edgy or dark, or darkly edgy, or even particularly twilit about Edge of Darkness, at least as thrillers go.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Gibson's character here is a man crazed with grief. But it looks as if Gibson is just using that as an excuse to act crazy, period.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is more powerful and haunting thanks to the ample footage incorporated of Hetherington himself, a cheerful soul even when faced with evidence of unimaginable cruelty, such as photographing those blinded during the war in Liberia.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's easy to see how inspiring he could be as an artist, and how tragically addictive the insanity of combat becomes when the engagement and desire to understand run that deep.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is alternately tender, sad and smart. It's also very funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This just kind of fell flat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Enjoyable as it is to see Gervais trying (and often succeeding) to make something of the mediocre dialogue, it's not enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Naturally, Koepp makes it his business to redeem this unpleasant character and recast him as an acceptable stand-in for a romantic lead. But cynics should not despair; it's not a complete makeover.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's enlivened by the performance of Ricky Gervais as Bertram Pincus, a latter-day Scrooge for whom the living are no less annoying than the dead.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The best part of the movie is watching Gervais and Leoni delight in each other in scenes that burst with spontaneity and genuine warmth.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sure, it's a light comedy, but it effectively achieves what it sets out to do: amuse us and tug on our heartstrings. And best of all, it's written, directed and acted with intelligence and wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Through it all there always shone this subtle, gleeful naughty schoolboy charm, not quite a full-on wink at the audience, but a tacit acknowledgement that sometimes even total jerks can exhibit an endearing charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fans of Gervais' awkward, caustic brand of humor should be pleased to see him in a big Hollywood movie that'll make him more of a household name.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ghost Town, a romantic comedy about the living and the dead coming to terms with each other, is both very funny and a bit of a tearjerker, with an on-the-money performance from Ricky Gervais and a nice feeling for New York in fall.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Leoni and Gervais are wonderful together, as much for the ways in which they wobble against each other as for the ways they ultimately mesh.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although ghost hijinks are a very Hollywood way of dealing with the subject, the twists are executed superbly, right up to a climax that fits the David Mamet definition of what makes for a perfect ending: It is both surprising and inevitable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Leave it to the unfailingly brilliant Gervais to breathe new life into an expiring genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The painfully awkward, stubby Gervais as romantic lead is a funny enough concept, but the actor's ongoing banter with Kinnear is engaging, and their styles mesh entertainingly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gervais is a master of the flustered broken thought, and Koepp takes full advantage in scenes that pit Pincus against a distracted doctor (a droll Kristen Wiig) and an imposingly large dog.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The sharp comic timing and the offbeat chemistry of Ricky Gervais, Greg Kinnear and TA (C)a Leoni keep Ghost Town afloat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With lesser talent in front of the camera or a heavier hand behind it, the film might have crashed with a thud.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>On the Waterfront has a script that is a work of love and shows it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Under Elia Kazan's direction, Marlon Brando puts on a spectacular show, giving a fascinating, multi-faceted performance as the uneducated dock walloper and former pug, who is basically a softie with a special affection for his rooftop covey of pigeons.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's hard to deny that Marlon Brando's performance as a dock worker and ex-fighter who finally decides to rat on his gangster brother (Rod Steiger) is pretty terrific.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's pretty electrifying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You miss this, you're buyin' a one-way ticket to Palookaville.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Indisputably one of the great American films, its power undiminished.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>So when does it hit you that you're in the presence of movie greatness?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is thanks to Brando that this posthumous Popular Front classic is a heart-clutcher from beginning to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An uncommonly powerful, exciting and imaginative use of the screen by gifted professionals.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is still possible to feel the power of the film and of Brando and Kazan, who changed American movie acting forever.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are elements that hold up - especially Cruise's blinding charisma. The aerial scenes are still thrilling, and perfectly suited to a giant screen. Everything else? Well, that depends on how nostalgic you're feeling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The aerial sequences in Top Gun are as thrilling -- while remaining coherent -- as any ever put on film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Top Gun is about the training of the Navy's best fighter pilots and their blooding in cold war incidents, and the only thing Director Tony Scott has not brought up to date is the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Every moment is hyped for maximum visual and visceral impact, but Scott doesn't display the slightest bit of interest (or belief) in the actual characters and situations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Set in the world of naval fighter pilots, pic has strong visuals and pretty young people in stylish clothes and a non-stop soundtrack.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story is risible, the direction routine, the underlying ethic highly questionable; but the flying stirs the blood like speed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Once 'Top Gun... gets back to earth, the master of the skies is as clunky as a big land-bound bird.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The dogfights are absolutely the best since Clint Eastwood's electrifying aerial scenes in Firefox. But look out for the scenes where the people talk to one another.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One's opinion of it may depend more on age and parental status than exposure to other rock-concert films. But there's no denying the film delivers on its promise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What this concert film and documentary makes clear is that the real Miley is not just like her predominantly pre-adolescent, female fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Obviously, there's no replicating the real thing. But it's as close as you'll come to achieving the best of both worlds.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For the parents at least, this filmed concert is probably better than actually being there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Some movies are critic-proof -- some for the wrong reasons, some for the right ones. This one falls into the latter camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Seems Disney has discovered yet another way to print money.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Once the movie (and the ringing in your ears) stop, though, it's obvious why Cyrus has become such a phenomenon. She's pretty and stylish but never a mean girl, energetic and popular but not conceited.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Totally slick and vanilla, but you have to like a kid who works this hard.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rock and roll may never die, but you know it's been eaten by the consumer culture when you see Hannah Montana and Miley Cyrus: Best of Both Worlds Concert.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gena Rowlands turns in another virtuoso performance as the troubled actress. Cassavetes' highly personal work will please his coterie of enthusiasts, but for general audiences it will be viewed as shrill, puzzling, depressing and overlong.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>John Cassavetes was unique in his visions and his films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Juggling onstage and offstage action, Cassavetes makes this a fascinating look at some of the internal mechanisms and conflicts that create theatrical fiction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At once a lament to the ravages of age and an examination of those tiny foibles which separate reality from dramatic artifice, it's a baffling and intricate film which, although light on conventional pleasures, still manages to provoke and beguile.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The scenes in which Myrtle consults first one and then another spiritualist are typical of Cassavetes's genius in filming madness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A flawed but highly entertaining B Western blown up to John Ford scale.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The casting of this film may be its greatest asset: Duvall and Costner have the easy familiarity of longtime partners.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Charley's crusty assessment of events -- 'Nothing that's been happening in this town is much of a surprise' -- is all too knowingly accurate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie that seeks no higher calling than to entertain us the way Hollywood used to.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Open Range has too much of what its title portends.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Has a pace as laconic as its director's screen persona.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Open Range is a Western in which the carts pull the horses.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] very special and singular film</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Purty but shallow.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An awesome compendium of cowboy-movie cliches. It borders on parody, and often crosses the border, rustling up a drove of oater aphorisms.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Open Range is too talky, too corny and too long. Yet it gets so much right, from its simple affection for the sight of horses at full gallop to a climactic gunfight that sets a new standard for wit and excitement and right- eous revenge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A juicy, character-driven western with a real plot that spins a hypnotic narrative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A solidly crafted and entertaining old-school western.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a fine little western lurking inside Open Range: Too bad it gets drowned out by director Kevin Costner's pretentiousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A great and beautiful Western in the classic vein.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first two hours of Open Range are a great pleasure, and the final minutes come as a vague indigestion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I have to say that the humour here (some of it Pythonesque) is mostly spot on and, at times, mischievously dark.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's just okay.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Now that we've made one of the best computer-generated talking-animal-on-an-odyssey movies in the brief but busy history of the genre, can we please, please move on?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A little bit like Over the Hedge, and a lot like the upcoming Flushed Away, in which an animated house mouse is forced to fend for himself in the sewers of London, Open Season may sound a bit familiar, but it is never dull.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With animated movies coming out every other week or so, mediocrity is becoming a rule. Open Season loses more points than most films because of its similarities to Over the Hedge, one of the few kids films that did it right this year.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's not deep and not totally original. But Open Season is whiplash quick with the gags and spot-on with the funny voices.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An ugly, painfully derivative and sleep-inducing talking-animals cartoon laced with potty humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A story that balances gentle messages with enough goofy anarchy to please any kid.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Open Season is a rambunctious blast. It's Sony Pictures Animation's first full-length feature film and no effort was spared getting it right.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For an inaugural effort, Open Season ain't bad, but the studio shows far more promise with its gee-whiz visuals than it does in the story department.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is a genial romp and because it relies on the gentlest of scatological comedy, it can be enjoyed by all ages.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film wraps mindless cartoon violence and a few fart jokes around life lessons about friendship and responsibility. Kids should like it; parents won't mind it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the biggest surprises in this first full-length film from Sony Pictures Animation is how funny Ashton Kutcher is as Elliot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This debut offering from Sony Pictures Animation has a giddy energy about it and a gleeful sense of its own weirdness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the filmmakers here have provided us with a passable tale that is mildly humorous, Open Season breaks no new ground, from neither the animation nor the storytelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When your most distinctive element is Ashton Kutcher as a one-antlered mule deer, respect has reason to elude you.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although Open Season isn't the perfect animated movie, it features enough humor and gags to entertain most small kids.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are no Hollywood heroes in these waters, only two regular people ... plus you and me, huddling in the dark.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An unnerving 'What if?' scenario that you won't be able to shake -- from either your dreams or your waking thoughts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sharks are nature's most efficient killing machines. Open Water, which co-stars sharks, is the summer cinema's most efficient scaring machine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Considered in its ham-handed entirety, Open Water feels more of an exercise in cinematic sadism.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Terrifying precisely because it doesn't go in for cheesy shock tactics and special effects.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The unforgiving power of nature are all on display to amazing, and frightening, effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Becomes a slow and steady descent into pure fear.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I'm sorry, but that's entertainment?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>We, the audience, shuffle out of the theater, feeling drained and punished.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As the clock ticks on, the sharks thresh and the dialogue continues to stagnate, you might just catch yourself wickedly thinking: Come on sharks, let's do this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A taut, riveting, uncommonly well-made film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a very pure, basic kind of terror, nail-bitingly fun to watch; made more so by the startling realism of the sharks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The nagging desire to help these people underscores the involvement of the audience in this superbly told story. You can almost taste the saltwater, and the fear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It should make you think hard about assuming only a big, effects-driven adventure can really give you your money's worth.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kentis keeps it simple and direct, and the effect is devastating.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A low-budget indie film whose tension and realism are augmented by unknown actors who fully inhabit their roles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you want to be consumed by special effects, go to any of the many formulaic thrillers in theaters these days. If you want to feel the real chill of fear, go for a swim.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's ridiculously cheap and terrifying at the same time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even if the script (written by the director and Mateo Gil) and direction are patchy, the obsessive theme is gripping.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is so smart, mischievous and stylish, you'll instantly want to see it again.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you're the type who doesn't mind jigsaw puzzles unassembling themselves as you assemble them, if you enjoy enigmas and don't need explanations, the film just might work for you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For adventurous filmgoers, though, this Spanish import offers something off the beaten path and a chance to play the coffee-shop game: Could This Screenplay Be Saved?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Amenabar may drop the ball with a surprise happy ending, but the real shock is that when Cesar finally opens his eyes, you feel he's earned it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While it will not get the kind of wide release necessary to make a big splash in this country, those who see it will not quickly forget the experience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A film with enough intellectual meat on its stylish bones to give more adventurous moviegoers something to chew on afterward.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Blake Edwards directs with his customary wit, breeziness, and acute sense of pacing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Operation Petticoat has no more weight than a sackful of feathers, but it has a lot of laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not unpleasant, but the situations (including the inevitable invasion of women aboard the sub) are horribly familiar, and the dialogue none too inspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Kasdan] and White aim very low here and fail to take advantage of the abundant opportunities for social satire that its upper class and academic settings provide.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The urine-quaffing gags and hearty barfing asides are the lowbrow price extracted for...gestures towards semi-intelligence.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[T]oo many of these gross out scenes...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Strictly a vanity vehicle with a mess of star babies on board.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the smartest idiotic teen comedies you'll ever see.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lessons are learned amid the scatological yucks, profitless cameos (Chevy Chase, Ben Stiller), and Black's graceless mugging.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's derivative and tiresome with little more to offer than one might anticipate from a teen comedy road trip.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This one is geared more toward the volleyball players we see early on, leaping and spiking in the sand.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Full of keenly observed moments of intergenerational embarrassment, as a smarter-than-average teen movie Orange County falls somewhere smack in between Ghost World's depressive cynicism and Teen Movie's gleeful cliche-bashing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This may be the dumbest, sketchiest movie on record about an aspiring writer's coming-of-age.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are laugh-out-loud moments and some well-observed satire, but when the movie tries to get serious, it collapses.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If Orange County has a warmth that takes you aback, don't be surprised. There's something endearingly familial about this movie -- onscreen and off.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's not as gross or stupid as a lot of teen comedies. Just really thick-witted.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A modestly surprising movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pale, stale teen comedy with a (lame) message.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The essential problem in Orange County is that, having created an unusually vivid set of characters worthy of its strong cast, the film flounders when it comes to giving them something to do.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Just when it seemed there was no other possible way to copy a cat, they prove you wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Young Hanks and Fisk, who vaguely resemble their celebrity parents, bring fresh good looks and an ease in front of the camera to the work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fellini's films often seem lazy, but this one looks plain tired.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Both emotionally and intellectually the picture is hypnotic, and some portions will nail the spectator to his seat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A strange, wondrous and shocking work. Once seen, it's unlikely to leave you.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What Redford accomplishes is to provide an excellent portrait of how well families can hide their inner turmoil from the prying eyes of outsiders.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An austere and delicate examination of the ways in which a likable family falters under pressure and struggles, with ambiguous results, to renew itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A powerfully intimate domestic drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film looks austere and serious, rather as if it had been shot inside a Frigidaire, and the oppressiveness of the images tends to strangle laughter, even at the most absurd excesses of Alvin Sargent's script.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An actors' movie and an advert for therapy, extremely bitter, but handsomely directed in its elegant pretentiousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An intelligent, perceptive, and deeply moving film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A moving, intelligent and funny film about disasters that are commonplace to everyone except the people who experience them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A strenuous effort to be an inventive comedy with perversely wicked humor, this midnight movie (premiering at Toronto Fest) showcases the talents of Trey Parker as writer-director-star; hopefully, his next film will be more successful</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Original Gangstas leaves you feeling that more could have been made of this 'blaxploitation' reunion, but it's not bad -- and no more and no less substantial than the films of the original cycle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Think Boyz N the Hood meets The Mod Squad.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The purpose is to entertain, and on that score the film delivers impressively.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>High on lust and low on logic, the preposterous Original Sin is an erotic thriller that evokes more laughs than sweat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is all posture, cliche, and editing-room Spackle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A textbook case of a movie that would have been better had it been worse.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Cable fare masquerading as a theatrical feature because of its high-profile cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Suggests unintentional self-parody from the get-go.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aficionados of movies in the so-bad-they're-good category might just revel in this overheated costume melodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Original Sin is really about murky storytelling, bad dialogue and arty close-ups of Jolie's formidable lips.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Neither epochal nor epic in its ludicrousness. It's just run-of-the-mill trash.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Makes for an extremely well-acted movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The kind of movie that keeps you on your toes waiting for the next deadly serious absurdity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Cristofer's approach is relentlessly serious and dead-on, devoid of humor, wit or personality.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is never moving or shocking. It needs to be both.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's your basic, steamy black widow tale with one of the most implausible set-ups in memory.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A plateful of steamed corn.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Loses its nerve and instead of maintaining its theme of obsession, it starts piling up absurd complications.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Original Sin, despite the heavy-handedness, isn't awful enough to be a hilarious howler. But neither is it good enough to become the tropical noir it could have been.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Cristofer sabotages his movie by killing most of the suspense and robbing it of logic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Swinton's androgynous affect has rarely been better exploited: It's a kick to see her transition among Orlando's numerous identities, whether wooing a Russian princess or submitting to the charms of the horseback-riding Shelmerdine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the kind of movie you want to talk about afterward.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Decidedly amoral.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This wickedly entertaining, if slightly over-stretched, variation on the familiar 'evil child' scenario displays an unusually complex grasp of twisted psychology.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It would be harder to find a more dark and joyless thriller on the market than this one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's bloody, you should be warned, but in the end it is worth it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Painfully predictable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a surprise ending, followed by several bonus endings, and we're not giving anything away in noting that the film's titular adoptee has more lives than Chucky.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Clocking in at more than two hours, the movie teeters between psychological horror and violent blood-letting and, as such, probably won't completely satisfy fans in either camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the third-act surprise twist of Orphan must have looked wicked-good on paper, on screen ... not so much.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The scares are often the generic, push-off-the-slide variety and Orphan doesn't add much to the genre except, disturbingly, a fetishistic bent that's creepy in the wrong way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Although reasonably, cheesily suspenseful, the movie takes a long time to get going. Its tagline, 'There's something wrong with Esther,' turns out to be a masterpiece of understatement.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film rests on Furhman's shoulders, and she's up to the task.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The best thing about Orphan, is the way it plays with the genre's overused staples and its sophisticated audience's expectations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a cut above most spooky-kid movies, with a twist that sets it apart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>So sloppy, so lowdown, so shameless and so entertaining, Orphan provides everything you might expect in a psycho-child thriller, but with such excess and exuberance that it still has the power to surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Orphan] never exploits the dramatic possibilities, despite the efforts of its excellent cast and gorgeous production values.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Actors have to eat like the rest of us, but you still have to wonder how Vera Farmiga and Peter Sarsgaard ended up wading through Orphan and not laughing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To really get under your skin, a bad-seed horror movie needs a demon child whose dastardliness sneaks up on you. There's nothing too subtle, however, about Esther.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jean Cocteau's scripting and directing give the film its proper key of unworldliness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Somnambulistic symbolism may be art for art's sake. Maybe not. This writer finds it slightly tiresome.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its tight cross-lacing of paranoid dreaming and poetic realism grips like a bondage corset.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cocteau's film technique is as eccentrically sui generis as ever -- his apparent mistakes are often among his most expressive moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Seeing Orpheus today is like glimpsing a cinematic realm that has passed completely from the scene.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film prefigures Mizoguchi's later work in its angry emphasis on double standards, its visual precision and its engaged but never preachy tone.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of Kenji Mizoguchi's finest efforts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is after all a Gillian Anderson picture, which means the film's physical production is just as impressive as its spiritual apsiration; Cate Blanchett, in a role originally intended for Judy Davis, is bound to become a major star</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a lack of dramatic focus, and the leads fail to evince any particular chemistry.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie transpires mostly in quiet, engrossing dialogue scenes, and its austere style shares a good deal in common with the protagonist, who seems both opaque and completely exposed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Displays] an invigoratingly acute understanding of the psychology of insecurity, longing, defensiveness and inward-turning rage.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Trier proves that he's no one-hit wonder.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The result is a superb exploration of loss, guilt and regret in Norwegian director Joachim Trier's often-unpredictable second film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It has absolute clarity about a character who isn't at all sure about what he wants - or whether he wants to keep going at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Screenwriters] Trier and Vogt are neat and cunning.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pared down and sparse, almost Bressonian in its formal rigor...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A study of a man who pulled away from the edge of the abyss at the nick of time, only to realize he may not be able to forgive himself for the things he's done.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Te movie seems more like a searing portrait of self-discovery and realization, with the understanding that not everything you learn about yourself will be pleasant.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Trier ... keeps us aware of the emotions and perceptions of all the characters, even at those times when their perceptions are limited and differ from objective reality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With his angular features and intense gaze, Lie is utterly convincing as an intellectual in the process of repairing his damaged life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Oslo\" is an example of strong, confident filmmaking in which nothing is miscalculated or out of place.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a marvelously constructed personal journey, both wrenching and bittersweet, whose emotional ripple effects stay with you for days and weeks afterward.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In its depiction of a man who's considering death, the film is never less than fully alive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With only two films, Danish director Joachim Trier has soundly established himself as a singular talent.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Trier's compassion for what it takes to survive, mixed with the love he bestows on Oslo, is rewardingly profound.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The plot's so much old rote, and the characters have all the personality of protoplasm; but the anthropomorphising of this microcosmic metropolis is wonderfully imaginative, and the dialogue decidedly spiffy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Remains stubbornly one-dimensional.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It should have been placed in a hazardous waste container, encased in concrete and dumped into the Farrelly brothers' septic tank.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A very clever, very gross, very funny spoof of the cliched cop genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Isn't a movie so much as a health-class nutrition lecture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watch what you buy at the concession stand.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A hilarious, hellzapoppin' hybrid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's no funnier than your average grade-school biology lesson and less pedagogically useful than your typical Farrelly brothers comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In more parts than not, Osmosis Jones is funny as it is fearless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I really enjoyed Kroon and Sito's movie, but disliked the Farrellys. It's time they try harder - their style has grown sickening. And it's time Kroon and Sito make both halves of a film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's lively enough and passably entertaining, even if you may need a barf bag to get through it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As long as Osmosis Jones sticks to the action-flick innards -- from the gangster dens of the armpits to the deportee docks of the bladder -- it's an inventive series of gags (in both senses).</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Likely to entertain kids, who seem to like jokes about anatomical plumbing. For adults, there is the exuberance of the animation and the energy of the whole movie, which is just plain clever.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Osmosis Jones, with its effluvia-festival brand of humor, is often fun, and the rounded, blobby rendering of the characters is likable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Movies are easier to enjoy when you aren't always covering your eyes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though juvenile tastelessness continues to run rampant, Osmosis Jones can at least be safely enjoyed by most juveniles, who will also get a valuable lesson in what a lifetime of junk-food abuse can do.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Adults might remain immune to the process of Osmosis, but younger viewers probably will be receptive to its nervy fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>All this is mighty silly, but there's something to be said for watching a French movie that, for a change, isn't about l'amour, existential angst, or madness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The tenor, tone and immaculately lampooned art direction often make up for shtick that gradually grows thin in the belly-laugh department.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's generally friendly and enjoyable, but it sags a bit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A reasonably pleasant surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's larky, snarky fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The part is tricky, but Jean Dujardin does it well, greeting every woman with a cocky Jean-Paul Belmondo smile, and every foreign disaster with calm. Thank heavens France is here to help!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mr. Dujardin, a skilled comedian, deftly embodies the spy's combination of cluelessness and condescension, but it's an act that eventually wears thin.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I don't know about you, but I look to French films for stylish love stories and potent social dramas. I definitely don't look to Gallic movies for slapstick comedy, a genre at which the French are especially bad.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A very funny French comedy of a variety that usually doesn't make its way here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is like a subpar Naked Gun feature cooked up by Eisenstein and Godard during a drug-addled lost weekend. Where's Leslie Nielsen when you need him?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's the grooving to composer Ludovic Bource's fab xylophone beats and Dujardin's hyena laugh and heroic self-regard you'll remember.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ossessione, which also began the late Mr. Visconti's remarkable film career, may be slow-going to the uninitiated, but its historical importance is not to be denied.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Luchino Visconti's first solo effort and the first great Italian neorealist film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Low-budget but visually stunning.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The visual rhetoric is synchronised with the verbal imagery: they hit sensory overload together.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Film is an impressive rendering of the Shakespearean tragedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Individual scenes are in an unrestrainedly operatic bravura style, and while the film succeeds visually, it ultimately fails as drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A folly perhaps, but a grand one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the filmmaker's great masterpieces.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Othello has been filmed numerous times, but never with such extraordinary visual grace and power.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are flashes of brilliant suggestion in this tumbled, slurred, and helter-skelter film. But they add up to nothing substantial -- just a little Shakespeare and a lot of Welles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>From its opening shots, where the camera looks down on a solemn funeral procession, Othello exhibits Welles' flair for dramatic compositions.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Compelling, distressing documentary about the weirdly mechanized world of industrial farms, slaughterhouses and other sources of mass-produced food has a surrealist edge that gives the film a dreamlike ambience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Essentially, it's a Koyanisquaasti for metal and meat fetishists, and that's no bad thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The camera simply looks, with unflinching interest, as plants and animals are processed (in European industrial settings) into the food we eat. It's up to the viewer to distinguish tastes of horror, compassion, and awe at the efficiency involved.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An alarming vision of the antiseptic order we have created around the business of stocking our fridge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thought-provoking documentary that would go well on a double bill with Richard Linklater's fictional Fast Food Nation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This documentary is an unblinking, often disturbing look at industrial food production from field to factory.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pic offers a tabula rasa in which some auds will see a horrifying indictment of the industry's cruelties, others a realistic depiction of mechanized farming, and some a soft-spoken tribute to manual labor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Our Daily Bread is quietly radical in showing creatures whose existence is solely and inexorably a preparation for death.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nikolaus Geyrhalter's beautifully shot and elegantly edited documentary belies the frequent ugliness of its subject matter.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I didn't buy a word of this thing and I didn't laugh enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Alternately flat and overwrought.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To anyone who has ever sparked up a TV set, let alone entered a movie theatre, all this is perfectly evident in the first five minutes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Alternately rancid and ridiculous, strident and sickly sweet, Our Family Wedding offers plenty that's old, borrowed and blue; it's the something new that's missing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] slick, slapsticky, forgettable comedy, a cool-jazz riff on upper-middle-class American families sorting through misconceptions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Our Family Wedding plays out like an elongated Disney TV episode, going precisely where you expect every inch of the way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The only bouquet anyone's going to catch from this contrivance has the aroma of stale comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A cringeworthy, unfunny example of a culture-clash romantic comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rick Famuyiwa's movie repeatedly trips and falls on its way up the aisle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ferrera and Gross are the most appealing pair I've seen in awhile; their calm confidence is a welcome antidote to the unrealistic couples who've been cluttering our screens way too long.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Instead of invitations, they should be sending out apologies for Our Family Wedding, a cake-and-kisses comedy that has disaster written all over it and not for the right reasons.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The likable cast keep things watchable, particularly handsome Gross, who is surely destined for bigger things, and Ferrera, who's still as sweetly unaffected on-screen as she was back in Real Women Have Curves.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This mixed-race page from the Meet the Parents book is a tasteless exercise in familiarity and contempt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Wait till the DVD release.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Our Family Wedding is another Hollywood fast-food sandwich. But instead of two squirts of ketchup someone actually took the time to lay some fresh tomato on that greasy bun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Vacuous and contrived.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You almost miss the laugh track. Difficult problems are sidestepped, arguments are overacted, and there are three food fights involving wedding cakes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Be prepared to swallow a lot of empty-calorie jokes in which blacks and Latinos insult and misunderstand one another in a spirit of vigorous buffoonery before dancing together in maniacal harmony during the never-in-doubt wedding-scene finale.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A broad and formulaic culture-clash comedy built on fill-in-the-blank wedding comedy cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rudd brings color and dimension to a borderline-simpleton schlub who could have easily become a one-note cliche.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Strange, then, how Our Idiot Brother wastes its lone asset -- there's not enough idiot, and far too many boring savants.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's rare that summer ends on as sweet a note as Our Idiot Brother.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The cast members, beginning with Rudd, have an improvisatory ease, and the director, Jesse Peretz, working from a script by Evgenia Peretz and David Schisgall, doesn't indulge in the sort of nail-on-the-head comedy that currently reigns.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even the usually likable Rudd can't do much with the enigmatic Ned, who often behaves exactly in the idiotic manner he's accused of.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dude, where's the movie?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film goes far on its good nature, though it is never more than gently funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A film that offers dumb fun, but in reality may be crazy like a fox.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rudd has created a genuinely engaging character in the Candide-like Ned, but \"Our Idiot Brother\" gives him very little garden to cultivate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite a pleasantly laid-back demeanor, you wish it would just get focused.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a warm, intelligent and highly contemporary comedy with just the right amount of edge, a terrific ensemble cast and a big, fuzzy golden retriever ready to knock you down and lick you like a giant lollipop.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ned turns out to be a strangely moving figure, a comic foil worthy of affection, perhaps even respect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The laughs are consistent and occasionally outlandish, but more often, they arise out of recognizable family situations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thin, unconvincing movie made likable by the charm and skill of its cast and by a script peppered with wit and insight.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Easily could have been mildly funny and phony but instead is really funny and true to life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Welcome to the world of Ned, an eternally sunny realm where everyone is greeted as an old friend and everything will always work out fine, even when it doesn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Our Idiot Brother comes off as a blueprint for a smart script no one really made.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's mediocre in a passive, energy-sapping way midway between humdrum and ho-hum.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The comedy isn't always as crisp as it should be, but Peretz has the perfect partner in crime in Rudd.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The rhythms are gentle, the smiles plentiful, the chuckles frequent, with the overall effect about as pleasantly innocuous as the film's hero.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The gimmickry congeals.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] dazzling, action-jammed swashbuckling spoof.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It becomes a parade of nonsense, a steal on the comic strips.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jaunty.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The mixture of mayhem and heehaw is particularly tricky to handle, and not even the sure hand of Director Reed has always achieved a smooth blend.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Polished, diverting entertainment, brilliant in its comedy but falling apart towards the end when undertones of drama, tragedy and message crop up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A real 'winds of change' film, with traditional values crumbling in the heat of pre-revolutionary Cuba. Guinness is wonderful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For those who regard Alec Guinness as the niftiest little con man on the screen, we will guarantee Our Man in Havana to be a source of immeasurable fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Guinness is in above-average form, and Ernie Kovacs is wonderful as the callous but charming government official with a soft spot for Guinness's daughter.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While the actors are responsible for much of the creativity, these are the director's most obsessive works: every shot and scene is set up more as a question than an answer, hinging on the adventure and mystery of not knowing what will happen next.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A monumental if cheeky culmination of the French New Wave.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hoffman doesn't get the chance, or need, to act: he just does things, like Ford.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An absolute hoot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a picture good enough to make you want to go to the movies and frightening enough to make you wonder if you should avoid the crowds.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Displays all the initial symptoms of a promising thriller, it soon degenerates into a low-fever whodunit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the great scare stories of our time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Comes off as a shrill, self-important bore.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No one likes to be teased, but that's exactly what this movie does to us, with predictably frustrating results.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A big, bustling, intermittently dippy melodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A clunky thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As if to justify a serious discussion of this comedy before dissing it, some reviewers have pointed out that it evokes Casablanca.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its only redeeming value is the killer snowboarding scenes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Funnier than Woody Allen's last four movies, more exciting than Tarkovski's The Sacrifice, Out Cold will play best if your first legal beer is still far enough into the future to seem a vision of the promised land.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The result is so derivative, they should've called it Eskimo Pie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even though no one in the film breaks a leg, Out Cold is as lame as it gets.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When Lee Majors can steal every scene he's in, your movie's in trouble.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I can't imagine why anyone would pay money to see this sorry excuse for a film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No brains, no headache.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the presence of pro boarders doing their thing might be a selling point for enthusiasts, the predominantly lame goings-on will leave others snow-bored.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As in the old beach movies, a great deal of screen time is devoted to the astounding exploits of stunt doubles, who here are riding powdered snow rather than waves.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More Caddyshack than Casablanca.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Out Cold isn't the worst movie ever made. It is, however, one of the most pointless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out for Justice harbors an incredibly simple vengeance plot loaded with enough macho sadism to satiate the action genre's bloodthirsty fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you cut the beatings, you wouldn't be left with much.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As a courtesy to his many fans, the ponytailed action hero Steven Seagal not only attacks sleaze but also goes out of his way to examine it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is Old Jack City, a place where better actors and directors have taken us frequently in the last year. This particular trip seems unnecessary.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Daft, obvious but hugely enjoyable, 'Outlander' is superior trash.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An unexpectedly enjoyable science-fiction adventure that should be generating louder fanboy buzz than it has so far.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Outlander is a cheesy, low-budget, space alien Viking monster movie. And seemingly proud of it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In its second half, Outlander falls apart completely, becoming nothing but a violent, mindless monster movie along the lines of Alien vs. Predator.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In Outlander, the nuttiest hunk of junk in many months, Viking warriors and a stoic intergalactic traveler join forces to combat an enormous beetle with whiplash stingers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There isn't a single scene in this story about a traveler from another planet who crash-lands on Earth during the Iron Age that doesn't remind you of another, better movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By taking nonsense seriously Outlander never achieves camp. It's a comic book that's mistaken itself for scripture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An enjoyably goofy hybrid of extraterrestrial sci-fi and Iron Age action.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I am tempted to describe the plot of Outlander as preposterous, but a movie about an alien spaceship crashing into a Viking fjord during the Iron Age is likely to be preposterous.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of the more outlandish B-pictures to come out of the Great Movie Mash-up Machine known as The Weinstein Co.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Daft, obvious but hugely enjoyable, 'Outlander' is superior trash.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An unexpectedly enjoyable science-fiction adventure that should be generating louder fanboy buzz than it has so far.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Outlander is a cheesy, low-budget, space alien Viking monster movie. And seemingly proud of it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In its second half, Outlander falls apart completely, becoming nothing but a violent, mindless monster movie along the lines of Alien vs. Predator.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In Outlander, the nuttiest hunk of junk in many months, Viking warriors and a stoic intergalactic traveler join forces to combat an enormous beetle with whiplash stingers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There isn't a single scene in this story about a traveler from another planet who crash-lands on Earth during the Iron Age that doesn't remind you of another, better movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By taking nonsense seriously Outlander never achieves camp. It's a comic book that's mistaken itself for scripture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An enjoyably goofy hybrid of extraterrestrial sci-fi and Iron Age action.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I am tempted to describe the plot of Outlander as preposterous, but a movie about an alien spaceship crashing into a Viking fjord during the Iron Age is likely to be preposterous.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of the more outlandish B-pictures to come out of the Great Movie Mash-up Machine known as The Weinstein Co.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Africa is, at last, the free-spirited, fullhearted gesture that everyone has been waiting for the movies to make all decade long. It reclaims the emotional territory that is rightfully theirs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Maybe the problem of the pacing is simply the nature of the beast these days with expensive period pieces. Once the difficult details are all in place, it may be too much to expect a director to resist milking every scene for more than it's worth.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sydney Pollack applies craftsmanship and restraint to a classic plot curve of longing, fulfillment, and loss, and although the denouement is a bit overextended, he never yields to facile, insistent sentimentality -- his effects are honestly won.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all that it may come out of Africa, the film's final destination is not many miles from Disneyland.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With the exception of Miss Streep's performance, the pleasures of Out of Africa are all peripheral -- David Watkin's photography, the landscapes, the shots of animal life -all of which would fit neatly into a National Geographic layout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Africa is a great movie to look at, breathtakingly filmed on location. It is a movie with the courage to be about complex, sweeping emotions, and to use the star power of its actors without apology.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It tells a grand love story in less-than-grand fashion but is nevertheless worth seeing because of all the other things it does right.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Africa is, at last, the free-spirited, fullhearted gesture that everyone has been waiting for the movies to make all decade long. It reclaims the emotional territory that is rightfully theirs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Maybe the problem of the pacing is simply the nature of the beast these days with expensive period pieces. Once the difficult details are all in place, it may be too much to expect a director to resist milking every scene for more than it's worth.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sydney Pollack applies craftsmanship and restraint to a classic plot curve of longing, fulfillment, and loss, and although the denouement is a bit overextended, he never yields to facile, insistent sentimentality -- his effects are honestly won.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all that it may come out of Africa, the film's final destination is not many miles from Disneyland.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With the exception of Miss Streep's performance, the pleasures of Out of Africa are all peripheral -- David Watkin's photography, the landscapes, the shots of animal life -all of which would fit neatly into a National Geographic layout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Africa is a great movie to look at, breathtakingly filmed on location. It is a movie with the courage to be about complex, sweeping emotions, and to use the star power of its actors without apology.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It tells a grand love story in less-than-grand fashion but is nevertheless worth seeing because of all the other things it does right.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Steven Soderbergh's most ambitious and most accomplished work to date.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>From the first shot to the last, Mr. Clooney is in complete command of the screen in the assured manner of the biggest stars in the past, and he doesn't need a ton of special effects and digital enhancement to generate excitement.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A splendid reminder of just how assured, intelligent and involving Soderbergh's movies can be.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Sight may go down in the annals of film as the movie in which George Clooney learned to keep his head still -- and became a leading man.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Sight isn't just a rousing piece of entertainment, it's also a cinematic salvage operation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As always with the best of Leonard, it's the journey, not the destination, that counts, and director Soderbergh has let it unfold with dry wit and great skill.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Steven Soderbergh's best film since Sex, Lies and Videotape a decade ago.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's refreshing to find a picture like Out of Sight, which is not only smart, but a great deal of fun, as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soderbergh takes real delight in giving his stars the star treatment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Some reviewers have applauded Out of Sight for its nuances of character, but I and others don't see any characters at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like Get Shorty, Out of Sight has been adapted with deftness and fidelity by Scott Frank, who knows exactly how to translate Leonard's narrative voice to the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The usual dramatic affectations applied to such true-life material are largely absent; instead, Sarkies focuses on various quotidian elements that take on weight as the inevitable draws closer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sarkies avoids the genre's conventional trappings and prefers instead to concentrate on the ways in which the people of Aramoana deal with the unfolding event.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Robert Sarkies' dramatization of that event is as sensitive to its subject as it is stark in its rendering.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Without such thematic resonance, it plays like a more elaborate version of one of the dramatic re-creations seen on any number of true-crime television programs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like Steven Spielberg's historical epics, the film shows the nastiest incidents from a great distance, or cuts away before a bullet's impact to show an onlooker's shocked reaction. The director confronts horror without wallowing in it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's some nifty soft-focus cinematography and fine performances, but otherwise, not much to resonate on this side of the pond.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An effectively harrowing and non-exploitative recap of real-life events.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Direction by Jacques Tourneur pays close attention to mood development, achieving realistic flavor that is further emphasized by real life settings and topnotch lensing by Nicholas Musuraca.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most delicate and nuanced of film noirs, graced with a reflective lyricism that almost lifts it out of the genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the greatest of all film noirs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's very snappy and quite intriguingly played by a cast that has been well and smartly directed by Jacques Tourneur.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cinematic perfection, a Hollywood classic that's as great and as enjoyable as its reputation has promised.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a great ride.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I just wish they would have tried a little harder with the script.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A consistent pleasure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Out of Time seems out of another time and place.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Franklin is known for being good with actors, but Out Of Time also reveals his flair with machines, which too often dominate the plots of latter-day noirs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A well-performed, perfectly watchable thriller that's nonetheless as generic as its title.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A shrewd thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Washington has never been more of a movie star than he is here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a kick to watch Denzel Washington do a movie just for the hot, sexy fun of it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most purely entertaining thriller since No Way Out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's great to see Franklin back in top form.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Time is probably Hollywood's most seamless suspense trap since The Fugitive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Incredible but fun noir.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A solid thriller full of surprises.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Out of Time isn't entirely memorable, and it contains enough plot holes to drive a train through, but the movie is almost all pleasure, stand-up Hollywood entertainment without a trace of pretense, served straight up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite its exciting moments the film is marred by contrivance and implausibilities.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You gotta figure something's wrong when the best part of a Denzel Washington movie is John Billingsley.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soggy at the beginning, silly at the end, but often riveting in between, Out of Time is another Denzel Washington movie that's nowhere near as good as Denzel Washington.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>How can anyone can get excited over something so grim and redundant?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a gangster story, told well, with no punches pulled.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kitano is clearly enjoying his powers as a master of the form, and the movie invites the viewer to share in his enjoyment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's like a version of \"Cinema Paradiso\" where all the murders were saved up by a censor and strung together for a bloodbath.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's retaliation without foundation, all fun and games until everyone gets hurt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Kitano leaves it up to us to connect the dots. Unfortunately, he seems to get bored before he's done, and so do we.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The longer Outrage goes on, the more distance it gets from its core themes about the moral chaos of gangsterism. It becomes a film about cool killings, which may satisfy the bloodlust of some Kitano fans but hardly amounts to a return to form.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately the film itself feels a little punch drunk, particularly as the feuds escalate. Who's trying to knock off whom? It's hard to keep track...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The editing (by Kitano) and lensing are stylish and guaranteed to keep viewers hooked through the final rubout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>So low-key and offhanded in its mastery that it becomes something like a pulp sleight-of-hand trick.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Kitano's immaculate compositions and eccentric flourishes are part of the film's sustained, muted pleasures and are often in service to some underlying meaning.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Kitano] directs with such wicked confidence and so many gleefully extreme flourishes...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Takeshi's] sense of style is very much in evidence here, and so is his sense of humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not even Michael Mann merges hot tempers and cool formalism this well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like one of its yakuza bigs, Outrage commands respect but no affection.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The results are so visually stunning, why quibble?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As violent, amoral and misanthropic as a Jacobean play, Outrage is Takeshi Kitano's first yakuza flick since Brother, and arguably his best film in a decade.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Midler and Long are never less than fun to watch.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As a vehicle for their considerable comic talents, the enterprise is wheelclamped by typecasting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Every bit as rude and wonderful as Ruthless People...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's more regressive coyness in this buddy adventure-comedy than anyone should have to sit through in a lifetime...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Such rarefied screen writing calls for the peerless talents of Arthur Hiller, a director with the comic timing of a tax auditor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, the movie is so busy cross-polinating its genres that it never pauses for the kind of thought that might have made it really special, instead of just fitfully funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Because it falls in with the undulating rhythm of the life of its heroes, for whom a fatal fight and a quiet night have almost equal importance, the picture never manages to reach the peaks of satisfying Hollywood melodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Well acted and crafted but highly conventional.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is unremitting in its morbid sentimentality, running its teenage characters through a masochistic gamut of beatings, killings, burnings, and suicides.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lightly likeable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Coppola's] revisions to the film, which include a new, improved soundtrack, invest it with grandeur worthy of both its characters and his own ambitions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's not much life in this movie, or spontaneity. It's a stylistic exercise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sporadically engaging.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the prospect of watching Miss Hawn play a rude, nasty socialite is appealing, and even the transformation to homebody is a funny idea, Overboard winds up taking things too far.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A warm and funny movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If there's an amnesia movie worse than Overboard, it slips my mind.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[An] offense of a ghost comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You may remember Noel Coward's Blithe Spirit. This is Bleh Spirit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The kindest context in which to put Over Her Dead Body, which was written and directed by Jeff Lowell, is that of a training film, a public display of people trying to master their craft. The best way to see it is not at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The tale [falls] short on imagination.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Writer/director Jeff Lowell settles for a story that takes a little too long to tell, concocted situations a little too implausible to buy and repartee that occasionally hits the dartboard but never gets close to the bull's-eye.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The worst night at the movies in this young year.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You can't even feel sorry for Henry, because anyone blind enough to want to marry Kate is clearly delusional and deserving of any misery that comes his way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately wit-deprived.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For what is essentially a screwball comedy, Over Her Dead Body is surprisingly uninspired, a frothy concept that offers little satisfaction in the way of execution.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The grating presence of Longoria Parker will be enough to ruin the movie for many, but she's just one of many shortcomings in this romantic comedy, which seriously lacks both romance and comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An unsurprising entry in that hoary micro-genre of romantic comedies to feature a fresh-from-the-corpse disembodied spirit who just can't seem to get a move-on.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A wan, sad-eyed romantic comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a film that's completely happy being its silly little self. And if it produces some giggles along the way -- and it does -- it has done its job.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Over Her Dead Body itself is a movie haunted by the annoying, humorless performance of Eva Longoria Parker.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Over Her Dead Body, billed as a romantic com edy fantasy, is in reality a mystery: The Case of the Missing Jokes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Over Her Dead Body is to romantic comedy what Spam is to meat. But at least with Spam, you get cool packaging.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Consider for a moment how this movie might play if it took itself seriously. Would it be better than as a comedy? I suspect so.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Overlord feels like a small but vivid tragedy inside an epic container.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's still a feat of period filmmaking. More than that, Overlord's revivification of a wasteland Europe offers up a powerful whip lesson for the postwar complacent.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A majestic, somber work about war.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cooper gives it the right understated, unheroic feel.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's an extremely clever weave of components, combining, almost flawlessly, the dramatized and the archival, the result being a hybrid of forms.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Combines its newsreel and fictional footage so effectively that it has a greater impact than all fiction, or all documentary, could have achieved.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story has a loony, slapstick verve, and the star-studded voice work is uniformly entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Over the Hedge aims solely to entertain, it does so in a way that's mildly amusing but mostly hackneyed. If it aims to instruct, it weakens its own argument with the plethora of product tie-ins.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The final showdown, in which the critters tangle with security-rigged lawn flamingos and garden gnomes, would have made Rube Goldberg proud.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It misses the mark a couple of times but in the main, it's good clean fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An endearingly cheerful animated feature from DreamWorks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Over The Hedge is cute without being cutesy, satirical without being too cynical, and just a whole lot of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is competent work and frequently amusing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A charming, clever and crisply paced little confection about small, junk-food-addled mammals that's sure to delight large mammals of any age.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Inspired casting of voice actors is one of several pleasures in this fun film for children, which has enough social satire to satisfy adults as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Over the Hedge isn't by any stretch bad. It's just banal.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Over the Hedge may be 'just' a cartoon. But it's also a biting and funny jab at SUV-MSG Nation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The writing doesn't measure up to the casting, and the picture is miles from original.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If they were still making Looney Tunes, they'd look a lot like Over the Hedge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The computer-animation is terrific, most of the slapstick gags are fun, and Wanda Sykes' voice performance as feisty Stella the Skunk is one that will be remembered -- and not because it stinks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Spends none of the time that Michael Fry and T. Lewis' daily comic strip does staring at the stars or asking questions of the Tree That Knows Stuff, but the movie does offer an amusing animals'-eye-view on the absurdity of suburbia.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its own animal, a spirited and intrepid critter that mooches our affection along with the garbage.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There may be only so many ways you can spin a computer-generated animated feature about a gang of animals and their grand project against an evil adversary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ultimately Hedge is deja vu all over again, a computer-generated work of wonder that could have come out last year, last month or two months from now, a film so reminiscent of other films it almost immediately dims in the memory.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An imaginative mix of live-action and CGI that pays homage to the iconic images and timeless sense of wonder in the classic The Wizard of Oz without being too deferential.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful is entirely serviceable family entertainment. Problem is, serviceable doesn't quite cut it when you're talking about the magical land of Oz.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aside from a trio of witches that can hold its own with Eastwick's in the dishiness department, Oz the Great and Powerful is a peculiarly joyless occasion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Let us take a moment to praise two great and surprisingly powerful characters: a winged monkey and a wee girl made out of china. Because so much human wonder resides in these two creations of make-up, puppetry, digital effects and lovely performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful somehow manages to be both slavish to its hallowed template (when convenient) and completely tone-deaf to the magic that made it a one-of-a-kind cultural milestone.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Raimi's film is supposed to be about magic, but magic is in scant supply.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Oz the Great and Powerful\" will likely dazzle family audiences while satisfying movie purists. Somewhere over the rainbow there may be a more magical movie, but this will certainly do.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A Blunder-full Blizzard of Blahs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a journey of self-discovery, rife with movie cliches about believing in yourself, believing in your dreams, yada-yada.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Where's the gentle sentiment? The quiet moral lessons? The warm comforting message of family, and home, and realizing that the thing you needed most was really inside you, all the time?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful aims for nostalgia in older viewers who grew up on The Wizard of Oz and still hold the classic dear while simultaneously enchanting a newer, younger audience. It never really accomplishes either successfully.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A visually over-crammed, emotionally empty mega-spectacle on the model of Tim Burton's Alice in Wonderland.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A partially effective jumble whose elements clash rather than cohere, this solid but not spectacular effort stubbornly refuses to catch fire until it's almost too late.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The more you like the Judy Garland film, the more you might appreciate \"Oz the Great and Powerful.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Oz] qualifies as a cautionary tale, not about the perils of ambition and selfishness, but about the movie industry's misguided belief that it can distract the audience from a film's narrative weaknesses with little more than flash and spectacle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful tells the story of how the Wizard came to Oz, answering a question I suspect no one was asking, but with considerable digital wizardry.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Relax, my pretties. \"Oz the Great and Powerful\" is a lollapalooza of funhouse thrills and visually sumptuous filmmaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>... as limitless technology teaches the wizard about his own human limitations, Franco hits grace notes that let us see glimmers of how great and powerful this uneven Oz might have been.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What does it say about \"Oz the Great and Powerful\" that China Doll, a creature born of digital code, is the movie's most affecting character?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An imaginative mix of live-action and CGI that pays homage to the iconic images and timeless sense of wonder in the classic The Wizard of Oz without being too deferential.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful is entirely serviceable family entertainment. Problem is, serviceable doesn't quite cut it when you're talking about the magical land of Oz.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aside from a trio of witches that can hold its own with Eastwick's in the dishiness department, Oz the Great and Powerful is a peculiarly joyless occasion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Let us take a moment to praise two great and surprisingly powerful characters: a winged monkey and a wee girl made out of china. Because so much human wonder resides in these two creations of make-up, puppetry, digital effects and lovely performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful somehow manages to be both slavish to its hallowed template (when convenient) and completely tone-deaf to the magic that made it a one-of-a-kind cultural milestone.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Raimi's film is supposed to be about magic, but magic is in scant supply.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Oz the Great and Powerful\" will likely dazzle family audiences while satisfying movie purists. Somewhere over the rainbow there may be a more magical movie, but this will certainly do.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A Blunder-full Blizzard of Blahs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a journey of self-discovery, rife with movie cliches about believing in yourself, believing in your dreams, yada-yada.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Where's the gentle sentiment? The quiet moral lessons? The warm comforting message of family, and home, and realizing that the thing you needed most was really inside you, all the time?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful aims for nostalgia in older viewers who grew up on The Wizard of Oz and still hold the classic dear while simultaneously enchanting a newer, younger audience. It never really accomplishes either successfully.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A visually over-crammed, emotionally empty mega-spectacle on the model of Tim Burton's Alice in Wonderland.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A partially effective jumble whose elements clash rather than cohere, this solid but not spectacular effort stubbornly refuses to catch fire until it's almost too late.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The more you like the Judy Garland film, the more you might appreciate \"Oz the Great and Powerful.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Oz] qualifies as a cautionary tale, not about the perils of ambition and selfishness, but about the movie industry's misguided belief that it can distract the audience from a film's narrative weaknesses with little more than flash and spectacle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oz the Great and Powerful tells the story of how the Wizard came to Oz, answering a question I suspect no one was asking, but with considerable digital wizardry.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Relax, my pretties. \"Oz the Great and Powerful\" is a lollapalooza of funhouse thrills and visually sumptuous filmmaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>... as limitless technology teaches the wizard about his own human limitations, Franco hits grace notes that let us see glimmers of how great and powerful this uneven Oz might have been.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What does it say about \"Oz the Great and Powerful\" that China Doll, a creature born of digital code, is the movie's most affecting character?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bentley plays the role of funny, cagey psychopath quite well, and the film packs more laughs than frights. What woman wouldn't be interested after his homicidal message of love?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[A] miscast, misdirected botch of a can't-miss plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is one of those thrillers where the person on-screen is often the only person in the theater who can't guess what'll happen next.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A slickly efficient neo-grindhouse shocker, a gory palate cleanser for this season of high-toned Oscar magnets and high-minded political dramas.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Amid the dumbness and disgust for paying customers, the movie does manage to cough up something I didn't expect: a performance so terrible you can't quite believe it's happening: Bentley's.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The majority of [director Khalfoun's] chase and fight scenes are so artlessly staged that they render suspense moot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It sounds like a formula slasher film, but it's actually done well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A minimalist and unimaginative horror thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A serviceable gore-minded thriller --- a competent execution of a premise that ultimately becomes hampered by its inherent constraints.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The same old grim game of cat and mouse. Sure, we hope the mouse gets away. But mostly we just want the whole thing to end.</content>
</item>
</dataset>