<?xml version="1.0"?>

<dataset>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is cloying, deceitful, and more or less irresistible.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is an embarrassment, an overdrawn rom-com gone very wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A highly engineered puffball.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>All in all, I thoroughly enjoyed the movie until, in the end, it went somewhat bonkers with what amounted to a communal love fest on Christmas Eve.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Whatever the actors are given to do they make so delightful -- or so delightfully moving -- that Love Actually wins out over its wobbles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... a terrific film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are no fewer than nine interlocking and overlapping love stories in Richard Curtis' deadly epic sprawl of a romantic comedy, Love Actually. By the end of the movie, that's nine too many.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's enough that's right about Love to compensate for what's wrong with it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If listing the cast of Love Actually is exhausting, it's even more tiring to watch it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Love Actually is irresistible.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A form of emotional hardcore.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's no hardship whatsoever to sit through Love Actually ... But if Curtis could have sharpened his focus, and trusted his actors a bit more, Love Actually could have been splendid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Love Actually , Curtis' holiday-themed directing debut, abandons any pretext of sophistication for gloppy sentimentality, sugary pop songs and bawdy humor -- an approach that works about half the time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Call me Scrooge, but I sincerely hope that this film does not become a Christmas perennial.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's too busy with too many stories to tell. But there's so much heart and silly fun and genuine sentiment here, delivered by an A-list of Brit and American talent that it's hard to fault.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Yet another pandering, half-baked romantic comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Slick but uneven romantic comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie is so unfunny, uninspired and unoriginal I swear it could have started out as a club-footed Coen Brothers vehicle for George Clooney.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Curtis] is nothing if not capable of creating merry, madcap romantic comedy, and he punctuates the purposely hackneyed developments and labyrinthian structure with sly wit and sprightly pacing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The concept is solid, applying rusty romcom cliches to a tale of new-found masculine buddydom. But the plot is scatty.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I Love You, Man is the second movie this year -- He's Just Not That Into You being the first -- with a popular catchphrase for its title. This is one of the film's few distinctions.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a thin premise, and I Love You, Man features the usual quota of jokes involving masturbation, projectile vomiting and flatulence. But is it worth it? Thanks to Rudd and Segel (and some terrific cameos), totes magotes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The picture is worth catching for the delicate and toxic nuances of Rudd's performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the script doesn't always rise to their level, I Love You, Man is more than worth seeing for the chemistry between the shambling Segel and the endlessly inventive Rudd.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a hilarious comedy made even more successful because so much of the satire seems fresh.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The marvelous thing about John Hamburg's new comedy, I Love You, Man, is that rather than conforming to fit into some preexisting trend, it recognizes and even exalts in the reality that close male friendships can be a source of confusion and awkwardness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Luckily, the cast is so winning, that the occasional sexism can be ignored, and the off-the-wall pop culture name-checks (Lou Ferrigno, as a guest star?) enjoyed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In almost every major detail and minor plot hiccup, the sweet, vulgar, hilariously awkward I Love You, Man follows Ye Olde Formulae for standard romantic comedies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a one-joke pony, but director John Hamburg and his screenwriters manage to stretch it to nearly two hours of hilarity and quasi-profundity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The comedy I Love You, Man marks the overdue emergence of Paul Rudd as a star.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I Love You, Man is a success; it's Fight Club with hugs, not fists.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As sweet as it is tart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I Love You, Man feels like a clever concept in search of a completely developed movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its wit and ingenuous characters prove how far the bar's been raised.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fitfully funny comedy that owes much to Judd Apatow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite the clever premise and several laugh-aloud moments, the film as a whole underwhelms.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Smarter than it looks from its ubiquitous trailer, but not smart enough to be a fully satisfying adult comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I Love You, Man's light-hearted exploration of male bonding provides substantial fodder for humor, heightened by the inspired casting of two of the industry's most appealing comic actors.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An overt desire to please often leaves Tillman relying on force-feeding techniques.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Food aims to be a banquet of feelings, but mostly it serves up tripe.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The steaming platters of fried catfish, macaroni and cheese, sweet corn bread, and black-eyed peas that appear early and often in writer-director George Tillman Jr.'s sentimental family drama should be listed in the credits as costars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soul Food serves up family melodrama-cum-comedy that's tasty and satisfying, if not particularly profound or original.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tillman is tremendously skilled at bridging the vast shifts in tone.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A hearty, old fashioned meal of a film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A warm, funny, touching African American family drama, the kind of bittersweet melodrama that critics tend to relegate as crowd-pleasing corn. We could use more when it's this well done.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tasty, but easily forgotten.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tillman drew inspiration from his own Milwaukee family, his beloved grandmother in particular. Humor, sentiment and melodrama strike a balance as he brings to life nine major characters and a host of others as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An attractive cast and lingering shots of artery-busting delights that amount to pigout pornography.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This new menu movie has a soapy plot, appealing stars, family values, down-home atmosphere and a conviction that there's rarely a problem fried chicken can't cure. There sure are worse ways of looking at the world than that.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Tillman says Soul Food is based in part on his own family, and I believe him, because he seems to know the characters so well; by the film's end, so do we.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a fine line between good, solid drama and the sudsiness of a soap opera, and, although there are times when Soul Food crosses over, the movie remains predominantly on the right side.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nicely cast ensembler, centered on a hopelessly disorganized eatery owner and peopled by a weird collection of lovable eccentrics, is pacey entertainment that hardly puts a foot wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Akin perfectly captures the antic pace, eccentric personalities, and fickle fortunes of the restaurant game, and his vision of the Soul Kitchen as an all-night bacchanal is irresistible.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tasty concoction about a young man's frenetic struggle to keep his offbeat restaurant going.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Akin's earlier films were dramas, and he hasn't remade himself as a master of comedy, but even when the gags fall flat the vibe is agreeable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The slapsticky tone of Akin's latest work is more anarchic than heavenly, but the picture has its screwball charms.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soul Kitchen, which features a soundtrack laden with American soul and RandB standards, was a hit in Europe, and I suspect many American moviegoers will respond to it as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's silly, but it feels pretty good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Zany screwball farce.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A loose, generally good-natured comedy with screwball overtones.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lively, easygoing farce filled with high-energy music and amusing complications.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A pleasant enough piffle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not to warm to this movie would be churlish, and foodies will drool on demand; I recommend the shoal of silvery fish, spitting in a wide pan and awaiting its rain of lemon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching the German dramedy feels like sinking your teeth into a piece of angel food cake only to find you've bitten down on nothing at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You could call Soul Kitchen a romance with sensational music, or a hymn to friendship with romantic resonances. Whatever you want to call it, the thing is bursting with life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soul Kitchen is a ragged -- all right, sloppy -- group comedy that taxes neither us nor its maker.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are moments of fun (an aphrodisiac-laced dessert, for example), but generally the humor seems warmed-over.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soul Kitchen is sprawling, undisciplined, raucous, occasionally crass-and so full of life you forgive it everything.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soul Kitchen isn't, like Akin's earlier films, a full feast, rich with carefully catered courses of philosophy, cultural conflict and melodrama. It's really more akin to a light snack. But take a bite.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is tiresome not merely because of the familiarity of the material, but because there's little verve surrounding the proceedings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Akin's vision of interconnectedness in the global village, while similar to that of a movie like Babel, is more casual and lighthearted.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>This social farce is excellently written, fast paced and intelligently directed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In the end, however, it's let down by one easy laugh too many.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a blithe, silly, good-natured movie and, of its kind, quite an enjoyable one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The pity is, it isn't even outrageous.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Of course, simply everyone is completely bamboozled by our hero's disguise, even though he now looks like a Ken doll with liver disease.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a genuinely interesting idea, filled with dramatic possibilities, but the movie approaches it on the level of a dim-witted sit-com.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Men could have been so much more.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Considering the canvas the story provides, and the richness of the tradition it taps into, the amount and quality of the music is pretty disappointing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This one's only fair, but it has its low-down wiles and its moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is not a perfect film but it is a nice, solid reminder of how great Bernie Mac was.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It really is bittersweet to watch Mac in one of his final performances. He makes the most of pretty average material here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie crams in myriad needless subplots -- ostensibly to provide padding, which only draws attention to how thin the original story really is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, [it's] not good enough to make up for the unnecessary proliferation of Viagra humor, rectal-exam jokes and comedy at the expense of women.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While it's a shamelessly mediocre movie, it's not mediocre in the usual ways.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Men has a lot to overcome in its effort to be funny. The pall over it can be ignored only intermittently, at least for the time being.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The only good reason to see the otherwise dismal comedy Soul Men is to have a look at the late actor and comedian Bernie Mac in one of his final screen roles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>So why is this film worth seeing? Because it's an ideal showcase for Mac's peerless comic chops.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>We've heard this tune before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sort of a riff on The Sunshine Boys with hints of Dreamgirls, about all Malcolm D. Lee's relentlessly crass comedy has going for it are some amusing Motown-ish numbers and the chemistry between Mac and his real-life friend Samuel L. Jackson.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a raunchy energy to Soul Men that cannot be denied. Even if the film is derivative, predictable, visibly low-budget and crude, it's also darn funny a good deal of the time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's nothing here you haven't seen before, but the genuine and infectious chemistry between Mr. Jackson and Mr. Mac and the irresistible energy of their performances is more than enough to give the movie real heft and momentum.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mac was a magnetic performer with a long history of redeeming mediocre movies; unfortunately this is another one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Samuel L. Jackson and Bernie Mac appear to be having a good time, and for most of this raunchy, poorly orchestrated buddy comedy, that's enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Men has soul, but expects too much of its charismatic stars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Soul Men is a raucous, rambling comedy, offering some laughs, some groans and a feast for fans of the musical idioms it mocks and celebrates.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This nearly plotless movie follows the maiden voyage of NWA (a moniker that seems to be the extent of the film's wit) through a torrent of stale ghetto jokes in the vein exhausted years ago by the Wayans brothers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An hour and a half of real airplane turbulence is better than sitting through the bad, offensive material that makes up Soul Plane.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Makes up for what it lacks in genuine humor by overdosing viewers with outrageous sexuality and outsize stereotypes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sloppy, uneven, vulgar, lowbrow and often very funny, Jessy Terrero's debut movie might be called Airport Car Wash Scary Movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No doubt Soul Plane sounds more offensive than it is when seen. That doesn't make it more than passable burlesque, but burlesque has its place, too.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A better- than-average comedy that is raunchy and tasteless but ultimately funny from beginning to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Plane is about 'the first urban' (black) airline, whose motto is 'We fly. We party. We land.' They left out 'We potty.'</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Movies like Soul Plane give bad taste a bad name.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This one-joke comedy vehicle is flying through a laugh-free zone.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nearly unwatchable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No one is spared the movie's raunchy political incorrectness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If it's not funny to you that a bunch of white passengers in polo shirts would say 'Oh, goody!' when they hear the in-flight movie stars Sandra Bullock, then don't bother with the rest of Soul Plane.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A relentless sucker punch to black entrepreneurship.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The jokes fly faster than the plane, but the humor cruising level is closer to the old TV series Flying High than to Airplane.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A third of the way into Soul Plane, maybe earlier if you're in the right mood or with the wrong company, you might actually start to enjoy disliking the movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Plane begins as a high-spirited romp before running out of gas and ideas about halfway up the tarmac.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A succession of would-be rousing cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Surfer seems simply too sugar-coated to be true.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You wonder why this movie isn't a documentary, rather than a synthetic feature film with the heroine's arm digitally removed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hamilton is played, blandly, by Anna Sophia Robb, and her devoted parents, less bland, are played by Dennis Quaid and Helen Hunt. The surfing footage, much of it shot off the coast of Kauai, is not bland at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's Bethany and Alana's friendship - its sturdiness and vulnerability, its laughs and sincere apologies - that rules the day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A by-the-numbers biopic about young surfer Bethany Hamilton.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For plenty of family viewers, this film will catch a wave.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An inspiring tale, even when true, doesn't necessarily make for an inspiring movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Given the heroic subject, the movie is as thrilling as a dish of rice pudding, a made-for-TV-style effort that rides a wave of religious sentiment into theatres.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The swells of inspirational storytelling sometimes threaten to swamp the underlying inspirational story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The flaw in the storytelling strategy of \"Soul Surfer\" is that it doesn't make Bethany easy to identify with. She's almost eerie in her optimism. Her religious faith is so unshaken, it feels taken for granted.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its bubbling optimism and spectacular scenery are hard not to like.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bethany's determination and faith are remarkable. It's too bad this movie made a brave young woman's life appear like an unremarkable soap opera.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The surfer's story is so made-for-cinema that a complete wipeout seems almost impossible. And yet the filmmakers come pretty close.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a portrait of a spirited, resilient athlete, the movie succeeds best, unafraid to face its heroine's daunting challenges directly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though it flirts with saccharine Sunday-school uplift, there's a redeeming core of sincerity in this story of real-life tragedy and perseverance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The best moments come when Robb's all-purpose toughness experiences vulnerable doubt. These moments are flickers, but they're bright and human.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>That \"Soul Surfer\" rates as a giant leap for this team speaks well about the conviction the movie's actors bring to the material as well as the respect afforded the Hamilton family and their faith.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>AnnaSophia Robb is too subdued as the teenage heroine; one might expect more affect from a young woman fighting to overcome disability and return to competitive surfing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A horror movie without horror, a spook pic without spookiness and a metaphysical drama without the slightest spiritual tug.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[A] dodo of suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A cinematic oxymoron: the tasteful teensploitation pic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soulless, spookless sludge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The concept of the story is far more interesting than the finished product, which is standard fare at best.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Survivors is a truly awful mix of bad direction, nonsensical story line and dialogue that appears to have been made up on the spot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a real struggle to survive Soul Survivors to the finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For an exploitation flick, Soul Survivors also is woefully slow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Survivors is such a numbingly opaque and enervating movie experience that even Jeepers Creepers seems poetic and luminous by comparison.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soul Survivors wants to be like a bad dream and it succeeds. Unfortunately, bad in this case doesn't mean scary and surreal. It means boring and confused.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A sentimental story of little suspense and scant terror.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is a dog. It's tepid and clumsy, and entirely derivative.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Psychology-themed horror tale goes a little nutty in the end.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A preposterous supernatural thriller that inexplicably managed to sign up Julianne Moore to star.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What unholy spirit could have possessed Julianne Moore when she signed on for the sort of throwaway horror flick that would normally star unknowns and go straight to DVD?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The end credits, which seem almost as long as the movie itself, dementedly thank everyone from the citizens of Pennsylvania to William Wyler, Howard Hawks and God. What an insult.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ultimately, the silly material overwhelms the style ...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, no one here is especially sympathetic, and the shock both parents seem to feel on discovering their kid is a grade-A brat is hard to believe, given the general sense of verisimilitude.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Martin Ritt soaks us in the heat, the beauty, the racism and the buzzing cicadas of Louisiana.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ritt's film must respond to the needs of an entertainment industry, and in its desire to be uplifting, leaves its characters one-dimensional without ensuring that the one dimension is heroic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Sounder, an inteligent enough movie, avoids all the major pitfalls of its type, it also lacks the excitement that may have come from plumbing greater depths and discovering a few tougher, less accessible insights.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is one of the most compassionate and truthful of movies, and there's not a level where it doesn't succeed completely.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Painfully honest, unpretentious, and blessedly simple.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a thriller, 'Sound of My Voice' tails off and its budget shows. But for Marling it's an impressive calling card.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is a huge difference between an unexpectedly sudden ending (like The Sopranos) and a non-ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's nothing wrong with asking viewers to fill in some holes. But \"Sound of My Voice\" leaves you dangling, reaching out for something that's just not there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Behold the trials and tribulations of going undercover. It doesn't matter if it's cop or journalist, a muddying of purpose takes hold once a mole plunges deeper into the darkness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The intelligence in it is both soothing and intimidating.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This plays like an early George Romero shocker but without Romero's humor or social commentary.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sound of My Voice grounds its science fiction in scarily effective \"what ifs\" that don't require a light year's stretch of the imagination.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Marling] is a talent with an understated presence. It conveys in this film an insidious conviction: What is her motive, really?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[The] idea is intriguing enough. But this clever, low-budget film kicks the concept up a few notches to mesmerizing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>That the movie is part of a possible trilogy doesn't make up for the thin, underdeveloped feel. But Marling, who weaves a strong spell, will probably keep appearing in our future.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fascinates and titillates, but never quite persuades.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You just want something energetic to happen, and it doesn't until the film's effective final scene.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sound of My Voice serves up moments of extreme dread and discomfort, but works a winning undercurrent of playful absurdity into the material as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Proves how effectively you can set the mind-bending mood without any special effects, action sequences or spectral rabbits.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's an unshakeable sense of uneasiness as one never knows precisely what might occur, and the truth is almost impossible to discern.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sharp little cult thriller with a do-it-yourself ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>None of this really adds up to much beyond an hour-and-a-half or so of vague doubletalk, arbitrary decisions and increasingly annoying frustration.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"Sound of My Voice'' holds your attention for a while, but fails to build much suspense as it races toward a predictable climax.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Marling seems less in danger of creating the same part over and over again than the same movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The contemporary music sequences are a distraction from the heart of the movie: truly astounding archival footage of speeches, marches, and demonstrations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Through vivid archival material and voice-overs, the filmmakers create moving vignettes that, taken together, form a fascinating primer on nonviolence as a political force and discipline.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An elegantly crafted new documentary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tthe film is primarily interested in the music that accompanied this turmoil, which is a bit like covering the American Revolution with the focus on the wigs Washington and Jefferson wore.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Essentially a condensed, lightly airbrushed, skillfully assembled history of the civil rights movement, with musical interludes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A documentary that uneasily combines a history of the civil rights movement with renditions by contemporary pop stars of the songs that rallied it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For anyone who is either ignorant of or has simply forgotten the extent to which broken bones and unbowed heads paved the way for the Obama Age, it's a much-needed history lesson.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Holes in logic get swept aside by the brisk pace and stimulating tale.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A casually brainy and surprisingly thoughtful blockbuster... that is ultimately as much about saving the day as seizing it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is a formally disciplined piece of work, a triumph of movie syntax, made with a sense of rhythm and pace, and Gyllenhaal, who is always good at conveying anxiety, gives Stevens's desperation a comic edge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This time, Jones has more money and greater studio expectations behind him, so what begins as another existential head trip that puts ideas before spectacle eventually morphs into something trite and compromised -- hard sci-fi gone soft.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A smart sci-fi thriller that maybe asks a bit more of its audience than the average movie. But the payoff is solid, and really -- how long is eight minutes?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Years -- months? -- hence I expect there will be an avalanche of PhD theses focusing on these mumbo-jumbo mind-meld melodramas. In the meantime you can pick up your BA at the multiplex today.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>None of this makes any sense if you think about it, but the idea is so much fun that thinking about it may be your last impulse.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The problem with \"Source Code\" is the idea of \"Source Code.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Jones and screenwriter Ben Ripley also deserve credit for expertly shuffling the plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first film in a while to have a decent heart while quickening your pulse.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Putting across a premise as fantastical as this film's requires top-flight acting, as well as a kind of poker face, and that's precisely what the movie delivers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fun ride of a sci-fi thriller with terrific romantic chemistry between Jake Gyllenhaal and Michelle Monaghan.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For the most part, \"Source Code\" delivers on its promises with precision and care - all that's missing is Punxsutawney Phil and a toast to world peace.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thriller that takes a science fiction premise and uses it, not for the sake of splashy effects, but as a doorway into the human soul.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's just enough pop physics, and more than enough real human psychology, to lend this intriguing popcorn movie some depth.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Source Code\" is perfectly enjoyable as a swiftly moving thriller, and Gyllenhaal is effective as a mystified fellow who eventually engages himself - and us - in putting the pieces of the puzzle together.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In \"Source Code,\" thinking is doing, which makes it a nice respite from standard action fare with its guys, grunts and guns (though there's some of that here too).</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With a twisty, mind-bending plot that frequently changes direction and occasionally overreaches, \"Source Code\" wouldn't work at all without a cast with the determination and ability to really sell its story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Source Code\" is a bullet train of a thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I can't easily remember a film I've enjoyed less.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What's frustrating about the film is that even though it's clear Stone is making a number of valid and important points about both media manipulation and America's untoward political influence, he's also so obviously biased in his reporting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stone has a crucial, overlooked viewpoint to impart, but as a documentary filmmaker, his content and technique are not terribly engaging.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It looks like raw notes and impressions for a future novel.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>South of the Border offers valuable historical, social and political context, particularly if you aren't an international-news junkie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Oliver Stone might not be the ideal reporter to send on a truth-seeking mission to South America, but if nobody else wants to do it, we have to take what we can get.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A personal, maddeningly blinkered travelogue through Latin America that, for all its willful naivete, offers a valuable glimpse of historical and social change.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I think it's a galling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too much of the movie is about Stone's fawning regard for these powerful men. He's an annoying presence, both on screen and in voiceover, who nearly sabotages his own movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unabashedly one-sided.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Because so little has been made in the United States about South America's leftward continental drift, South of the Border is a valuable, if naively idealistic, introductory tutorial on a significant international trend.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Marks an anti-milestone in journalism (about which Stone has plenty of complaints, specifically identifying Fox News and the New York Times).</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like Michael Moore -- a clip of whom appears early in the film -- Stone isn't just his own worst enemy, but his cause's.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>...engaging enough as polemics go, but unlikely to change many minds. Stone has many directorial gifts, but lightness of touch isn't really one of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>South of the Border is near worthless as reportage, but it is an endlessly rewarding auteur project.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is rose-colored agitprop, but it catches a current of history.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So one-sided that it nearly validates what the Right says about Hollywood's liberal crusaders.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A predictable compendium of Fox News clips on one side and peasants glad-handing their leaders on the other, the docu offers little genuine information and no investigative research, adopting a style even more polemical than Stone's earlier docs</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Good-humored, illuminating and without cant.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[An] inspired, self-referential animated musical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rude, but inspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A happy surprise!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While there aren't more than a handful of gut-busting, laugh-aloud moments, there is enough sly, slick humor to keep the average viewer chuckling throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's without any redeeming social value whatsoever. And it's funny from beginning to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Very funny, extremely obscene.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Profane, blasphemous and absolutely hilarious, Bigger, Longer and Uncut is easily the funniest of all the high-profile comedies released this year!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even clean-thinking people may be tempted to admit that the thing is shamelessly, raucously hilarious!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>South Park has a gag-to-laugh ratio even higher than the new Austin Powers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The quite clever satirical moments in this crudely animated filth fest, though, are not remotely worth being dragged through the cinematic sewer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Certain, probably arrested, personalities (like mine) just find this kind of sh*t pretty funny and any attempt to talk your way around that is, as Cartman would say, blowing bubbles out your *ss.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Parker and Stone are madly inventive when it comes to details.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A more clever diversion than anyone had any right to expect!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>After Big Daddy, it's almost heartening to see a movie that's not afraid to be upfront about its coarseness, one that doesn't smother its very reason for being with hypocritical sentimentality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tasteless, scatalogical and very funny!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Raunchy, riotously irreverent and thrillingly rangy!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The year's most slashing political commentary is not in the new films by Oliver Stone, David Lynch or John Sayles, but in an animated comedy about obscenity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In terms of raw wit and fearless satire, the South Park kids put Mike Myers and Adam Sandler to shame.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>South Park: Bigger, Longer and Uncut turns out to be the funniest, most risk-taking, most incisive movie of the summer!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[An] inspired, self-referential animated musical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Rude, but inspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A happy surprise!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While there aren't more than a handful of gut-busting, laugh-aloud moments, there is enough sly, slick humor to keep the average viewer chuckling throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's without any redeeming social value whatsoever. And it's funny from beginning to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Very funny, extremely obscene.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Profane, blasphemous and absolutely hilarious, Bigger, Longer and Uncut is easily the funniest of all the high-profile comedies released this year!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even clean-thinking people may be tempted to admit that the thing is shamelessly, raucously hilarious!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>South Park has a gag-to-laugh ratio even higher than the new Austin Powers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The quite clever satirical moments in this crudely animated filth fest, though, are not remotely worth being dragged through the cinematic sewer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Certain, probably arrested, personalities (like mine) just find this kind of sh*t pretty funny and any attempt to talk your way around that is, as Cartman would say, blowing bubbles out your *ss.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Parker and Stone are madly inventive when it comes to details.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A more clever diversion than anyone had any right to expect!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>After Big Daddy, it's almost heartening to see a movie that's not afraid to be upfront about its coarseness, one that doesn't smother its very reason for being with hypocritical sentimentality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tasteless, scatalogical and very funny!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Raunchy, riotously irreverent and thrillingly rangy!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The year's most slashing political commentary is not in the new films by Oliver Stone, David Lynch or John Sayles, but in an animated comedy about obscenity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In terms of raw wit and fearless satire, the South Park kids put Mike Myers and Adam Sandler to shame.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>South Park: Bigger, Longer and Uncut turns out to be the funniest, most risk-taking, most incisive movie of the summer!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A story which the book reviewers warned us was disappointing and dull, as originally told by James Hilton in his So Well Remembered, has been miraculously transmuted into an affecting and fascinating tale in the film of the same title.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The somewhat plausible and proximate horrors in the story of Soylent Green carry the production over its awkward spots to the status of a good futuristic exploitation film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Uneven and slightly muddled futuristic horror story -- not really science fiction, more like an antipollution PSA gone berserk.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Good, solid stuff, assembled efficiently enough to be pretty persuasive.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The crew flings itself energetically through space in search of laughs, but it will never penetrate the galaxy where Blazing Saddles and Young Frankenstein traced their giddy orbits.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film's low-tech styling is roughly the cardboard inversion of the cinematic machines it parodies, and Brooks seems less inclined than usual to push the overkill urges too far.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mel Brooks will do anything for a laugh. Unfortunately, what he does in Spaceballs, a misguided parody of the Star Wars adventures, isn't very funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Typically, the best conceits end in pratfalls, and non-Brooks fans may find that the gravitational pull towards the thumpingly obvious outweighs the wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If it isn't likely to generate what Mr. Brooks himself refers to as 'Spaceballs II: The Search for More Money, neither is it anything less than gentle, harmless satire that occasionally has real bite.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>How do you review a movie like this, anyway? I guess by saying whether you laughed or not. I did laugh, but not enough to recommend the film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The jokes in the films are all pretty much in the same vein -- you might call it borsch-belt postmodern -- and they're all on about the same level, too.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Coupling the men-on-a-mission antics of 'Armageddon' with the catch-all sci-fi pastiche of TV's 'Futurama', 'Space Chimps' is an underwhelming slice of lowbrow CGI entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I have to admit, there's a sort of dopey, cute, harmless charm to this movie. It actually doesn't stink.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The animated action movie nevertheless delivers -- da-dum -- more fun than a barrel of monkeys.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Space Chimps may be just a computer-animated comedy, but -- don't laugh -- it cleverly resonates with arguments favoring increased stature for chimpanzees (and all apes) with whom humans share a near-identical genetic blueprint.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's probably not enough fuel beyond cute chimps in Candyland to achieve orbit for the kids.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When it comes to chimps and space, Stanley Kubrick pretty much covered the topic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A bland tale.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film's creators haven't learned the Pixar strategy of creating a resonant story as the foundation of a film. So we get a formulaic tale of a lazy nonconformist who learns to take his responsibilities seriously and saves the day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Why would you take your kids to see Space Chimps, an uninspired animated feature about chimp astronauts, when you could take them instead to see Wall-E.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Journalism is all about having the courage to write the truth even if it will get you mocked by your relatives and co-workers, so here goes: Space Chimps is hilarious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The CG animation is nothing special, but the characters are surprisingly fun and the story is full of enough puns, wordplay and slapstick to elicit laughs from across the age spectrum.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Worse are the chimps themselves. Their bodies are realistic in all the wrong ways, with grotesque appendages and unpleasantly textured fur, while the expressions on their unadorable mugs are entirely devoid of humanity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Space Chimps is delightful from beginning to end: A goofy space opera.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of those cartoons parents at least won't mind sitting through while little Miss or Mister Eight-and-younger gets his or her chuckles at the cute talking primates.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While candy-colored graphics should dazzle kids, Space Chimps has little draw for audiences spoiled by the Pixar-given knowledge that CGI can entertain -- and not just stupefy -- moviegoers of any age.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It'll keep the kids entertained for a while and give their parents a chuckle or two along the way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As light as a banana souffle and about as substantial.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a rare pleasure to watch four terrific actors having the time of their lives.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie may not pack anything near the emotional punch of Unforgiven, but it's an entertainingly raffish action-comedy nonetheless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Eastwood] made a mature film that bests nearly all of the summer's highly touted blockbusters for pure escapism.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Some of the bits are funny ... but after a while it gets kind of old.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A comic masterpiece of full rear male nudity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of those over-the-hill-gang buddyfests that pretend to be about teamwork and valor but are really about movie-star cronyism.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Space Cowboys is poorly engineered: lurchingly paced, the dramatic conflicts duct taped together.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even star power can get lost in space.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As craftily savvy as it is well-crafted.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An absorbing mix of perilous suspense, derring-do, personal courage and well-judged self-sacrifice.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's an abundance of charm and screen presence from the four veteran actors.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Old stars shine in funny, thrilling Space Cowboys.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Clint Eastwood makes our day with the summer's most delightful surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Eastwood's economy of gesture both behind and in front of the camera is a pleasure in itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Space Cowboys works both as a humorous action movie and a cultural statement.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Without succumbing to bitterness or nostalgia or overstating the case for one generation's virtues, [Eastwood] and his cohorts mount a vigorous and funny defense of maturity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Simpler and cruder than Who Framed Roger Rabbit in terms of story and technique, this is still a great deal of fun, confirming that Jordan is every bit as mythological a creature as Daffy Duck or Yosemite Sam.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cute, rambunctious, generally amusing rather than outright funny, this clever mix of live action, highlighted by the unequaled skills of basketball superstar Michael Jordan, and animated Looney Tunes antics will be a must-see for kids.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sufferin' succotash!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This film was made very quickly by animation standards, and the haste shows.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's the first time either Jordan or Bugs has had a starring role on the big screen. It's gimmicky Saturday-morning cartoon wackiness in your face -- funny, but brain-deadening.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Space Jam is no Who Framed Roger Rabbit, but it works well enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's an inspired way to use, and kid, Jordan's image while at the same time updating Bugs Bunny and Company to doing battle in the multizillion-dollar animation sweepstakes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In basketball terms, Space Jam is more akin to the 'garbage time' that concludes lopsided games, when reckless playing is no substitute for the real thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie's undermining flaw is its lack of screen magic (and first-rate cartoon gags) that Who Framed Roger Rabbit had throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The climactic game in Space Jam goes slack repeatedly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jordan has immense likability, and his extraordinary talents need no further adulation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are signs that a lot has been cut, and in trimming his film Brooks may have squeezed too tight: his movie needs breathing space.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is Hollywood liberal humanism as muted join-the-dots melodrama, all carefully calculated colouring, broad outlines, and no room for fruitful digression.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film gets better as it goes along ... and all the characters, including Deborah, become more interesting and appealing as we get to know them better.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Brooks, fumbling around with too many characters and too many issues, can't find the heart of the story or give heart to the part of it he chose to focus on.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film too often seems to be talking down, to its subjects and to its audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is what in Hollywood they call 'character-driven,' and it does take its sweet time. But much of that time is sweet indeed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Offensive because it turns liberal self-abasement into self-congratulation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sometimes Brooks's ideas are legitimate, but his way of putting them across is dishonest. Sometimes the ideas are dishonest, but his way of putting them across is legitimate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's funny and wicked fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So rancid is Brooks's fury that it's clouded his judgment, so that each of his main characters is a stereotype of the most broad-brush, malodorous nature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A performer's showcase. While the pleasantly sentimental comedy doesn't bowl you over with cinematic technique, it's likely to make audiences happy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Feels like inadvertent misogynist psychodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's fun to be had if you can accept Spanglish's dubious relationship to the actual universe.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An unusually observant film marked by dry, acerbic humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With his unerring eye for characters, even their hidden dark corners, Brooks makes Spanglish a rich blend of humor and heartbreak.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A pepperpot bubbling with pungent insights and sharp wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is no shortage of zingers (mostly delivered by Evelyn), but the film lacks credibility.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You're constantly aware of how oddly these people are behaving, and the artificiality spoils the illusion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Doesn't match Brooks' prior efforts because the characters are too broadly written.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An unusually shallow and facile work for Brooks, but the writing and the performances -- other than Leoni's -- keep us at least halfway involved.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sparkle shamelessly piles on the cliches, but it's an entertaining ride throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Noteworthy only for featuring Whitney Houston's last screen appearance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sparkle is an assembly of parts and pieces from other, better movies - an overly familiar jumble of cliches mashed together.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Sparkle\" isn't blindingly original but it delivers solid entertainment, and despite the cliches I was never for a moment bored.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Anyone who has seen Dream Girls, What's Love Got To Do With It? or even The Doors will find themselves in familiar (if inferior) territory here ...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's nice that \"Sparkle\" honors the memory of Motown's heyday; if only it could have lived up to those standards.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Often seems like a flat, straightforward Supremes biopic in its adherence to seemingly pointless scenes and exposition.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Sparkle\" trafficks in the same gorgeous Motown style -- sonic and visual -- that made the original film, and \"Dreamgirls\" after it, such delectable fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Generally improves on the source material as much as possible while still succumbing to some of the same hoary showbiz beats.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Sparkle\" was made by smart people who built on their star's strengths, accounted for her weaknesses and didn't lean on her to carry the whole picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If the film is a sudsy show-business Cinderella story in which Emma's youngest daughter, Sparkle (Jordin Sparks), ascends to glory, Houston's presence makes it a cautionary tale.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The melodramatic story is familiar, though the talented cast makes the most of rather tired material.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Houston's performance proves that this could have been the first step not merely in a comeback but in a major re-invention. She had the instincts of a superb character actress.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tika Sumpter [is] the best actress of the three ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Where the original Sparkle was a ghetto melodrama with equal parts mob and music, the Akils have refashioned it into a saga of family rupture and reconciliation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A bright and breezy musical that puts a breath of spring in this clammy late-summer season.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a fun, sudsy tale of show-biz ups and downs, with an endearing Sparks in the title role as one of three singing siblings in Motown-era Detroit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At times funny, sad, poignant and suspenseful, Sparrows is a showcase for Majidi's masterful storytelling -- and Naji's superb acting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At times tedious but ultimately beguiling, Song of Sparrows morphs from a sly dramedy about running a household into a fable about two ways of life (urban and rural) that can't coexist.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The images in The Song of Sparrows have a poetic grace that's to be desired in storytelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is somehow congenial to feel that we are watching a tale that could have been told elsewhere.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Delicate and sturdy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Song of Sparrows is a sweet and uplifting humanistic fable that celebrates the joys of community and pastoral life over a harried and materialistic urban existence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the fourth collaboration for Naji and Majidi, and the actor and director feed off each other creatively, pushing the boundaries of the characters each time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A leisurely and lovely picture, well worth seeing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Director] Majidi is a master director of tear-jerkers, and he proves true to form with Sparrows.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you can look past the almost silent-era sermonizing of The Song of Sparrows, you can see something else at work here, and deeper things on view.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As unabashedly sentimental as The Song of Sparrows often becomes, this simple fable of a righteous man's relationship to his family, his community and most of all his faith has the force of conviction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A parable of corruption, catastrophe and eventual redemption. Mr. Majidi's tale wasn't meant to be timely, of course, but the shoe fits, and the film wears it well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's Majidi's impeccable eye that lifts the movie's everyday-people parable above the norm; wedded to such visual poetry, even its minor tragedies and smaller victories seem positively profound.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is pleasingly meandering, till the more typically Majidian soulful and teary-eyed climax.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story, spiked with gentle humor, moves smoothly through the standard tropes of Iranian art house cinema.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Beautifully crafted, often sentimental, sometimes humorous pic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This may be the most literate of all the spectacles set in antiquity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Asurprisingly apt companion piece to Paths of Glory in its consideration of the mechanisms of power.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is a spotty, uneven drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The result in Meet the Spartans is less classic Mel Brooks than middling Best Week Ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I'm moving to Europe.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's so bad even Carmen Electra should be embarrassed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a MADtv or Saturday Night Live sketch dressed up in feature-length clothing. It's way too much of an OK thing. And the way-too-much-ness goes on and on.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Jason Friedberg and Aaron Seltzer, the team behind Meet the Spartans, prove that ridiculing other movies is much easier than making your own.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lazy, lame and painfully unfunny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What's the point of making a parody that's dumber than the stuff it parodies?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Writer-directors Jason Friedberg and Aaron Seltzer basically reprise the tired formula from their earlier efforts, which is to throw in as many pop culture references as possible to cover up the lack of any real wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film gives you the pleasurably junky sensation of living inside an apocalyptic videogame.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A moodily malevolent, anything-goes revenge fantasy that relies more upon special visual and digitally animated effects for its intended appeal than any comics-derived sci-fier to date.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This hopelessly redundant action gross-out aspires to a form of hip vacuousness -- and may achieve it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dippe, an old SFX hand, needs to think about how to tell a story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The nonsensical screenplay can barely stand-up to the hellzapoppin,' Beelzebubbin' effects mustered by first-time director Mark Dippe.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a visual experience, Spawn is unforgettable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>... an incoherent blitz of noise, chintzy special effects and bargain-basement allegory.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's no suspense, no emotional involvement with the characters, and the cynical, sophomoric storytelling is confusing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>... a nonstop bombardment that recalls Judge Dredd, but with better diction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As a comic book, Spawn may be first rate, but, as a movie, it's a retread.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the parallels drawn between therapy and prostitution grow tiresome, the duo's interaction is peppered with inspired comedic moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At the end, there is no great revelation, but Huppert has succeeded once again in making us wonder what's going on in there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Complex, compassionate and endlessly illuminating...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It isn't a lightweight erotic romp at all, but a complicated and delicate two-person odyssey that's much richer and subtler than that.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As cliches trot through their sessions - it's like \"In Treatment\" as bedroom farce - we check out. Huppert, though, is as fearless as ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite uniformly fine acting, Special Treatment never really pulls the viewer in because its insights and observations, while artfully rendered, don't possess the energy of revelation; they're largely obvious.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mugging to an unfunny script, Keaton and Davis are no Tracy and Hepburn, and the funereal pace doesn't help.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ron Underwood, the director of City Slickers, once again compromises appealing actors and an entertaining premise with a needless overlay of mush.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Speechless is overplotted and underwritten. Every situation is straight out of stock, with no room for variation or originality.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie's a campaign disaster from the get-go, and no amount of damage control (including MGM's extensive publicity) can hide it.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>Director Ron Underwood demonstrated a knack for comedy in City Slickers, but when it comes to love scenes ... Keaton and Davis might as well be stampeding cows.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The level of humor is dialed safely down to the Sitcom setting, which limits what can happen, and how much we can care about it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Do yourself a favor and see a movie instead.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[It] sinks faster than a rock.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dafoe's take on Dennis Hopper's Hopper impersonation is plain pointless; Bullock too is wasted in a ditzy half-role; and Patric is unsmiling and resolutely uncharismatic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even the film's big-ticket closing stunts are more impressive for their size than for any excitement they generate.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>They keep getting worse and worse and worse . . .</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Movies like this embrace goofiness with an almost sensual pleasure. And so, on a warm summer evening, do I.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I hope that somewhere Keanu Reeves is laughing about being considered a nonactor while the wax dummy Jason Patric has somehow achieved a rep as intense and gifted.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A waterlogged sequel that'll soon be bottom-feeding with Beyond the Poseidon Adventure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What a reeking bag of nothingness! What emptiness, what vaporous vapidity! What rot, stink, and whiff of mold spore!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Twelve-year-old boys should be wowed, but for the rest of us, it will depend on your appetite for eye candy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I love the look and the style and the spirit of this film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Speed Racer intends to convey a sense of heedless momentum, but it drags painfully.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This toxic admixture of computer-generated frenzy and live-action torpor succeeds in being, almost simultaneously, genuinely painful -- the esthetic equivalent of needles in eyeballs -- and weirdly benumbing, like eye candy laced with lidocaine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More than the story of the Racer family, Speed Racer is the visual autobiography of the Wachowskis and their pit crew of computer-nerd Einsteins, using the tools of their trade to transform the movie medium.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a movie about velocity, the excitement factor is low and the races feel like a drag.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie, unfortunately, doesn't make that leap from sensation to art, but it suggests fascinating possibilities for moviemakers interested in using the latest techniques seriously to explore the world -- the fairyland we have made with our technology.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Shapes hurtle toward you, then recede abruptly, each bearing some fragment of narrative information that has now passed you by forever. Nausea and anxiety begin to wash over you in overlapping waves.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The actors seem lost in a gumball dispenser; the audience, for the most part, might well feel the same way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Someday, real artists may come along to use some of the techniques that the Wachowskis are developing. Then things will get interesting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Any film fan will appreciate the Wachowskis' vision of this alternate universe that's every bit as densely textured and as pan-Asian/pan-planetary in its casting as The Matrix.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Speed Racer is brilliantly photographed and edited. It's told in a literally visionary style, full of innovation and breathtaking risk. But when it comes to the story, it's running on empty.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie makes you crave a streamlined story, interesting characters and a joystick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Were Larry and Andy Wachowski just really, really lucky when they made The Matrix?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The fakeness of it all overwhelms, dampening any real excitement. It's hard to care about characters so stiff and one-dimensional they out-cartoon the cartoon originals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It gave me a headache, a stomach ache and the less-defined unease that comes from witnessing a major change in the zeitgeist. Because the zeitgeist, judging from this movie, now embraces rattle-headed visual delirium at all costs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's exploitation at its most listless and uninspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hard to watch -- not because of its unflinching realism, but rather for its mawkish reliance on every boy hooker flick from Midnight Cowboy to Johns.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A potent mixture of sentiment and grit, and it showcases the talents of its young principals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Cars are not funny. Speeding cars are not funny. It is not funny when a car spins around and speeds in the other direction. It is not funny when a car flies through the air. It is not funny when a truck crashes into a car.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not to be speechless about it, David O. Selznick has a rare film in Spellbound.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An empty shell.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Three major stars being involved, it all wraps up happily but implausibly.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The ending, though emotionally satisfying, collapses under scrutiny. This lack of payoff is a real flaw in a film pitched to a discriminating sci-fi mentality.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Given its situational premise -- outer space goes underwater -- Sphere is filled with visual potential, yet Levinson can't tap it. He's just a whole lot more comfortable trying to tame the human software than the technical hardware.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As the umpteenth entrant in the We-Are-Not-Alone sweepstakes, Sphere feels awfully familiar because it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While this is no quick-witted treat on a par with Mr. Levinson's Wag the Dog, it's a solid thriller with showy scientific overtones.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Somewhere out there, maybe there's a small cadre of film-goers who will appreciate Sphere's dubious charms, but I'm not among them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sphere winds up just a load of balls.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The only excellence is in the acting, and even then the screenplay puts the characters through so many U-turns that dramatic momentum is impossible.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are some things that humankind is just better off not knowing about.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In emphasizing angst over energy, the movie is much like its hero -- not the dashing crime fighter in a red-and-black bodysuit but the introspective nerd who both endears and exasperates.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A perfectly serviceable early-summer popcorn picture that will satisfy its core teen constituency and not displease general viewers looking for some disposable entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately the film, like many of its ilk, is driven by special effects, and there's a serious disconnect between Maguire's sweet-natured dialogue and Spider-Man's pounding violence and stunning acrobatic work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This accomplished blockbuster announces itself as a stylish piece of pop myth-spinning.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's got appealing performers as the leads.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Raimi gives this unapologetic fluff a mind, a heart and a keen sense of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A]n energetic romp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a pure popcorn movie -- the kind of film one can unabashedly enjoy for what it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With disarmingly entertaining movies like this, dare I say, who needs big bad superhero movies?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An exuberance, a celebration, a hoot, a kick and a half.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A blockbuster with a heart and a brain.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie that both thrills the eye and, in its over-the-top way, touches the heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The superhero part of the movie will leave audiences with a flat feeling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A model of what films like this should be like.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Speaking in terms of spectacle, craft, romance and humor, it's the movie to beat this summer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Maguire is a surprisingly effective Peter/Spider-Man.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Exciting as it is tender and romantic, Raimi's Spider-Man looks like a movie that will please not only the Spider-Man converted but also the viewer who just wanders in.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even when it sputters, this Spider-Man is loftier than most attempts at movie wizardry.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too many villains, too many pale plot strands, too many romantic misunderstandings, too many conversations, too many street crowds looking high into the air and shouting \"oooh!\" this way, then swiveling and shouting \"aaah!\" that way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nap time. Perhaps it's the weight of expectations, the rattle of a zillion calculators or the curse of Bryce Dallas Howard (forever our Lady in the Water), but the latest Spider-Man is a fussy, dispirited affair.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Raimi at least manages to make it both huge and human.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After two epic successes that deserved their success, the latest installment swings between intense action sequences and unaccountably flat dramatic interludes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One has to consider that the film's problems -- and they are numerous -- may be the product of the franchise's runaway popularity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All in all, the fun has simply gone out of it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aesthetically and conceptually wrung out, fizzled rather than fizzy, this latest installment in the spider-bites-boy adventure story shoots high, swings low and every so often hits the sweet spot, but mostly just plods and plods along.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An extravagant three-ring circus of a movie from director Sam Raimi, but it's not without a struggle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The tone is ultimately more subdued than your average superhero movie. Kudos to Raimi for making it feel justified.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's mostly enjoyable. But it's a limping effort compared with the first two. The trilogy hobbles to a finish when it should have soared.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Maguire has made Peter/Spidey all his own; the supporting characters are marvelous, but it's his brave, soulful work that pulls it all together.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I liked it. To place a sensitive story in a male-epic genre -- to dramatize feelings of angst and personal betrayal worthy of an Ingmar Bergman film, and then to dress them up in gaudy comic-book colors -- is to pull off a smartly subversive drag show.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Landis never bothers to account for the friendship that springs up spontaneously between these two antipathetic types, but then he never bothers to account for anything in this loose progression of recycled Abbott and Costello riffs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script is so patchy that most of the genuine laughs are squeezed into the first half; the rest is a rather tacky and confused extended joke about the nuclear arms race.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are seeds of something funny in the film's beginning and in its premise, but they are soon dissipated by so little sustained wit, and so much scenery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For music biz insiders, This Is Spinal Tap is a vastly amusing satire of heavy metal bands.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The material is consistently clever and funny, though ultimately the attitudes are too narrow to nourish a feature-length film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reiner's brilliantly inventive script and smart visuals avoid all the obvious pitfalls, making this one of the funniest ever films about the music business.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It stays so wickedly close to the subject that it is very nearly indistinguishable from the real thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is a composite of classic moments, all of which we sense could have happened to any of the classic heavy metal bands -- or at least to those whose members combined delusions of greatness with low I.Q.s.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This Is Spinal Tap doesn't pull punches...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The satire has a deft, wicked touch.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Only Fellini (Toby Dammit) really manages to make much of his source.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Toby Dammit] is marvelous: a short movie but a major one. The Vadim is as overdecorated and shrill as a drag ball, but still quite fun, and the Malle, based on one of Poe's best stories, is simply tedious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's nothing thrilling or new about the work here, but accomplished it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Spirit is smarter than your average cartoon because it doesn't try to joke around with a host of annoying talking animals.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's not much of a story, the whole thing's a bit superficial, and there's little to laugh at, but it's still a refreshing change from the norm.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An exciting and exquisitely rendered film in which the horse goes through as many adventures and perils as Indiana Jones on a good day.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A welcome family film that extols noble values and offers first-class animation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As animation increasingly emphasizes the computer and the cool, this is a film that takes a stand in favor of tradition and warmth.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's big action scenes ... make you forget you're even watching animation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A ripping yarn with memorable characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie that will touch the hearts of both children and adults, as well as bring audiences to the edge of their seats.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is perhaps Spirit's greatest achievement that the horses upstage the human actors, but it's also its greatest weakness. The human characters have no depth or personality, but are rather completely forgettable, stiff stereotypes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Adams' hoarse anthems become a betrayal of this horse opera's true potential; fortunately, there is enough fine achievement here to make the film worth seeing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A mishmash that is sometimes moving, sometimes absurd and most of the time just oddly off balance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Refusing to condescend to us with the usual cutesy anthropomorphic qualities often foisted on animated animals, Asbury and Cook keep matters realistic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A cartoon that's truly cinematic in scope, and a story that's compelling and heartfelt -- even if the heart belongs to a big, four-legged herbivore.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not quite as miraculous as its DreamWorks makers would have you believe, but it more than adequately fills the eyes and stirs the emotions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A beautifully rendered but unimaginatively plotted cartoon about settlers, Native Americans and the horses caught in between.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A strange, often intriguing animated film for children and young adults that takes a lot of chances and only occasionally stumbles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Uncluttered by comic supporting characters and cute sidekicks, Spirit is more pure and direct than most of the stories we see in animation -- a fable I suspect younger viewers will strongly identify with.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Original in some ways but the same old plate of fried green tomatoes in others, this Sundance Festival favorite might rate wider acclaim for its two leads if the overall tone weren't so bloodless and even dreary.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A romantic comedy that is as salty and bracing as a plunge in the surf.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although film is a bit uneven, production benefits from a tasty look, an airy tone, and a delectable, unblemished performance from Hannah.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Howard demonstrates exactly the correct soft touch, skirting the myriad problems of taste.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's too bad the relentlessly conventional minds that made this movie couldn't have made the leap from sitcom to comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Splash may feature a heroine with fins, but it's mostly a standard love story, albeit one with some delightful new twists.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its appeal is based almost entirely on regression -- a thematic regression to infancy and a stylistic regression to the most lulling kind of TV blandness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I can't imagine how the filmmakers went about it, let alone pulled the whole thing off, but their film comes together in unpredictable and remarkably pleasurable ways.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A glorious rebuke to all this summer's recycled, effects-ridden, laboriously \"fun\" Hollywood disappointments piled along the wayside like so many crashed cars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>We're constantly kept on our toes regarding issues of representation while Pekar's sour but indefatigible working-class skepticism carries us along.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hugely enjoyable and very clever portrait of Harvey Pekar.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It would be a mistake to regard American Splendor as an anthem for the common man. It is the uncommon that is being celebrated here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If Harvey Pekar is a brilliant oddity so is the movie that tells his story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pulcini and Berman have inventively rethought the notion of the biopic, and the results are audacious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reminds you that sometimes, simply getting out of bed each morning can be the most heroic of acts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The kind of movie that sticks with you for days, your admiration growing each time you remember it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An audacious mix of documentary, animation, comic and staged film that somehow finds heart and hope in the gray wash of a real life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Codirectors Shari Springer Berman and Robert Pulcini, who have three traditional documentaries on their resume, do a good job of keeping the various Harveys and Joyces from bumping into each other.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Wildly original and entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As touching as it is achingly, hilariously prickly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's an experience that's deeply human and profoundly moving.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Funny, poignant and vitally original.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The real magic of American Splendor lies in the sprightly transitions, the way it takes you from one level of reality and representation to the next without missing a beat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most amazing, colossal and fantastic comic-inspired movie in years.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Thrillingly inventive, charming when it needs to be, prickly when it has to be and, like a potter's wheel, constantly in motion as it shapes celluloid into visual art.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a humane and witty treatment of an average life that, incidentally, speaks to the worth and inherent drama of average lives.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>That rarity: a true original.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A complicated film that never really successfully yokes together the themes of money-making and sexuality, it reveals both Kazan's operatic sensibility and his inability to follow an argument rigorously through.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This Cronenbergian exploration of the perils of inter-species gene-splicing wrestles with some topical and disturbing ideas, but never quite pins them down.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[It's] witty, aware of its own craziness, and disarmingly insightful about the psychology of its characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A good horror flick always does metaphoric battle with our interior demons, and Splice summons them in impressive numbers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Daring, disturbing and deliciously twisted.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What makes Splice morally compelling isn't the bioethics quandaries it raises so much as the way it delves into parenthood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An engrossing, if flawed, techno thriller that never quite goes where expected, and that's what makes it such a pleasant surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... mining horror out of moral quandary rather than mindless slaughter, Splice occasionally achieves a terrible beauty.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A thoroughly repulsive science fiction-horror flick that slicks up its B-movie tawdriness with high-gloss production values and two otherwise classy stars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brody and Polley's performances keep the film grounded in a semblance of reality even when it threatens to go over the top near the end, and director Natali infuses the proceedings with a consistent sense of nail-biting dread.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It wants to tour the scarred human psyche, yet the cobbled-together screenplay is silly when it should be spooky, cold when it should boil over and dumb when it should be smart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though a stylish thriller with an initially palpable sense of menace and kinky tension, the story takes such ridiculous turns that it ends up undercutting its initial promise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Cronenberg influence here is evident in Mr. Natali's interest in the body and birth and in an initially subdued, near-narcoleptic atmosphere that helps build a nice sense of foreboding.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Before the film devolves into cliche, director and co-writer Vincenzo Natali creates a potent and provocative thriller about gender politics and human impulses that can't be reduced to a science.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The special effects and creature design, as good as they are, don't exceed the acting by Polley, Brody and Chaneac, who make it all seem entirely plausible and emotionally real.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Splice is a hybrid that works. It's a smart, slickly paced, well-acted science-fiction cautionary tale-horror movie-psychological drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film's deliberately provocative premise is worked out in broad, lurid comic-book strokes, consciously calculated to shock the easily shockable and titillate the peculiar.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While it's far from perfect, it's a timely and well-considered thriller about the scarier aspects of genetic engineering.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] rich and textured film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Maddeningly ruled by signposts spotted from miles away.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Features more cliches than it can comfortably handle and is not helped by its grindingly slow pacing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Strongly acted and beautifully photographed (by Virgil Mirano), \"Spoken Word\" is a quietly resonant family drama about the tug of old habits and the difficulties of escaping the past.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Shallow, melodramatic, pretentious and wildly misguided, it's also ambitious, entertaining and rather funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film becomes unintentionally funny when he falls for another hustler (Margarita Levieva) with even less conscience, their grand passion leading to ludicrous behavior and soap-opera dialogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Although Kutcher deserves some credit for trying to spread his professional wings, it quickly becomes clear that he's in over his head.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A witless homage to Shampoo and American Gigolo that's brain-dead on arrival.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its formulaic, unconvincing story adds little to the conversation about slack ambition, mutual exploitation and evolving social mores.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Props to Kutcher for going to surprising, painful places. There's something haunted in his portrayal that hits hard and sticks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film's biggest problem, though, is that it spends so much time in a vacuous Hollywood demimonde that some of the emptiness inevitably rubs off.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mostly Spread feels likes a bungled opportunity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More skin is shown in Spread than in most Hollywood movies. But despite twitches of insight into its characters and their world, Spread refuses go more than skin deep.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's hard to know where to begin on how awful this is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The pic reveals the palpable pressure to resolve matters pressing heavily on a screenwriter who opted for an unsatisfactory shortcut to an ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For this kind of film to work it's necessary to like or at least feel sympathy for the characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Is there anything soggier than a cad redeemed?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Spread becomes a sloggy, tepid comeuppance tale.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The performances are the biggest asset.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I'll admit the main story is implausible, but the flashbacks were spectacular, and the cast is really good here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's clever and shows great control of craft, but it doesn't care, and so it's hard for us to care about.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A yawn, and the two glamour boys (who, by the way, look awful) are both snoring.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Happily, beneath the film's nostalgic veneer and tooth-rattling visual and aural effects lies a mature ambiguity that's unusual for a holiday blockbuster.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Redford dazzles in his best role in decades.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An engrossing, tough-minded drama about the slippery morality of espionage and the harrowing decisions agents must make to serve the greater good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It trades in the kinds of shadings and moral quandaries that have been meat and drink to Le Carre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Scott films every scene, no matter how routine, as if he's covering the launch of a nuclear missile.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Spy Game is never boring and rarely predictable except in its broad, overall us-versus-them outline.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With its cast of back-stabbing functionaries and desk jockeys, Spy Game makes the sport and hard work of espionage seem chillingly real.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A taut, timely and intelligent thriller with cloak-and-swaggering performances from Robert Redford and Brad Pitt.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you can't find a copy of Condor, you can learn everything you probably need to know about espionage by pairing Spy Game with Spy Kids.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Scott, who's made numerous big-star action movies, brings some unexpected humor and elegance to this otherwise predictable film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A glossy, suffocatingly predictable star vehicle for Robert Redford and Brad Pitt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The picture that will test the durability of Leslie Nielsen's lowbrow franchise, Spy Hard sticks closely to the Naked Gun formula. Not only is the formula itself wearing thin, but the gags themselves feel recycled.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like Hot Shots! there's the same mistaken belief that simply tagging other films will be intrinsically funny...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie unfortunately wastes a perfectly promising idea -- satirizing James Bond films along with any other pop-culture celluloid phenomenon that crosses the filmmakers' minds.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A dreadfully unfunny comedy that takes Naked Gun-like sketches and rehashes them without a whit of style or energy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You won't laugh hard at Spy Hard. And that's not because the jokes aren't funny. Most of them aren't even jokes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fulfills kids' empowerment fantasies and features enough techno-wizardry and cool f/x to satisfy those weaned on videogames.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In terms of its family ethos, this makes an interesting comparison with the Addams Family films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a piece of almost dadaist filmmaking, Spy Kids is great fun with its continual spirit of invention.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fine, relatively non-violent example of pure family entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A good live-action children's movie -- a species so rare that many presumed it extinct.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the best kids movies in years.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's entertaining and inoffensive, a rare combination in kids' films, which are usually neither.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A virtual eruption of special effects and sorcery, borrows a little here and a little there from a lot of espionage thrillers, which may amuse parents.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Enjoyable and charming if overactive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Doesn't feel like it rolled off a studio assembly line.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The adventures of the Cortez family have a casual multicultural feel that is welcome.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A winner.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A treasure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Just wacky enough and gadget-driven enough to appeal to bored kids looking for fresh energies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Energetic and slickly done, but also somewhat soulless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This surprisingly entertaining movie turns the adults into kids and the kids into adults -- and everyone laughs at the talking toilet.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Spy Kids may have its faults, but, for adults, it's far from a Mission: Unwatchable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The kids' movie kids have been waiting for.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez seems to be trying too hard to cram in too much - more gadgets, more characters, more noise, more color. But bigger, brighter and faster isn't necessarily better.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez seems to have forgotten that making a spectacle is not the same thing as creating a sense of wonder.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I didn't like the first one enough to recommend it. I liked this one even less.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Given the appeal of his first movie, Rodriguez had a big act to follow. Spy Kids ' progeny, though slightly lacking in the warmth of the first, should no doubt please audiences.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's enough here to keep the sequel rocking, providing you can leave the adult in you at the door.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Robert Rodriguez has once again caught lightning in a bottle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Manages to be wholesome and subversive at the same time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The continued good chemistry between Carmen and Juni is what keeps this slightly disappointing sequel going, with enough amusing banter -- blessedly curse-free -- to keep both kids and parents entertained.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To the delight of gadgetheads and the dismay of the rest of us, Spy Kids' paraphernalia is better developed and considerably more fun than its story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The imagery snaps and pops with such jumpy, carefree energy that the movie seems to be making itself up as it goes along.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I like the movie, but hate its presentation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[I]t's not really a movie, it's a video game that doesn't work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie that aims for the fun and sensation of being inside a video game, but not a whole lot more.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Differs from its predecessors in some important -- and occasionally unfortunate -- ways.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This third installment follows up on the thrills and dazzling visuals that charmed audiences in the first film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez may have overreached his abilities with this film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For those who like a plot along with their car races and lava surfing, it's game over, quickly.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Starts off with a burst of energy but becomes tedious midway through.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>IMAX this isn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is really just an excuse for blink-and -you'll-miss -them appearances by characters from the previous two films.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story is tedious, and the dialogue can sound hokey to adult ears.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While there's a certain rough charm to the handmade virtual reality world [Rodriguez] creates, the movie still has the undeniable drawback that it causes a headache.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez's family franchise about underage secret agents limps into its fourth installment with shiny CGI and frequent fart jokes to hold the attention spans of the underage and undemanding.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like its predecessors, a tediously cartoonish candy-colored rollercoaster.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez's various family-geared movies - notably the \"Spy Kids'' series - have been annoying creative clunkers, the one area where doing things his way has seemed like an iffy way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An endless series of scatological jokes saps the charm out of nearly every scene, and there's little effort to create an interesting mystery at the movie's center.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A pleasant time-waster kids will love with a pro-family togetherness message parents can appreciate...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This fourth \"Spy Kids\" picture isn't so much bad as it is just boring, lacking the buzz and brio of even some of the earlier entries in the series.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Feels more like straight-to-DVD filler than a chapter in one of the last decade's most entertaining and sophisticated family-film franchises.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Would have been better titled Spy Kids: All the Time Puns in the World.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The gadgets are a lot of fun, including a robot dog with more functions than a Swiss Army Knife, hilariously voiced by Ricky Gervais.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A cheap-looking, vaguely depressing echo of Robert Rodriguez's well-loved kidpic trilogy, assembled with minimal imagination or effort.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rodriguez only needs the script to take us from one gimmick to the next, and his lack of attention to it shows.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its virtues remain intact.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Directorially, production is John Ford in peak form, sustaining interest and suspense throughout, and presenting exceptional characterizations. Picture is a display of photographic grandeur.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Seen today, Stagecoach may not seem very original. That's because it influenced countless later movies in which a mixed bag of characters are thrown together by chance and forced to survive an ordeal.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Impossible to overstate the influence of Ford's magnificent film, generally considered to be the first modern Western.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>John Ford has swept aside ten years of artifice and talkie compromise and has made a motion picture that sings a song of camera.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While it sometimes lapses into pure corn, it nevertheless manages to capture the manic-depressive dormitory atmosphere of young actresses trying to make it in New York.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is funny in spots, emotionally effective occasionally, and generally brisk and entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Wyman is delightful as embryo actress but the choice femme spot goes to Dietrich.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The issues aren't satisfactorily resolved, but Hitchcock seems to be exploring the ways in which various falsehoods -- the falsehoods of acting, storytelling, and art in general -- can lead to the truth</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fairly routine thriller, noted chiefly for its cheating flashback, though with much more to enjoy than its detractors -- including Hitchcock -- make out.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One is strongly suspicious, after watching this helter-skelter film, that Mr. Hitchcock was much less interested in his over-all story than in individual scenes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As rowdily entertaining on the screen as it was on the stage.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The resulting letdown is terrific, but along the way there is some of the funniest men-at-loose-ends interplay that Wilder has ever put on film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lusty comedy-melodrama, loaded with bold, masculine humor and as much of the original's uninhibited earthiness as good taste and the Production Code permit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The good greatly outweighs the bad, particularly in the profile of Holden's character, a pragmatic, self-centered cynic whose heroism, when it is finally called upon, appears to come from deep within the barriers he has placed inside of himself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fascinating film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A cracker jack movie entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Reiner seems lost in his own cinematic wilderness -- button-down careful, almost afraid to move</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Good luck choking back the tears, folks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Scripters have written inspired dialog for this quartet of plucky boys at that hard-to-capture age when they're still young enough to get scared and yet old enough to want to sneak smokes and cuss.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is so well-observed and so energetically acted by its young cast that mawkishness is kept at bay.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rob Reiner's direction hammers in every obvious element in an obvious script.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Parents and anyone beyond adolescence will find it an intolerable attempt to cash in by imitating films they've seen before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For us grinchy adults out there without children to sedate, the whole thing feels slightly less like a movie than like the filmed record of a mutiny at a juvie talent agency.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite its absurdly optimistic title, Standing Ovation deserves a resounding chorus of boos, and maybe a few well-aimed tomatoes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Standing Ovation is an innovative film in the sense that every minute or so it comes up with a different way of being annoying.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A glittery string of backstage conventions. Backstabbing! Pushy parents! Precocious stars! Blind ambition! But if you're a tween (and don't watch Glee), the cliches will be new to you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a bubblegum mess, lacking structure, coherence,and any sense of drama. But it manages moments of daft fun, sometimes in spite of itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Thematic inconsistencies abound as Stevens aims for a tone somewhere between Grumpy Old Men, The Hangover, and Goodfellas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Some actors don't need top-shelf material. Just the pleasure of their company is enough. And so Al Pacino, Christopher Walken and Alan Arkin turn the insubstantial Stand Up Guys into solid entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's just fun to watch Pacino, Walken and Arkin work together, very much enjoying the shared experience. Seeing Stand Up Guys is an offer you could easily refuse, but hey, why fight it?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you don't think Al Pacino still has it in him, this is a welcome chance to be proved wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Is it fun? Sure, some of the time. Is it good? That's a stretch. Does it tap the potential of these three actors? Fuggedaboutit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The degree to which \"Stand Up Guys\" succeeds at all is completely dependent on Walken, who elevates everything around him by seemingly doing nothing at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fisher Stevens directed from Noah Haidle's script, which is obviously the work of a young writer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's been a long time since a movie wasted as much talent as Stand Up Guys, a film that aims to be a geezer Goodfellas but whose execution is a misfire.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Makes its way under your skin thanks to its three lead actors, all of whom have a way of bringing a uniquely weirdly spin to their not-so-tough-guy lines.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I can't argue that performers the stature of Pacino, Walken and Arkin don't deserve better material, yet it's so nice to have them onscreen together I'm in no mood to quibble.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Actor-turned-director Fisher Stevens gravely misjudges the tone - when he isn't trying to get too cute about everything, he slathers his characters in unearned sentimentality.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"Stand Up Guys\" is mostly a string of low-key, almost-amusing chats over breakfast tables and pool tables, as if just watching these actors exhale should be entertaining enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Elegiac and corny and not really convincing on any level ...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's like watching your grandfather get naked on YouTube.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In the end Stevens, probably wisely, just gets out of the way and lets the old guys have a ball.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An excruciating and melodramatic comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is a sense that everyone, this treasure trove of talent included, is waiting for something to happen, some bit of alchemy that will make the story coalesce into a whole and take it beyond the jokes about Viagra, hookers and regrets.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Arkin in particular can barely hide his lack of enthusiasm for the material. Some of the looks he shoots his co-stars appear to contain a secret code of some kind, deciphered as: 'Well, at least I'm in 'Argo.'\"</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sometimes it's all about the casting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stand Up Guys reminds you that these three are still way too good to collapse into shticky self-parody, even when they're in a movie that's practically begging them to.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The elements are in place but they don't add up to great drama in this well-meant effort to personalize the plight of illiterate people.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The ending, despite good intentions, is American cinema at its tackiest and most hollow.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's as honest and direct and entertaining as the considerable talents of everyone involved can make it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Here, in a movie less animated than a barrel of tree sloths, Ritt encourages stale performances and a pace as dull as more tree sloths.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>McAlpine may be the movie's smartest contributor. He alone seems to realize that this pedantic project will soon be graduating into home-video or classroom use.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A grave and vigorous popular entertainment, a picture that regains and sustains the filmic Force [Lucas] dreamed up a long time ago, in a movie industry that seems far, far away.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lucas is a brilliant technician but a poor philosopher, and his lurchingly thought-out rendering of futuristic politics prevents the entire series from achieving the greatness to which it aspires.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>.. even though Revenge is a better experience than Phantom Menace or Attack of the Clones, it doesn't add anything that satisfying or compelling to the big picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not far into the first third of the movie, I didn't think I was going to make it all the way through the percussive nonstop action.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lucas has woven into the action and effects a relatively thoughtful story about a young man meant for greatness but corrupted by his own fear and confusion, a story more Shakespearean than Arthurian.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you've seen the others, you'll want to see this one. Let's face it -- there's no turning back.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Just when you thought it was safe to ridicule everything Star Wars, Lucas returns from his flirtation with the Dark Side by crafting a terrific caper to his monumental series.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film that never wields the dramatic impact its plot should demand, and never realises the emotional potential at its dark heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Revenge of the Sith might be tolerable if it weren't designed to be taken seriously.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For fans it will be nirvana, and for everyone else a welcome relief.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Revenge of the Sith, it's hard not to wonder if Lucas even knows how good a movie he almost made.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas had lost his way for many years, gone to filmmaking's dark side. But now he's mustered up completely unexpected reserve for a last-minute redemption.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Revenge of the Sith overcomes its dime-store dialogue and less than convincing performances through the sheer force of its director's vision.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's better than Episode I and not quite as good as Episode II. What it isn't is a lot of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More than a first-rate wrap-up job, it stands on its own as a dazzling piece of showmanship.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Revenge of the Sith is more of the same: wildly flamboyant effects serving weak characters, bad acting and obtuse plotting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Man: 'You're so beautiful.' Woman: 'It's only because I'm so in love.' Man: 'No, it's because I'm so in love with you.' Me: 'Man oh man.'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas makes it easy to experience Star Wars: Episode III -- Revenge of the Sith as a rush of deliverance -- even if the movie itself doesn't fully deliver.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's good. I mean really good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like the star that falls to Earth near the beginning of the movie, Stardust is glittery and pretty and possesses its own pleasing-enough personality, but it won't set the world on fire.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You could call it a cousin of 'Time Bandits' or 'The Princess Bride', but it lacks the former's originality and the latter's heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Everybody has a lot of fun here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's puffed up in obvious ways but disarmingly puckish in others.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This luminous, magical movie will dazzle even the fantasy-film phobic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stardust lights up the screen with a splendid tale of heroism and romance. You don't have to be a fan of fantasies to enjoy its considerable whimsy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stardust [feels] episodic and clunky, constantly straining for the impression of overall coherent design that Gaiman renders invisible.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stardust suffers from uneven pacing and some cheesy-looking special effects. But the fine cast keeps things watchable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the special effects are at times a little more elaborate than necessary, they don't overwhelm the story's human scale.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Look deeply into Stardust and all you see is a slightly diluted Princess Bride, and a happily-ever-after you've seen a dozen times before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An overstuffed, overlong epic with a tongue-in-cheek approach that repeatedly begs unfavorable comparisons with The Princess Bride.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A kitchen-sink fantasy, in both mood and content. It is exciting, funny, adventurous, magical and very romantic. The special effects are great, but the characters are even better.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most surprising thing about Stardust is that its most winning element is neither its delightful story nor its special effects but its sly sense of humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No, Stardust isn't a children's movie. It's a movie for anyone, of any age, who believes in magic -- or wishes they did.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, putting witches in a script does not guarantee magic. Stardust simply has no sparkle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even if it is not as smart and emotionally affecting as MirrorMask it will alert moviegoers to the talent of Gaiman -- a storyteller for the ages.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>We can tell you this: Your own pure escapism is assured.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though there are laughs along the way, this is a truly mean-spirited picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With its blunt, artless angst, the picture leaves you feeling depleted, squashed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One long cry of anguish about the price of fame comes perilously close to self-pity. And self-abuse.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's the first Woody Allen film in which impotence has become the situation rather than the problem. This is a movie about a guy who has given up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Invokes the mood of an early Fellini film as it swirls through the troubled recollections of a film director, played by Mr. Allen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie Ed Wood, about the worst director of all time, was made to prepare us for Stargate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] loopy, mostly entertaining sci-fi adventure.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A cinematic fireworks show without the grand finale.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is little that is original in Starman, but at least it has chosen good models.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It isn't pleasant to watch a talented filmmaker like John Carpenter willfully distort his personality to fit a commercial (read Spielbergian) profile, and only the opening suspense-horror sequences have the weight of real involvement.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The best special effects are in the first five minutes. Thereafter, it's all rather predictable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Mr. Bridges' hands [his role] becomes the occasion for a sweetly affecting characterization -- a fine showcase for the actor's blend of grace, precision and seemingly offhanded charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Too amiable to cook up anything truly memorable...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stiller and Wilson look bewildered.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sterling supporting cast -- down to the tiniest bit parts -- provides enough astringent intelligence to make the slobbering sentimentality go down with ease.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Moves slowly and without much grace; it tries to jiggle laughs out of us instead of letting them flow freely.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is a comic-book devouring, Playboy-stashing adolescent male heart thumping rather sweetly at the core of this homage-spoof.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A scattershot cop comedy that aims its parodistic firepower not at any single target -- least of all its namesake -- but at an entire decade.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A really good not-great movie, the kind that would be classified as a guilty pleasure were it not executed with guilt-free honesty and good nature.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Forget Mel Gibson, this is the year's biggest bummer for the Jews: that their biggest box-office champ, apart from Jesus, is the image of angry impotence.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Apart from wardrobe and hair, the two heroes completely miss the spirit that made the original spark.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Starsky and Hutch is funny throughout, but with a handful of really hilarious moments of a kind that most comedies just don't deliver.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>All in all, the film has a certain authenticity, capturing the spirit of the series.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The stars give [the movie] so many knee-slapper moments you'll want to wear long thick pants to save your thighs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Probably the most enjoyable Hollywood update of a decades-old TV series since the first Brady Bunch movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This SandH is only as funny as you can imagine Stiller and Wilson being. For me, that's pretty funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The worst thing about Starsky and Hutch is how devoid of actual jokes the movie is. It's all premise, no substance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although Starsky and Hutch is a movie without a sincere moment, somehow it never seems cynical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A surprisingly funny movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An enjoyably stupid night at the movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lacks the courage of the book's fascist conclusions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lacking the sophistication of the average comic book, it compensates with panoramic attack sequences, reminiscent of the Japanese swarm attacks in American war movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A jaw-dropping experience, so rigorously one-dimensional and free from even the pretense of intelligence it's hard not to be astonished and even mesmerized by what is on the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Flawed but fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>May just be the bug movie to end all bug movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most audacious pop-cultural amalgam since Star Wars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Manages to be both fun and shocking -- sometimes in the same shot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Terrific entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Maybe the filmmakers are so lost in their slambang visual effects that they don't give a hoot about the movie's scariest implications.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Paul Verhoeven is back in his subversively nimble RoboCop groove with the uproariously cheeky Starship Troopers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The action sequences are heavily laden with special effects, but curiously joyless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Too amiable to cook up anything truly memorable...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stiller and Wilson look bewildered.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sterling supporting cast -- down to the tiniest bit parts -- provides enough astringent intelligence to make the slobbering sentimentality go down with ease.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Moves slowly and without much grace; it tries to jiggle laughs out of us instead of letting them flow freely.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is a comic-book devouring, Playboy-stashing adolescent male heart thumping rather sweetly at the core of this homage-spoof.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A scattershot cop comedy that aims its parodistic firepower not at any single target -- least of all its namesake -- but at an entire decade.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A really good not-great movie, the kind that would be classified as a guilty pleasure were it not executed with guilt-free honesty and good nature.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Forget Mel Gibson, this is the year's biggest bummer for the Jews: that their biggest box-office champ, apart from Jesus, is the image of angry impotence.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Apart from wardrobe and hair, the two heroes completely miss the spirit that made the original spark.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Starsky and Hutch is funny throughout, but with a handful of really hilarious moments of a kind that most comedies just don't deliver.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>All in all, the film has a certain authenticity, capturing the spirit of the series.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The stars give [the movie] so many knee-slapper moments you'll want to wear long thick pants to save your thighs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Probably the most enjoyable Hollywood update of a decades-old TV series since the first Brady Bunch movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This SandH is only as funny as you can imagine Stiller and Wilson being. For me, that's pretty funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The worst thing about Starsky and Hutch is how devoid of actual jokes the movie is. It's all premise, no substance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although Starsky and Hutch is a movie without a sincere moment, somehow it never seems cynical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A surprisingly funny movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An enjoyably stupid night at the movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In zooming out from Picard's glinty eyeball, this eighth feature film from the Trek factory displays a zippy new energy and a sleek, confident style fully independent of its predecessors.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>First Contact is no grab bag of camp gewgaws; it stands proud and apart, accessible even to the Trek-deficient. This old Star, it seems, has a lot of life in it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The elegance of the story is enhanced by the sure direction of Jonathan Frakes, who also plays Commander William Riker.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A smashingly exciting sci-fi adventure that ranks among the very best in the long-running Paramount franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This makes little concession to non-initiates.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The series now lacks all of its original stars and much of its earlier determination. It has morphed into something less innocent and more derivative than it used to be, something the noncultist is ever less likely to enjoy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The excitement comes from Frakes's direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A nicely constructed science-fiction film, with a simple premise, a charismatic villain and a good back-story to enhance the action.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Blessed with clever plot devices and a villainous horde that makes the once-dread Klingons seem like a race of Barneys, First Contact does everything you'd want a Star Trek film to do, and it does it with cheerfulness and style.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first stretch and the home stretch are so filled with visual interest and, more importantly, with the patented Star Trek philosophical and humorous tidbits that fans will gladly suffer the dull Borg patch for the pleasure of the rest.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While First Contact espouses the usual lofty Trek ideals, it never forgets to factor in the fun. As the Borg likes to say, resistance is futile -- and also unnecessary.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Trek: First Contact is one of the best of the eight Star Trek films: Certainly the best in its technical credits, and among the best in the ingenuity of its plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Following in the wake of a trio of disappointing features, First Contact proves to be the most entertaining Star Trek in more than a decade.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thoroughly enjoyable visit with the crew of TV's Star Trek: The Next Generation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Trek Generations has enough verve, imagination and familiarity to satisfy three decades' worth of Trekkers raised on several incarnations of the television skein.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At least the special effects and outer space vistas are more handsome than usual.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The series' dullest instalment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Generations is predictably flabby and impenetrable in places, but it has enough pomp, spectacle and high-tech small talk to keep the franchise afloat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A rich and absorbing saga.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mostly, Generations spends its running length searching for, and never completely finding, its niche.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A flawed but funky adventure involving a time warp known as the Nexus.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Here is a movie so concerned with in-jokes and updates for Trekkers that it can barely tear itself away long enough to tell a story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The meeting of Patrick Stewart's Jean Luc Picard and William Shatner's James T. Kirk is worth the price of admission or video rental: it's the clash of the titans, Shakespeare meets the Sixties.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>These are classic directorial occasions, and Nimoy rises to them with fervor, in effect beaming his film up onto a higher pictorial plane than either of its predecessors.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An emotionally satisfying science fiction adventure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Decent SFX, but a little more action wouldn't have gone amiss.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a good but not great Star Trek movie, a sort of compromise between the first two.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The humanity of the Star Trek series, unexpected as it is in a sci-fi setting, remains the series' best feature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Star Trek III' takes nearly forty minutes, much of which is filled with silly, mystical exposition about the current state of Spock's soul, before things start moving. The last twenty minutes are equally slow, but the stuff in between is quite enjoyable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is something comfortable, even old-shoeish, about the new film, a sense, appropriate to its theme of coming to terms with middle age, that all aboard are pleasurably rediscovering their best selves.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Trek II is a very satisfying space adventure, closer in spirit and format to the popular TV series than to its big-budget predecessor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If only director Nicholas Meyer had grasped the implications of his tale more fully and enthusiastically, this might have become a classic piece of cornball SF poetry, but as it stands the tepid acting and one-set claustrophobia take a heavy toll.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The net effect, between embarrassed guffaws, is incredulity: a movie at once post-TV and pre-DW Griffith.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although I liked the special effects in the first movie, they were probably not the point; fans of the TV series wanted to see their favorite characters again, and Trek II understood that desire and acted on it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Here comes a sequel that's worth its salt. The second Star Trek movie is swift, droll and adventurous, not to mention appealingly gadget-happy. It's everything the first one should have been and wasn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Trek II added hefty doses of action, adventure, and suspense, injecting life into a concept that had been left moribund by its first big-screen feature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The extravagant makeup and special effects are actually unobtrusive because they're demanded by the pleasantly formulaic story, whose conflicts--and broad, innocuous political allegory -- justify the heartwarming resolution.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Strikes a deft balance of predictable heroics and quirky humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite the usual strained stabs at topical social significance, Frakes maintains a brisk pace, staging the battle scenes with panache and undercutting the absurd techno gibberish with crass but leavening humour.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fun for most folks, heaven for Trekkers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More of the the same-old -same-old.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The latest and ninth installment in that line, Star Trek: Insurrection, lacks the adrenalized oomph of its predecessor, but no adventure of the Starship Enterprise is without its gee-whiz affability.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Inert and unconvincing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An appealing millennial throwback to the hippie dream that is part and parcel of Star Trek's utopian ethos.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story has enough plot switchbacks, space battles and gizmo wizardry to ensure that most viewers won't forget the film until at least the next morning.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In two outings as director, Jonathan Frakes has proven that he understands what makes Star Trek work on the big screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Doesn't exactly boldly go where no one has gone before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Latest excursion is warmer, wittier, more socially relevant and truer to its TV origins than prior odysseys.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I suspect the unconverted will want to be beamed up pronto.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kirk and Co return to present-day San Francisco to save the whales in the most enjoyable film of the series so far, also returning to the simplistic morality-play format that gave the original TV series its strength.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Nimoy directed this Star Trek installment, and indeed he should probably direct all of them. His technical expertise leaves much to be desired. But his sincerity is unmistakable, and it counts for a lot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is easily the most absurd of the Star Trek stories -- and yet, oddly enough, it is also the best, the funniest and the most enjoyable in simple human terms.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An effective and enjoyable sample of entertainment -- not good science fiction, but a lightweight piece of comic fantasy utilizing characters so familiar that they feel like old friends.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A happy, heartfelt chapter that reunites the original cast with the original TV format, shying away from the cold and epic scale of the preceding movie adventures.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Immensely pleasurable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reasonably entertaining if utterly familiar.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The outcome is as professionally crafted as ever, but the material feels learnt by rote.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As lo-fi as the special effects are, the folks who cobbled Nemesis together indulge the force of humanity over hardware in a way that George Lucas has long forgotten.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This tenth feature is a big deal, indeed -- at least the third-best, and maybe even a notch above the previous runner-up, Nicholas Meyer's Star Trek VI: The Undiscovered Country.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Trek: Nemesis stands alone as an engaging intergalactic thriller with a lot of spirit-and some rousing action scenes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is the fourth film to feature the Next Generation crew, and everyone is still off-track after the ideologically unsound, sparsely entertaining Insurrection.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cheesiness so endemic to the Star Trek franchise ... is back in full force.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An ordeal for all save the most ardent Treksters.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stewart instead lends integrity and wry stoicism to Nemesis, but the movie is unworthy of him.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the movie itself wanders off-course halfway through, the coming attractions -- showcasing Nemesis' jacked-up special effects, production values and camerawork -- were a knockout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Surprisingly, considering that Baird is a former film editor, the movie is rather choppy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Devotees of Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan will feel a nagging sense of deja vu, and the grandeur of the best Next Generation episodes is lacking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Trek: Nemesis spins a fascinating and, finally, quite moving variation on an old saw: You're your own worst enemy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nemesis suffers from a paunchy midsection, several plodding action sequences and a wickedly undramatic central theme.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Star Trek was kind of terrific once, but now it is a copy of a copy of a copy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too much of Nemesis has a tired, talky feel.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>May satisfy the faithful but can leave the casual moviegoer feeling as if he's walked into a bar where nobody knows his name.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A plodding if mildly entertaining sci-fi adventure that plays more like an extended television episode than a full-length film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nothing but a long day's journey into ennui.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The expensive effects (under supervision of Douglas Trumbull) are the secret of this film, and the amazing wizardry throughout would appear to justify the whopping budget.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For non-addicts, the smart plot and effects go some way towards compensating for the plastic characters and costumes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Weighed down by a midsection even flabbier than the long-in-the-tooth cast, director Nicholas Meyer still delivers enough of what Trek auds hunger for to justify the trek to the local multiplex.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though patchy, this is a lot more fun than the disastrous Star Trek V.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The principals' enthusiasm for their material has never seemed to fade. If anything, that enthusiasm grows more appealingly nutty with time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director/coscripter Nicholas Meyer moves this vehicle efficiently. He employs some tremendous visuals.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If, indeed, Star Trek VI turns out to be the last of the series, it couldn't have made a more felicitous or more satisfying exit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a movie that begins with such promise, The Undiscovered Country ends with a whimper.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>William Shatner's inauspicious feature directing debut is a double letdown.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[The] special effects, despite the hefty budget, look strictly bargain basement.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plot, about a quest for the Ultimate Answer, resembles something Douglas Adams would have thrown in the bin.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Captain Kirk and his crew go where too many film makers have too often gone before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bloated, bombastic and maddeningly pretentious.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The whole point of the movie has something to do with the search for God and Eden, but the theme is presented in the most mundane fashion imaginable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A snoozola of astronomic proportions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Of all of the Star Trek movies, this is the worst.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A grave and vigorous popular entertainment, a picture that regains and sustains the filmic Force [Lucas] dreamed up a long time ago, in a movie industry that seems far, far away.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lucas is a brilliant technician but a poor philosopher, and his lurchingly thought-out rendering of futuristic politics prevents the entire series from achieving the greatness to which it aspires.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>.. even though Revenge is a better experience than Phantom Menace or Attack of the Clones, it doesn't add anything that satisfying or compelling to the big picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not far into the first third of the movie, I didn't think I was going to make it all the way through the percussive nonstop action.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lucas has woven into the action and effects a relatively thoughtful story about a young man meant for greatness but corrupted by his own fear and confusion, a story more Shakespearean than Arthurian.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you've seen the others, you'll want to see this one. Let's face it -- there's no turning back.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Just when you thought it was safe to ridicule everything Star Wars, Lucas returns from his flirtation with the Dark Side by crafting a terrific caper to his monumental series.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film that never wields the dramatic impact its plot should demand, and never realises the emotional potential at its dark heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Revenge of the Sith might be tolerable if it weren't designed to be taken seriously.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For fans it will be nirvana, and for everyone else a welcome relief.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Revenge of the Sith, it's hard not to wonder if Lucas even knows how good a movie he almost made.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas had lost his way for many years, gone to filmmaking's dark side. But now he's mustered up completely unexpected reserve for a last-minute redemption.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Revenge of the Sith overcomes its dime-store dialogue and less than convincing performances through the sheer force of its director's vision.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's better than Episode I and not quite as good as Episode II. What it isn't is a lot of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More than a first-rate wrap-up job, it stands on its own as a dazzling piece of showmanship.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Revenge of the Sith is more of the same: wildly flamboyant effects serving weak characters, bad acting and obtuse plotting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Man: 'You're so beautiful.' Woman: 'It's only because I'm so in love.' Man: 'No, it's because I'm so in love with you.' Me: 'Man oh man.'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas makes it easy to experience Star Wars: Episode III -- Revenge of the Sith as a rush of deliverance -- even if the movie itself doesn't fully deliver.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's good. I mean really good.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This time the exposition is so thick that everyone except acolytes may tune out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Christensen is a winning mix of sultry and sulky as the now older Anakin, while McGregor is finally beginning to relax as the mentor who understandably refuses to treat his moody pupil like a grown-up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lucas has never been able to conjure another Han Solo, a character who could, with simply a wink, remind us that this was just an overgrown Saturday afternoon serial.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A commendable example of the sort of movie we once loved and then outgrew.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The scale of the enterprise is thrilling; it's too bad the movie is so muddled on so many different levels.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Phantom Menace and Attack of the Clones have reduced the franchise to, well, a franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hold on to your No-Doz: Another Star Wars is here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This film is too busy hitting all of its assigned marks to take on any life of its own.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unlike the first Star Wars, made for a general audience in search of a good time, Attack of the Clones is pitched to a cult audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Attack of the Clones is like getting rapped on the head with a rubber mallet -- no lasting damage (I pray and hope), but bad enough to bring on an acute bout of dizziness and disorientation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Yes, Episode II is beautifully rendered and better than the last. It's also duller than Tatooine's desert landscape until the last half-hour.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Takes itself on a dazzling, digital tear.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To borrow from Yoda-speak: Much to desire we still have.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's too long, it's too dull, it's too lame.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By going forward into the past to create a 'prequel' trilogy, Lucas has trapped himself in a fundamentally anticlimactic venture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Instead of zesty and daring, Attack of the Clones is often labored and stiff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a fantasy with no poetry in it, which explains why barely a frame of it stuck with me after I left the theater.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Clones is more star chores than Star Wars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At its best, it recaptures the sense of fun we got from the first movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Will it win new Star Wars acolytes? Probably not. Will it please Star Wars loyalists? Without a doubt.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A grave and vigorous popular entertainment, a picture that regains and sustains the filmic Force [Lucas] dreamed up a long time ago, in a movie industry that seems far, far away.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lucas is a brilliant technician but a poor philosopher, and his lurchingly thought-out rendering of futuristic politics prevents the entire series from achieving the greatness to which it aspires.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>.. even though Revenge is a better experience than Phantom Menace or Attack of the Clones, it doesn't add anything that satisfying or compelling to the big picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not far into the first third of the movie, I didn't think I was going to make it all the way through the percussive nonstop action.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lucas has woven into the action and effects a relatively thoughtful story about a young man meant for greatness but corrupted by his own fear and confusion, a story more Shakespearean than Arthurian.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you've seen the others, you'll want to see this one. Let's face it -- there's no turning back.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Just when you thought it was safe to ridicule everything Star Wars, Lucas returns from his flirtation with the Dark Side by crafting a terrific caper to his monumental series.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film that never wields the dramatic impact its plot should demand, and never realises the emotional potential at its dark heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Revenge of the Sith might be tolerable if it weren't designed to be taken seriously.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For fans it will be nirvana, and for everyone else a welcome relief.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Revenge of the Sith, it's hard not to wonder if Lucas even knows how good a movie he almost made.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas had lost his way for many years, gone to filmmaking's dark side. But now he's mustered up completely unexpected reserve for a last-minute redemption.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Revenge of the Sith overcomes its dime-store dialogue and less than convincing performances through the sheer force of its director's vision.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's better than Episode I and not quite as good as Episode II. What it isn't is a lot of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More than a first-rate wrap-up job, it stands on its own as a dazzling piece of showmanship.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Revenge of the Sith is more of the same: wildly flamboyant effects serving weak characters, bad acting and obtuse plotting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Man: 'You're so beautiful.' Woman: 'It's only because I'm so in love.' Man: 'No, it's because I'm so in love with you.' Me: 'Man oh man.'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas makes it easy to experience Star Wars: Episode III -- Revenge of the Sith as a rush of deliverance -- even if the movie itself doesn't fully deliver.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's good. I mean really good.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You realize how much humor Harrison Ford brought to things; without him, at times the movie itself feels frozen in Carbonite.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Charmless, sexless, passionless and robot-humoured, it's preposterously uninvolving.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are no romance, no humor, ultimately nobody to care about in this oddly sterile movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is nothing in this noisy, overdesigned bore to equal the excitement generated by the mere idea of the trailer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too bad writer-director Lucas left out the gee-whiz enthusiasm of the original movies. He also left out memorable characters. He left out the fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Creating a so-called modern legend, droning on about The Force and all the rest of it, is no substitute for the full engagement of our senses.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More shrewd showman than a great filmmaker, Lucas employs these effects to create a total fantasy universe.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though I've been bored senseless by the Star Wars phenomenon for over two decades, I found The Phantom Menace something of a pleasant surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An absolute disaster!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Incomplete, but still fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This film has a strange air of nada about it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is neither captivating nor transporting, for it lacks any emotional pull, as well as the sense of wonder and awe that marks the best works of sci-fi/fantasy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is a sense of discovery in scene after scene of The Phantom Menace.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Story. Character. They used to mean something to George Lucas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Visually dazzling, inventive beyond imagining and full of resonant detail that recalls stories told or hints at those to come!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Spectacular yet remote.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A highly entertaining and visually breathtaking movie, capable at times of rocking and delighting you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's no breather in the picture, no lyricism; the only attempt at beauty is in the double sunset.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>George Lucas, who made American Graffiti, has put together a sci-fi film that draws on any number of associations. Star Wars is both amazing and familiar.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A magnificent film. George Lucas set out to make the biggest possible adventure fantasy out of his memories of serials and older action epics, and he succeeded brilliantly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Has distinct limitations, but the current return to a cinema of spectacle and wonder is wholly encouraging.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is, all in all, hard to think of a place or an age group that would not respond to the enthusiastic inventiveness with which Lucas has enshrined his early loves.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lucas fills his screen with loving touches.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Compelling backstory, exciting action and pleasantly archetypal characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A dynamic entertainment, efficiently and exuberantly setting up its mythic tale of heroes and villains, rebels and rogues, princesses and monsters, good and evil.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A pop-culture landmark!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A combination of past and future, Western and space odyssey, myth and dream world, Star Wars may be the most enduring piece of escapism ever put on film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Grandiose but good-hearted epic!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like some indefatigable King of the Hill, it stands alone and triumphant, regardless of the many imitators that assail its position.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's fun and funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Twenty years later, George Lucas' loved saga of the war between good and evil in a distant galaxy returns in digitally enhanced and augmented form.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Darth Vader and his James Earl Jones voice is a bad egg no matter how much we know about his screwy upbringing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Backgrounds in some sequences are now more populated than they were, and it's fun to see all the creatures that make up the \"wretched hive of scum and villainy\" that Alec Guinness' Obi-Wan Kenobi describes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>None of these characters has any depth, and they're all treated like the fanciful props and settings!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is not as exciting as Star Wars itself, which had the advantage of novelty. But it is better and more satisfying than The Empire Strikes Back...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With its feints at horror and pathos, the third Star Wars film is the most Disney-esque in its emotional outline, yet that outline is buried beneath an obnoxiously hyped-up pace that reduces the emotions to rubble.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In scope and ambition, Jediresembles nothing so much as the next level of a computer game, with a new environment, new gadgets and new creatures.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though it looks almost too polished, a handful of eye-smacking action scenes were breakthroughs in precomputer cinematic graphics. And when the film moves, it does so with blazing energy and awesome noise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jedi may not be George Lucas's crown jewel, but his trilogy as a whole is as good as film fantasy gets.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The old Star Wars gang are back doing what they've done before, but this time with a certain evident boredom.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Has twice as many visual effects than the original first film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Marvelous!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jedi couldn't end the Star Wars trilogy on a happier note!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mark Hamill is particularly good in this film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The acting in Return of the Jedi is stronger than in the previous films.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Let's not pretend we're watching art!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Jedi is downright repetitive!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A mediocre Star Wars is better than no Star Wars at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is a huge, rousing finale that resolves all plot twists, settles all accounts, reunites old friends and sweeps to a climax that all but blows the theater apart!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In many ways the new film is a better film than Star Wars, visually more exciting, more artful and meticulous in detail.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Empire Strikes Back is a worthy sequel to Star Wars, equal in both technical mastery and characterization, suffering only from the familiarity with the effects generated in the original and imitated too much by others.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Irvin Kershner directed the actors this time around, and without the benefit of Lucas's personal affection they seem stiffer, more clenched.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An extended ricochet from one incendiary set-piece battle to another which still finds time to attend to plot, pace and character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The total effect is fast and attractive and occasionally amusing. Like a good hot dog, that's something of an achievement in a field where unpalatable junk is the rule.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is a visual extravaganza from beginning to end, one of the most visionary and inventive of all films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Empire Strikes Back is a technological triumph, a cornucopia of intergalactic tchotchkes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The balance between action and mysticism in Empire provides fascinating energy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A superior motion picture!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In the glory days of science fiction, critics wrote about the 'sense of wonder.' That's what The Empire Strikes Back creates in us</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I found myself glancing at my watch almost as often as I did when I was sitting through a truly terrible movie called The Island.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A dramatic illustration of the continued technical brilliance and leadership of the Lucas production team.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most classic in its style, design and narrative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It balances bloodshed with charm, spectacle with childlike glee. It's a near flawless movie of its kind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Genuinely powerful!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For many Star Wars fans, this second installment is the best of the George Lucas trilogy: a dark, ultimately melancholy, even philosophical episode that has no triumphant happy ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The storytelling is the series' best, with a zingy balance of drama, humor, and Deep Thoughts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This time the exposition is so thick that everyone except acolytes may tune out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Christensen is a winning mix of sultry and sulky as the now older Anakin, while McGregor is finally beginning to relax as the mentor who understandably refuses to treat his moody pupil like a grown-up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lucas has never been able to conjure another Han Solo, a character who could, with simply a wink, remind us that this was just an overgrown Saturday afternoon serial.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A commendable example of the sort of movie we once loved and then outgrew.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The scale of the enterprise is thrilling; it's too bad the movie is so muddled on so many different levels.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Phantom Menace and Attack of the Clones have reduced the franchise to, well, a franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hold on to your No-Doz: Another Star Wars is here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This film is too busy hitting all of its assigned marks to take on any life of its own.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unlike the first Star Wars, made for a general audience in search of a good time, Attack of the Clones is pitched to a cult audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Attack of the Clones is like getting rapped on the head with a rubber mallet -- no lasting damage (I pray and hope), but bad enough to bring on an acute bout of dizziness and disorientation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Yes, Episode II is beautifully rendered and better than the last. It's also duller than Tatooine's desert landscape until the last half-hour.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Takes itself on a dazzling, digital tear.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To borrow from Yoda-speak: Much to desire we still have.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's too long, it's too dull, it's too lame.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By going forward into the past to create a 'prequel' trilogy, Lucas has trapped himself in a fundamentally anticlimactic venture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Instead of zesty and daring, Attack of the Clones is often labored and stiff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a fantasy with no poetry in it, which explains why barely a frame of it stuck with me after I left the theater.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Clones is more star chores than Star Wars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At its best, it recaptures the sense of fun we got from the first movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Will it win new Star Wars acolytes? Probably not. Will it please Star Wars loyalists? Without a doubt.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A handsomely produced, mostly riveting, but ultimately overlong and overindulgent gangster picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Oldman gives an electrifying performance that both establishes a tragic, terrifying character and explains why that character's world is such a perilous place.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Penn's affecting performance, a strong and silent struggle with his warring emotions, is hard pressed to offset Oldman's shrill shenanigans.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What's best about \"State of Grace\" is what's unique to it - the twisted vision of the Oldman character, who lives in a world of evil and betrayal and has somehow thought himself around to the notion that he is doing the right thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Joanou shows signs of becoming a real director. But they're still only signs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite the cliched nature of much of the dialogue and the derivative thriller set-ups, 'State of Play' provides sufficient old-fashioned entertainment value to justify the ticket.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The three screenwriters may have been trying to work too many plot strands into two hours; in any case, State of Play is both overstuffed and inconclusive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's sentimental in all the right ways.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a former reporter and a fervent believer that we need good, independent newspapers to do their jobs keeping government and business in check, I think they got the journalism right.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I want to see more films like this.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A meandering movie that sometimes hits dead center and sometimes misfires dismally, resulting in a drama more tangled than taut.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a film in a hurry. In the scant minutes between plot twists, we get treated to bite-size nuggets of character development and a few juicy nibbles of acting from a cast almost universally committed to going large.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Giving new meaning to movie magic, those Hollywood tricksters have managed to shorten the story while slowing the pace -- all of a sudden, minutes are passing like hours.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>State of Play is bordered by the states of absurdity and cliche.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Holds together in proper, conspiracy-thriller style, providing general audiences with a few good surprises and some crackling performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>State of Play makes you wonder where we'll be in a decade; more importantly, it makes you wonder where we are now.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>State of Play does get a little creaky in its last third -- at that point it needs to be more streamlined, more concise. But Macdonald and the screenwriters manage to weave their ideas through a sturdy-enough plot, so we never feel we're being preached to</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This conspiracy thriller, starring Russell Crowe as an investigative newspaper reporter and Helen Mirren as his fire/ice editor, comes at us like the proverbial bat out of hell and keeps up a brisk rhythm built for intelligence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie doesn't quite work, but even when it's misfiring it has an old-fashioned appeal.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a handy compare-and-contrast, check out the small- and big-screen versions of State of Play. You'll see the difference between a vital work of popular art and a patched-up retread.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The chance to explore the swiftly changing culture of Web-age journalism is one of several intriguing possibilities that State of Play squanders.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Directed by Kevin Macdonald, it's a capable if convoluted 'B' movie about government corruption, with an 'A' cast furiously pounding the pavement and keyboard.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Explosions abound, along with expository dialogue and a ham-tastic triad of performances from Sam Jackson, Willem Dafoe, and Peter Strauss.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is that rare B movie that's rooted in gut-level stirrings of power and retaliation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So primitive, it must have been written in lizard blood on animal skin.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So devoid of craft, it looks as though it were filmed by robots.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A crisp adventure that grows increasingly audacious (the story climaxes with a huge battle waged in the Capitol) if only lightly enjoyable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its action scenes are too absurd and too computer-generated to produce any kind of rush. The dialogue, not just amateurish, fails even to approximate something resembling human interaction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perfectly mindless fun, where the emphasis is on the mindless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are bound to be pictures bigger, dumber and more punishing than this one released during the summer, but at least the warm weather also will bring a wider range of alternatives.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The chases, shootouts and explosions in this deafening, lamebrained wreck of a movie make the Road Runner cartoons look like National Geographic specials.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The part of me that wasn't rolling my eyes really wanted to know which media bad boy would be next in line.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Functions less as a movie than an overactive adrenal gland.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The most gratifying thing about xXx: State of the Union is that nobody wastes much time on character, motivation, plausibility, dialogue or sex -- all that slow stuff that drags down ordinary movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is just a warm-up as the summer movie season gets an early start. Big, loud and stupid, XXX: State of the Union isn't so much a sequel as a preview of coming attractions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is garbage, fun garbage at times, but action-bang trash nonetheless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A humorless foray of noise and fast-cuts signifying nothing much.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To say that Tamahori (Die Another Day) panders is to understate his capacity for bread-and-circus-style filmmaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are really only two kinds of big-budget action movies: stupid, and good and stupid. Surprisingly, XXX: State of the Union is good and stupid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A predictable hodgepodge of uninteresting psychological cat-and-mouse, dimly lighted action filmed by director Kasper Barfoed in standard-operating shaky-cam ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With Cusack's help, Barfoed holds your interest without resorting to car chases, a rarity in a contemporary thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This dreary spy drama is as flat and airless as the concrete bunker in which it unfolds.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Akerman does work hard to keep up the energy level. Cusack, though, seems bored by the superficial proceedings, which don't even offer the distraction of a real romantic connection or a suspenseful confrontation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are some decent shootouts, but the movie's strongest assets are the soulful performances ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A spell-casting mood piece that is also factually frustrating.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like Charles Foster Kane, Alexandre Stavisky is a man of intriguing parts that make up any number of wholes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a gothic backstory to all this, which makes no sense but looks pretty cool.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... while its narrative style -- elliptical, fragmented, even eccentric at times -- is ambitious and imaginative, it sometimes makes for a loss of clarity and momentum.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Videogames are no longer brainless, so why are videogame movies so slow to evolve?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An anemic attempt to update the horror genre's imperiled-teens-meet-bloodletting-uber-fiend substratum.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's unlikely that Stay Alive could ever have been a good movie in the traditional sense, but it might have been better if Bell and co-writer Matthew Peterman had done more to exploit their gaming premise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perhaps the worst horror film to not have Uwe Boll's name in the credits.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The star of Stay Alive is a cutting-edge video game, but the film still has hackneyed horror at its heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A notion of an outline of a rough draft of a killer video-game flick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Here's a movie that tries to be a video game but is less entertaining than a vending machine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a cool/potentially creepy idea only if you're in high school and goofing around with your friends at the movie theater. For everyone else, this isn't just a preposterous premise for a horror movie, it's a source of unintentional hilarity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dead on arrival.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What will terrify the audience very early on is the realization that there's better acting in the video game than on the big screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Debuting director William Brent Bell, who wrote the script with producer Matthew Peterman, keeps the pace brisk and the pot bubbling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a gothic backstory to all this, which makes no sense but looks pretty cool.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... while its narrative style -- elliptical, fragmented, even eccentric at times -- is ambitious and imaginative, it sometimes makes for a loss of clarity and momentum.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Videogames are no longer brainless, so why are videogame movies so slow to evolve?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An anemic attempt to update the horror genre's imperiled-teens-meet-bloodletting-uber-fiend substratum.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's unlikely that Stay Alive could ever have been a good movie in the traditional sense, but it might have been better if Bell and co-writer Matthew Peterman had done more to exploit their gaming premise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perhaps the worst horror film to not have Uwe Boll's name in the credits.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The star of Stay Alive is a cutting-edge video game, but the film still has hackneyed horror at its heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A notion of an outline of a rough draft of a killer video-game flick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Here's a movie that tries to be a video game but is less entertaining than a vending machine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a cool/potentially creepy idea only if you're in high school and goofing around with your friends at the movie theater. For everyone else, this isn't just a preposterous premise for a horror movie, it's a source of unintentional hilarity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dead on arrival.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What will terrify the audience very early on is the realization that there's better acting in the video game than on the big screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Debuting director William Brent Bell, who wrote the script with producer Matthew Peterman, keeps the pace brisk and the pot bubbling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Underneath it all is a lurching and poorly defined film concept.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It has its slack spells, but Rafelson's sure feel for the inexpressible subtleties of emotional relationships is evident throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is the sort of movie whose vapidity is exposed as soon as the clutter is removed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It introduces us to sharply defined, rather odd characters and then lets them mix it up. The movie is episodic, and some of the episodes are brilliant.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All could be forgiven if it weren't for the soulless overall slickness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A slick, commercial cinematic jukebox, a series of self-contained song-and-dance sequences that could be cut apart and played forever on MTV -- which is probably what will happen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A sequel with no understanding of what made its predecessor work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Overlong and overreaching.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[A] hilariously inscrutable exercise in pseudo-profundity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A civilized, mellow, and generally graceful chamber piece.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A welcome reminder of Bertolucci's directorial assurance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Bertolucci] builds an homage to beauty around a sullen void.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In contrasting the sexuality and rebellion of Lucy's generation with his own, Bertolucci clearly yearns to rekindle his creative spirit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even a lesser Bertolucci is an event, and Stealing Beauty has its charms.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie plays like the kind of line a rich older guy would lay on a teenage model, suppressing his own intelligence and irony in order to spread out before her the wonderful world he would like to give her as a gift.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It may not be epic in scale; in artistic terms, though, it's huge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What do you call a character study with shallow, sketchily-drawn characters, but a gorgeous setting? A scenery study, perhaps. Or an atmosphere study.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For all the film's missteps, there is cause to echo the uncritical compliment bestowed by the playwright (Jeremy Irons) upon the film's ingenue (Liv Tyler): 'I so enjoyed watching you.'</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Among the squandered supporting cast are Dennis Farina, Chris Penn, Megan Mullally, and Seymour Cassel.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Weird, then, how the cast play as if holding their breath for the pay cheque.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The timing in nearly every scene seems a half beat off.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Depressingly thin and exhaustingly contrived. Only masochistic moviegoers need apply.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's bland and that's the worst thing a comedy can be.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A shambling, incoherent story ... manages to abuse both Mr. Lee's good nature and his comic gift.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Chronicles lame crimes poorly imagined, unplanned, wretchedly executed, with little wit or surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Bruce McCulloch packs every scene with visual gags and his Kids in the Hall satiric touch is all over this movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealing Harvard doesn't care about cleverness, wit or any other kind of intelligent humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's not enough to say that Green isn't funny in Stealing Harvard -- that might leave the impression that Green simply isn't funny in comparison to other comedians. No, it's bigger than that.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealing Harvard is evidence that the Farrelly Bros. -- Peter and Bobby -- and their brand of screen comedy are wheezing to an end, along with Green's half-hearted movie career.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Put Tom Green in enough movies, and eventually something funny will happen. Stealing Harvard offers more evidence that this hasn't happened yet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script is stale, but the gags are downright rancid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film glorifies incompetence, in part by terrorizing you with it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealing Harvard aspires to comedic grand larceny but stands convicted of nothing more than petty theft of your time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is as lax and limp a comedy as I've seen in a while, a meander through worn-out material.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If we're going to be fighting the war on terror in perpetuity, could we at least get better movies out of it?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's not new. It's not interesting. I wish it would go away.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aiming to join the Jerry BruckheimerJerry Bruckheimer/Michael BayMichael Bay school of American movie war games, Stealth is just too dumb to make the grade.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealth manages to be so ridiculously unconvincing you think you're watching a live-action version of last year's sublime action-movie puppet satire Team America.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rob Cohen's airborne adventure Stealth commits the cardinal sin for an action movie: It's very, very dull.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No matter how hard Cohen flogs it, whips it, beats it, shakes it, kicks it and prods it with a sharp stick, Stealth, his latest, just doesn't spring to life.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Harsh and tasteless, it doesn't even qualify as a popcorn movie. Popcorn, at least, has some taste to it, and a certain airiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealth succeeds in satisfying a dozen different pubescent fantasies while simultaneously violating every aspect of logic and good taste.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Beyond mind-numbing explosions, Stealth's effects are good, especially the whooshing flight scenes. But as Eddie shows, humanity matters, and computer wizardry won't fill an empty plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Cohen is no stranger to cornball excess but Stealth is his chef-d'oeuvre, a movie so audaciously preposterous and jingoistic it plays like a parody of the genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Stealth] is the filmic embodiment of all that is indulgent, gratuitous and downright dumb in pop culture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealth doesn't so much crash and burn as just fly and fade into its CGI-created sunset.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hollywood hokum? Absolutely. Pop-culture propaganda? Perhaps. Yet Stealth goes beyond feeding our popcorn proclivities.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealth is a pretty fair military-hardware action movie until you start thinking about it -- at which point it turns incredibly sour in your mouth.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealth is so over-painted with CGI that it doesn't look as real as the sequence starring Shepard that inspired it in The Right Stuff, a movie made with model airplanes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The latest and, in many ways, most preposterous hunk of big-screen action to come out of Hollywood in some time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stealth is flimsy and forgettable, but it does have a few worthy action and special-effects sequences.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Unremittingly juvenile and irredeemably funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite some obvious flaws, 'Step Brothers' remains a hugely enjoyable, well-constructed slice of lowbrow Saturday night entertainment, leaving Ferrell's position as the reigning king of US comedy secure for a while longer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Don't watch it on an airplane, don't check it out on cable, don't walk past the bargain basement bin where it's been sold.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brideshead Revisited, it turns out, deserves a revisit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a good subject for satire here, the extended adolescence of American kids. But satire presupposes maturity, or at least some perspective.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The concept is inherently funny, but the plot grows thin and the laughs grow fewer once the premise is established.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie of unrelenting idiocy featuring boorish behaviour, unrealistic character development and ludicrous plotting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ferrell, the Hollywood star most notorious for going naked in his movies, shows off only his belly, and that for a teasing second. For most of the rest of the time, you'll be reveling in, or enduring, one more exhibition of grown men playing children.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stupid, crude and hilarious, Step Brothers works by sneaking past our better judgment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although the comedy is a little messed-up and childish itself, it still delivers a few good laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I thought I knew funny, but I was mistaken. Before the blessed light of Step Brothers entered my life, I knew not the sweet comedic splendors of live burial, bunk-bed catastrophe or a minivan family singing 'Sweet Child O' Mine' in four-part harmony.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching people act like kids is annoying. Now everyone can join in the un-fun with Step Brothers, Will Ferrell's latest summed-up-in-one-line concept comedy that tests our patience so much more than his previous movies did.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is no plot, no sense, symmetry or structure to this train wreck.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is ultimately Ferrell and Reilly's show, and although the two actors have played plenty of stooges in the past, they've never done it with quite the same abandon they do here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you put the collected works of Will Ferrell, Adam McKay and Judd Apatow in a pot, boiled off the excess and let the remainder cool, you'd have something very much like Step Brothers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Do not go to Step Brothers looking for anything remotely meaningful, sincere or spiritually enhancing. Go for a laugh. It's got plenty of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lab-engineered weepie!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A very bland pudding!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Never feels either real enough to move us deeply or bubbly enough to make us forget our woes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>These two actresses are so galvanized and team up so well that the women's relationship soon upstages anything having to do with the man.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a film that takes valid, complex family dynamics regarding divorce, remarriage, and parenting and reduces it all to bitchy catfighting, obvious button-pushing, and tawdry cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too loud, bright and shallow for its subject!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's merely a soap opera with elevated production values and a sterling cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script is a mishmash of cliches, inferior melodrama, and howlingly embarrassing dialogue, and the director, Chris Columbus, shows no evidence that he understands the meaning of the term 'subtle'.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Who knew Sarandon's headlight eyes and Roberts' high-beam smile would complement one another so well?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While Tatum has rough charm, Dewan is more dancer than actress.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fletcher ably blends ballet and hip-hop, but the filming itself is often clumsy, and Tatum's relentless African American impersonation quickly wears out its welcome.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a movie about dancing, Step Up is pretty clumsy on its feet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Step Up may sizzle on the dance floor, but when the dancing stops, the film fizzles.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lot of movies are derivative. What makes Step Up particularly dispiriting is that it has almost nothing fresh to add.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's almost as wrong-headed as it is pre-fabricated.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Being an urban dance movie, guns make their appearance, along with every stereotype about hip-hop or the young. Don't believe the hype. Just watch them dance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast is only one of the picture's shortcomings. It has clunky dialogue, a derivative storyline and some hypocrisy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Step Up is so predictable, with every scene loudly announcing what the next one is going to show, that teens in the audience will take lots of breaks to text each other on their phones.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Step Up barely bothers to build a memorable story. Instead, the movie rests entirely on the well-sculpted shoulders of charismatic leads Channing Tatum and Jenna Dewan.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Until the movie stumbles under the weight of its noble intentions and its tediously formulaic story, it delivers a few lively, well-shot dance sequences and some winning moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aside from the dance steps, you've seen it all before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's the storytelling that keeps landing on its keister.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Any guy who sits through this date movie deserves to get to third base at least.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Step Up is about following the teen-dance movie recipe without variations, right up to the big finale. By then, Wake Up would have been a better title.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast of mostly unknown actors, who can all really move and sing, are given a story that doesn't make sense and lines that are boring at best and nonsensical at worst.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Step Up sprints over its own soggy foundation of dance movie cliches with the sheer exuberance of its propulsively cut dance sequences.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Alive with infectious rhythm, likable characters, and slick dance moves, Step Up gives cliches a good name.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The well-cast leads are more than appealing enough to encourage a rooting interest. Better still, they obviously do their own dancing, and do it very well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I can't quite recommend it, but... for a certain demographic why not.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Promises to hit all the urban-dance hallmarks with sledgehammer intensity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Only any good when people are dancing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all of its ragin' dance moves and rebellious talk, is high-spirited and harmless. An MC at one dance contest declares, \"This ain't 'High School Musical'!\" Oh, but it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Let's wait for a movie where they do get it all right: story, acting and dancing. It'll happen, just not this time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story may be old, but these kids act -- and dance -- as though they are telling it for the first time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Doesn't measure up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dance scenes feel like a diversion, since the story, acting and dialogue are sadly lacking in originality and substance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Reeks of artificiality and phoney emotion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Completely predictable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The dance has to be good because the rest of the movie is one long cliche.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As strictly formulaic as its predecessor, this installment generally gets the job done, essentially resembling a longform music video interrupted by a perfunctory plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It doesn't skimp on cool pretzel moves.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A finale has the young people all dancing in the rain. Like almost everything else about the movie, it has been done before. But it's still foot-stomping fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While Tatum has rough charm, Dewan is more dancer than actress.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fletcher ably blends ballet and hip-hop, but the filming itself is often clumsy, and Tatum's relentless African American impersonation quickly wears out its welcome.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a movie about dancing, Step Up is pretty clumsy on its feet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Step Up may sizzle on the dance floor, but when the dancing stops, the film fizzles.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lot of movies are derivative. What makes Step Up particularly dispiriting is that it has almost nothing fresh to add.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's almost as wrong-headed as it is pre-fabricated.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Being an urban dance movie, guns make their appearance, along with every stereotype about hip-hop or the young. Don't believe the hype. Just watch them dance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast is only one of the picture's shortcomings. It has clunky dialogue, a derivative storyline and some hypocrisy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Step Up is so predictable, with every scene loudly announcing what the next one is going to show, that teens in the audience will take lots of breaks to text each other on their phones.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Step Up barely bothers to build a memorable story. Instead, the movie rests entirely on the well-sculpted shoulders of charismatic leads Channing Tatum and Jenna Dewan.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Until the movie stumbles under the weight of its noble intentions and its tediously formulaic story, it delivers a few lively, well-shot dance sequences and some winning moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aside from the dance steps, you've seen it all before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's the storytelling that keeps landing on its keister.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Any guy who sits through this date movie deserves to get to third base at least.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Step Up is about following the teen-dance movie recipe without variations, right up to the big finale. By then, Wake Up would have been a better title.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast of mostly unknown actors, who can all really move and sing, are given a story that doesn't make sense and lines that are boring at best and nonsensical at worst.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Step Up sprints over its own soggy foundation of dance movie cliches with the sheer exuberance of its propulsively cut dance sequences.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Alive with infectious rhythm, likable characters, and slick dance moves, Step Up gives cliches a good name.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The well-cast leads are more than appealing enough to encourage a rooting interest. Better still, they obviously do their own dancing, and do it very well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Star Missy Peregrym shows more promise in her first feature, despite the fact that her teenage years are clearly behind her, and her charismatic screen presence enlivens an otherwise dull film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A deliriously, defiantly unfocused headrush...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I love Jeff Bridges, but watching him mumble and stumble his way through this part, I wondered if maybe he was up before a judge who gave him two choices -- jail or starring in a really bad gymnastics movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is a positive message in the film, often obscured by the bogus punk attitude.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yes, we're in the world of elite gymnastics, and Jessica Bendinger's Stick It is an enjoyable exercise in girl power.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a credit to [writer/director] Bendinger's attention to the little details that make Stick It feel so unique and entertaining -- poking fun at elite-level child athletics while still respecting its young characters and their feelings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A spirited, dizzyingly athletic movie about female rites of passage within the bitchy, competitive world of Olympics training.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, [Jessica] Bendinger's directorial debut is far more formulaic [than Bring It On].</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stick It doesn't have an original bone in its buffed body. It's been molded from all the sports-as-salvation movies that Bring It On so adroitly spoofed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stick It is a melodrama that doesn't know when to turn off the waterworks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The use of the prim but rigorous world of women's gymnastics as a setting for teen rebellion is so strained it leaves the pic's ode to personal authenticity feeling as phony as a dubious decision by a competition judge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Subversively funny ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Writer-director Jessica Bendinger, an ex-model, veteran of Sex and the City and fun girl comedies, throws away more good lines than most teen comedies can muster.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A spry teenage comedy that gets everything right, Stick It takes the usual batch of underdogs, dirt bags, mean girls and bimbos and sends them somersaulting through happy cliches and unexpected invention.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rarely is a sports movie so inept that it can't even make its central figure likable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>On every other level, the film is thoroughly ordinary, with the only distinction being Bridges' typically unaffected and engaging performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Bendinger, who wrote for rock magazine Spin, has figured out a way to salute female competition and unity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stick It uses the story of a gymnast's comeback attempt as a backdrop for overwrought visual effects, music videos, sitcom dialogue and general pandering.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are some great gymnastics stories out there. This isn't one of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Star Missy Peregrym shows more promise in her first feature, despite the fact that her teenage years are clearly behind her, and her charismatic screen presence enlivens an otherwise dull film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A deliriously, defiantly unfocused headrush...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I love Jeff Bridges, but watching him mumble and stumble his way through this part, I wondered if maybe he was up before a judge who gave him two choices -- jail or starring in a really bad gymnastics movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is a positive message in the film, often obscured by the bogus punk attitude.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yes, we're in the world of elite gymnastics, and Jessica Bendinger's Stick It is an enjoyable exercise in girl power.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a credit to [writer/director] Bendinger's attention to the little details that make Stick It feel so unique and entertaining -- poking fun at elite-level child athletics while still respecting its young characters and their feelings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A spirited, dizzyingly athletic movie about female rites of passage within the bitchy, competitive world of Olympics training.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, [Jessica] Bendinger's directorial debut is far more formulaic [than Bring It On].</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stick It doesn't have an original bone in its buffed body. It's been molded from all the sports-as-salvation movies that Bring It On so adroitly spoofed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stick It is a melodrama that doesn't know when to turn off the waterworks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The use of the prim but rigorous world of women's gymnastics as a setting for teen rebellion is so strained it leaves the pic's ode to personal authenticity feeling as phony as a dubious decision by a competition judge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Subversively funny ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Writer-director Jessica Bendinger, an ex-model, veteran of Sex and the City and fun girl comedies, throws away more good lines than most teen comedies can muster.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A spry teenage comedy that gets everything right, Stick It takes the usual batch of underdogs, dirt bags, mean girls and bimbos and sends them somersaulting through happy cliches and unexpected invention.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rarely is a sports movie so inept that it can't even make its central figure likable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>On every other level, the film is thoroughly ordinary, with the only distinction being Bridges' typically unaffected and engaging performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Bendinger, who wrote for rock magazine Spin, has figured out a way to salute female competition and unity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stick It uses the story of a gymnast's comeback attempt as a backdrop for overwrought visual effects, music videos, sitcom dialogue and general pandering.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are some great gymnastics stories out there. This isn't one of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Flimsy and often stupid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Incomprehensible!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All the Aramaic in the world can't save it from its own pounding slickness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A bloody mess!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stigmata is possibly the funniest movie ever made about Catholicism.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A derivative, pretentious rock video with a half-cocked, quote-unquote religious melodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ludicrous plot and even worse dialogue!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stigmata is an unusually intelligent and original thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unless you are an admirer of splicing, production design and cinematography, there's not much point in seeing the film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>How several good actors got talked into this movie is a mystery.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At first seems to be about the Second Coming but turns out to be a half-baked anticlerical screed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tom Lazarus and Rick Ramage should be ashamed to have written such nonsense!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story makes increasingly little sense as it unspools!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A shameless guilty pleasure!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a depth and caring to Still Breathing that you don't find in the usual major studio fare.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A light and bright romantic comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film's success ultimately rests on the couple -- and not once in this film, aside from a lot of wispy talk about fate and dreams, did I see any reason why these two opposites would be drawn to each other.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a story that has been told many times before, but generally with more energy than this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A gooey, swooning swatch of romantic hyperventilation, its queasy charms. And let it be said that surrendering to those charms could be as guilt-inducing as polishing off a pint of Haagen-Dazs chocolate ice cream before lunch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] serious, atmospheric, character-driven supernatural drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The skillful shock cuts will make you jump out of your skin, but it's the digital visualisation of the ghostly Samantha which really makes the flesh crawl.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first two-thirds of the movie is engagingly spooky, more so than The Sixth Sense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stir of Echoes is a ghost story and a pretty darn good one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stir of Echoes might have worked just fine a few decades ago, but it now seems too simply schematic to spook us as much as it wants to.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stir of Echoes gives a classic ghost story extra zip by insisting on the reality of the characters and their place.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The kind of film that may give you pause the next time you walk into a dark room by yourself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bacon should be working with a more original substance, a subject that would be truly worthy of his highly original character and his responses.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After a compelling first half, the main echoes that this ghost yarn stirs up are of other movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Koepp keeps Stir of Echoes stirring for a good hour or so but is unable to sustain the mood throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The credibility quotient gets its biggest boost from Bacon's shrewdly detailed performance!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Koepp has made an interesting but irrelevant parallel between the otherworld and movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Star Kevin Bacon is at times wildly exciting, while Kathryn Erbe, playing his character's long-suffering wife, delivers an understated but terribly interesting performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It has enough smarts to scare us, Sixth Sense or not.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stir of Echoes is studded with potent fright scenes and built on a rock-solid performance by the ever - dependable Kevin Bacon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It offers a stir of an echo of horror, rather than the genuine cathartic article.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In a taut, grippingly intense performance, Bacon captures the frenetic torment of a man driven to extremes by forces he can't begin to fathom.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>David Koepp's second outing as director elevates the horror genre with a refreshing intelligence and humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stir of Echoes is much more down and dirty, and the thrills are more visceral.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This luscious film restores the creature's nobility and gives him peace.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Overall, this Dracula could have been less heavy and more deliciously evil than it is, but it does offer a sumptuous engorgement of the senses.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A somewhat dispersed and overcrowded story line that remains fascinating and often affecting thanks to all its visual and conceptual energy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This lack of a convincing central dynamic leads to the occasional sense that the film is little more than a spectacular edifice, but you'll be too spellbound to resist seduction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With Dracula it's apparent that Mr. Coppola's talent and exuberance survive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is Coppola's most lavish and, certainly, his most flamboyant film; never before has he allowed himself this kind of mad experimentation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is an exercise in feverish excess, and for that if for little else, I enjoyed it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In Bram Stoker's Dracula, director Francis Ford Coppola wins endless vam-Pyrrhic victories but loses the narrative war.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Oldman is so vivid and funny as the cackling, centuries-old Dracula that we look forward to seeing what he'll do in the London scenes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stolen begins at overdetermined, makes a pit stop at outright sadistic and winds up in the parking garage of ridiculous even for a movie of this sort.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The deep-rooted silliness makes it hard to take anything in the film seriously. But at least it has the decency never to ask us to.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In Stolen, [Cage] steals away with nothing; he's simply stalled out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of Truffaut's best, lyrical and resonant in a way the later films in the cycle would not be.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The slice-of-life pic also has neat slices of observation, tasteful presentation and easeful acting that avoid banality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A persuasively charming comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie so full of love that to define it may make it sound like a religious experience, which, of course, it is -- but in a wonderfully unorthodox, cockeyed way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's little here for British eyes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Benign nonsense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The moves can be remarkable, though ritually repetitive -- male chorus lines of adrenalized automata acting out anger, menace, pride, audacity or joy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stomp the Yard is a strange and at times strangely compelling mix of black fraternity recruitment video and inspirational tale about a hip-hop boy in a stepping world.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perhaps director Sylvain White hoped that this laughably melodramatic film might find its way into the pantheon of urban dance films. But seen against such films as Rize and You Got Served, it's a step in the wrong direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Typical of dance movies, there's a bit of story to fill the gaps between energetic sessions of movement. Director Sylvain White captures loads of feverish step action with stylishly jittery camerawork, muted colors and claustrophobic framing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film introduces too many elements, doubles back on itself, repeats and repeats the same information, starts and stops, includes needless tangential riffs, finds artificial means to stretch the running length and is in every way a flabby mess.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script, based on an earlier screenplay by a Florida AandM alum, accomplishes little -- it's basically Drumline, with dancing instead of drum corps.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast adds little. Columbus Short, a dancer-turned-actor, can move well, but he mugs too much for the camera when he's supposed to be having fun, and barely holds the screen when he's not.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie starts with furious team dance-offs, but these aren't as interesting as they should be. Camera trickery keeps slowing down or speeding up everyone's movements, which destroys the amazement factor raised by the documentary Rize.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What we get is scene after scene of exhilarating routines, all leading up to the big finale. And with two furiously intense teams ready to dance each other off the stage, it's an absolute winner.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The performance sequences are explosively exciting, and Short's acting is almost as accomplished as his acrobatic dance routines.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's impossible not to warm up to [actor Colubmus] Short's quiet intensity, and you can't beat the ferocious performance battle that rocks the stage in the film's final showdown. Don't be surprised if you leave the theater stomping your feet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plot is stale though some of the moves are fresh in Stomp the Yard, a Flashdance-like fable about a kid from the wrong side of the tracks who brings his street-wise gangster style to the world of competitive fraternity step dancing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stomp the Yard panders to every cheap expectation. Actually, director Sylvain White goes a bit cheaper than his immediate predecessors, drawing out the low booty shots for giggle and jiggle effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Are the dancers at least amazing? It's hard to say because novice director Sylvain White never gives us a decent look at them. It's hard to see much when shots are delivered like lightning flashes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film's makers get just how rich, even ecstatic, these subcultures of movement can be. It's aggravating then, to see how easily they trip up that vitality with uninspired storytelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A nod must be given to choreographer Dave Scott, who skillfully blends the dance styles into an explosive whole. Seeing Stomp the Yard for these bits alone is well worth it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Columbus] Short, another pop choreographer, sounds like Vin Diesel, but he moves like a bee. When he dances, he makes sure every girl in the theater goes home stung.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Henriksen, as the maniacal lead biker, steals the movie from under Bosworth's nose.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The action -- especially the motorcycle chases through the marble government halls -- pack a fairly good visceral charge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Brian Bosworth's acting debut in Stone Cold carries about the same wallop The Boz did in the late stages of his very brief career in professional football.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a movie about a groundbreaking gay rebellion, Stonewall Uprising plays it much too straight.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It comes alive through the memories of those who were there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>On the one hand, Stonewall Uprising shows how far we've come toward enlightenment and tolerance since that hot June night. On the other, it reminds us that there are still many minds to change and rights to win.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film does a sturdy job of placing the clash in historical context.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stonewall Uprising is an important documentary -- and a passionate and compassionate reconstruction of the historic standoff between police and pubcrawlers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fascinating doc provides the story of this pivotal moment in gay rights.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Many witnesses offer emotional recollections of the ensuing riots, but equally powerful moments come courtesy of old footage, in which anti-gay \"experts\" expound with a confident ignorance that sounds chillingly familiar even today.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The great strength of Kate David and David Heilbroner's Stonewall Uprising is its rich context.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stonewall Uprising is first and foremost about people. Politics and history and sexuality are there, too, but they're subsidiary to the human stories the documentary tells.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cohesive, well-structured docu from veteran filmmakers Kate Davis and David Heilbroner boasts a panoply of found footage, graphically positioning the uprising as a flashpoint following decades of repression.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stonewall Uprising methodically ticks off the forms of oppression visited on gays and lesbians in the days before the gay rights movement.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This all-new assemblage of rare home-movie footage, photographs, and gripping testimony from people who were there -- including one of the cops who led the raid -- allows us to experience a landmark civil rights event in a fresh and fascinating way.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The filmmakers do a good job of laying out the whos, whys and wheres through diagrams, reenactments and testimonials from veterans on both sides of the skirmish.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The memories of those who were definitely there during those momentous days in late June are undeniably powerful... But are their voices best served by the messy documentary in which they appear?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's the film equivalent of a weary shrug - capturing the national mood at a moment when we'd all prefer some mood enhancers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stop-Loss is not a great movie, but it's forceful, effective, and alive, with the raw, mixed-up emotions produced by an endless war -- a time when the patriotism of military families is in danger of being exploited beyond endurance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The power of Stop-Loss -- and this is no dumb joke -- is that it shows its hero between Iraq and a hard place.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] very worthy film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Swamped by cliches, continuity problems, stock characters and very good intentions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stop-Loss can't quite decide whether to focus on making a powerful statement on a controversial and unfamiliar military policy or on a more predictable drama about the traumatic effect of war on young people's lives.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is a gripping but very limited view of their lives.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a nation, we owe them more than they owe us -- as this painfully necessary and heartfelt movie makes abundantly clear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though it's no Boys Don't Cry, there's something about Stop-Loss that haunts you: Peirce has an uncanny way of catching the fierce light in her actors' eyes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Clearly, Peirce's motives are pure. She's not using the 'stop-loss' issue as a wedge to make the government or the administration look bad. She's using it to dramatize an injustice and to advocate on behalf of the soldiers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While it would be premature to decorate it as the Best Years of Our Lives or Coming Home of the Surge, Stop-Loss carries the emotional force and propulsive drama of the quintessential soldier's story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are good and confident choices here, particularly in the direction, and the way it integrates the soldiers' own war movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After five years of news footage and documentaries coming from the war in Iraq, Stop-Loss is as phony as a re-enactment with finger pup pets.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Viewers of any age are bound to be moved by [director Peirce's] primary theme: that there is no easy cure for these damaged young veterans, whether they return to war or fight their demons at home.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story steers away from cliches and political polemics, maintaining a tone of unflinching emotional realism.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stop-Loss is a film that does it right.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's more a sweaty assemblage of dramatic high-points than a coherent, persuasive story of wounded warriors trying to make it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Writer/director Kimberly Peirce has clearly done her homework. What she hasn't done, at least not here, is develop any strong point of view about the war.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a keen and ugly sense of anguish to Stop-Loss, a caged sense of powerlessness beyond political outrage that makes this film far and away the most effective effort yet at capturing the frustration of the war in Iraq.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Anchored by deft performances from a sturdy ensemble, Stop-Loss provides proof of Peirce's sensitivity with actors as well as her interest in stories of American folk who don't often get the close-ups they should.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Most of the blame for this unimaginative effort can be attributed to the script, but Spottiswoode's flat direction doesn't help.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This mom is impossible without being funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is moronic beyond comprehension, an exercise in desperation during which even Sylvester Stallone, a repository of self-confidence, seems to be disheartened.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As irksome as it is, the concept is actually better for Stallone than the premises of his earlier awful romps.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pudovkin's strict, building block editing, proficient as it is, tends to cramp the film's flow and suggestive space.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Excellent photography and sterling work by the eminently suitable cast are the conspicuous assets of Vsevolod Pudovkin's silent cinematic contribution.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Story of a Love Affair is tacky.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A remarkable formal effort involving a detective, an adulterous trio, a murder plot, a choreographic mise en scene, and an extended flashback.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plotline (derived from Hamlet) soon goes flat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The price of a ticket could buy enough beer for an experience at least as memorable as this one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Kathryn Bigelow comes closer than any other filmmaker to turning movies into a virtual reality trip.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Once the premise has lost its promise, and Fiennes's brave attempts at characterization are sacrificed to pseudo-dazzle, everything appears awfully humdrum and, yes, distinctly dated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Undeniably thrilling and troubling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though the creators of Strange Days may well be interested in its dramatic and thematic elements, they do not have the same touch for these moments as they do for camera pyrotechnics.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's big, explosive entertainment and, although not directed by Cameron, is very much in the vein we've come to expect from him.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's fascinating the way Bigelow is able to suggest so much of VR's impact (and dangers) within a movie - a form of VR that's a century old.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Winds up with a scene in which a merry-go-round goes wild, spins like a pin wheel, and crashes in a gaudy blaze of explosions that no earthly carrousel could touch off. The movie itself is the same way: implausible but intriguing and great fun to ride.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Perhaps Strangers on a Train still hasn't yielded all its secrets.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hitchcock erects a web of guilt around Granger, who 'agreed' to his wife's murder, a murder that suits him very well, and structures his film around a series of set pieces, ending with a paroxysm of violence on a circus carousel.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hitchcock was above all the master of great visual set pieces, and there are several famous sequences in Strangers on a Train.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Given a good basis for a thriller in the Patricia Highsmith novel and a first-rate script, Hitchcock embroiders the plot into a gripping, palm-sweating piece of suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>...his basic premise of fear fired by menace is so thin and so utterly unconvincing that the story just does not stand.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The actors and the filmmakers all take a more restrained approach than you might expect, keeping the humor gentle, and the jokes mostly as literary as the premise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An uncommonly plastic bit of Hallmark sentiment-mongering, with exactly the kind of New Age psychobabble ending youa(TM)d expect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A film well worth seeing and savoring.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stranger Than Fiction seems like an old episode of the Twilight Zone, and the idea would have worked better as one of Rod Serling's half-hour epistles on human foibles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stranger Than Fiction is both about a novel and like a novel; you eagerly await the turning of the pages.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It doesn't coast on its premise but follows where it leads, which is into some serious territory. What might have been a joke with a tagged-on sentimental ending becomes instead a sensitive movie that affirms the value of life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Willfully eccentric, odd in tone, it is an English major's comedy, a wry exploration of plot, narrative, character and a writer's imprint on her or his work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It seems like the screenwriter may have suffered a shortage of ideas and remedied the problem by watching Charlie Kaufman films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With its musings on free will and God, the story may not be original, but caring about its hero is automatic for the audience. That's more than most movies can say.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It has a nifty premise and outstanding performances from Ferrell, as the protagonist-in-progress, and Emma Thompson, as his blocked creator.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stranger Than Fiction may not be the typical crowd-pleaser, but it's a sweet, funny, intelligent film that showcases just how much Ferrell can do, even when he's doing less.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stranger Than Fiction might be film, but it moves like a novel: a literate, unhurried tale marked by softly wrought reflections on the self-made life.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>So, in lieu of the usual cookie-cutter movie, we at least get the cookie itself, a nice-light treat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A wondrously funny modern fairy tale, Stranger than Fiction manages to blend romance, satire and fantasy into a story that's both fully satisfying and patently absurd.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A comedy that takes itself too seriously to be truly enjoyed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Director Marc] Forster's sweetly engaging concoction bends our minds without too much strain, and even those moments that feel mildly familiar never breed anything close to contempt.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Will Ferrell delivers a moving and surprisingly delicate -- though not so surprisingly funny -- turn as the lonesome bureaucrat bedeviled by a voice only he hears.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stranger Than Fiction is uptight. [Writer Zach] Helm is clearly pro-love and happy endings, but he's short on loose, fresh ideas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Besides being inventive and witty, Stranger Than Fiction is a tribute to the power of literature. But art is not its only domain. It also delves into the world of ultimate certainties: death and taxes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While Stranger Than Fiction traffics in a bit of darkly funny existential anxiety, it also finds room for romantic fantasy and sentimental uplift.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not a lot to it, certainly, but the acting and performances combine to produce an obliquely effective study of the effect of landscape upon emotion, and the wry, dry humour is often quite delicious.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No snob to low-brow ridiculousness when it's actually unexpected, I'll admit to being amused exactly once.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie is designed for an audience that likes gross-out humour and endless silliness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite the presence of funny guys such as Zahn, Garlin, Justin Long and Jonah Hill, along with veteran character actors Ernest Borgnine, Joe Don Baker and Robert Patrick, the movie fails to be even passably funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are stupid stoner comedies and then there are stupid stoner comedies that ain't funny, and the latest effluvium from Adam Sandler's Happy Madison production company is mostly a bummer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Underachieving even by the standards of stoner comedies, Strange Wilderness is so inert that it doesn't so much unreel on screen as loiter there, giggling at its own outrageousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Laughter is definitely an endangered species where Strange Wilderness is concerned.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Obviously the product of minimal effort by all parties involved, Strange Wilderness is a slovenly, slapped-together stoner comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While the central story may lack edge, 'Strawberry and Chocolate' remains an entertaining, thoughtful take on the absurdity of confusing sexuality and politics.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A routine, if rather gruesome thriller with attractive leads ducking in and out of danger.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lurie, like Peckinpah, is fascinated by the idea that the seemingly mild, non-confrontational pacifist may be the villain in all of this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Everything here plays out to the same beats and yet ultimately results in conventional revenge-minded catharsis rather than queasy ambivalence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While Lurie could have gone lighter on the symbolism, he ratchets up the tension with deft intelligence. He's not just making a thriller but a horror film, and we feel his own fear in every scene.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of those movies that sits in an armchair, smokes a pipe and reflects \"seriously\" on \"the question of violence,\" but the main reason to see it is for the hilariously nasty uses it devises for a bear trap, nail gun, etc.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lurie's smart enough to know that we're supposed to be disturbed -- and not titillated -- by the savagery the movie depicts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The new 'Straw Dogs' is one of the more brutal films in recent years.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lurie informs his movie with plenty of nods to the original and at least manages a story that will have people talking - if not about the nature of human violence, then about the grisly depiction of it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You can understand Lurie's motivation for remaking Straw Dogs, and applaud the competence of his filmmaking and casting, while at the same time lamenting what has happened to him.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[It] doesn't bring anything new to the table.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a filmmaker, Mr. Lurie cannot hope to match Peckinpah's lyricism, but he strikes a decent balance of bluntness and subtlety.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Almost succeeds as an object lesson in the difference between being a man and being a macho animal. But it fails as a gripping home-invasion thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's no matching the sinister village faces in Peckinpah's cast or the psychological acuity of his scene-making, but Lurie shows himself man enough for the material.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Most details are in place, but the technique and inspiration are missing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is like being waterboarded by liberals outside a Democratic National Committee event.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kurosawa never forgets his audience. The result is a film that's traditional yet modern, one that even includes a ball game.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It goes partway toward realizing the full effect of a stage play as a film, then botches the job by the overabundant use of film techniques, which dismember what should be an ensemble performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sure it's searing and intense, but so is a microwave oven.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Clearly, this movie is meant to be dance over story. As such, leave your brains at the door and enjoy the pretty people dancing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Deeply unoriginal yet utterly entrancing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie has vim and spark in abundance and the filmmakers are canny enough to let the cast play to their strengths.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Proving that there's no statute of limitations on lousy ideas, director Andrzej Bartkowiak's attempted franchise expansion returns to the Capcom motherlode that produced the worst movie in the entire Jean-Claude Van Damme filmography.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A long slog with little payoff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This painful background tale of the schoolgirl master of the really slow fireball attack almost makes one yearn for the days of Jean-Claude Van Damme.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Neither the best nor the worst of movies derived from videogames, Street Fighter: The Legend of Chun-Li at least gives action fans plenty to ogle besides the titular heroine (Kristin Kreuk).</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching the movie, you can't help wishing you had some buttons to press.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a movie for the overcaffeinated, undereducated teenager in all of us.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Yet another video game crashes and burns upon its translation to the big screen with this cinematic rendition of the venerable franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The fight scenes are saggy, the actors are stiff, and the sleepiness of it all is enough to make you nostalgic for the simple smackdown charms of the movie's namesake videogame.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Daddies and daughters lend a wistful emotional core to Street Fighter: The Legend of Chun-Li, an otherwise generic martial-arts movie with video-game credentials.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Proving that there's no statute of limitations on lousy ideas, director Andrzej Bartkowiak's attempted franchise expansion returns to the Capcom motherlode that produced the worst movie in the entire Jean-Claude Van Damme filmography.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A long slog with little payoff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This painful background tale of the schoolgirl master of the really slow fireball attack almost makes one yearn for the days of Jean-Claude Van Damme.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Neither the best nor the worst of movies derived from videogames, Street Fighter: The Legend of Chun-Li at least gives action fans plenty to ogle besides the titular heroine (Kristin Kreuk).</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching the movie, you can't help wishing you had some buttons to press.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is a movie for the overcaffeinated, undereducated teenager in all of us.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Yet another video game crashes and burns upon its translation to the big screen with this cinematic rendition of the venerable franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The fight scenes are saggy, the actors are stiff, and the sleepiness of it all is enough to make you nostalgic for the simple smackdown charms of the movie's namesake videogame.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Daddies and daughters lend a wistful emotional core to Street Fighter: The Legend of Chun-Li, an otherwise generic martial-arts movie with video-game credentials.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Keanu Reeves' bad-boy cop Tom Ludlow may not play by the rules, but the film sure does.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What could have been endearingly daft remains merely forgettable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's really kind of a dirty scummy piece of work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Another 'roid-raging dirty cop drama from David Ayer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[James Ellroy] writes Calvinist screeds against sin; filmmakers turn them into shoot-em-up thrillers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Street Kings wastes a moderately intriguing premise by filling it with laughably cliched dialogue, one-dimensional characters and implausible turns of events.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The potential match made in crime heaven has some admirably gritty action but suffers from first-degree obviousness and some bad dialogue that's especially painful when it comes out of Keanu Reeves.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Keanu Reeves tries his best to channel Denzel and Clint in Street Kings, a wild and woolly if also slack and silly bad-cops-kill-other-bad-cops thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like director David Ayer's previous movies (he wrote Training Day), Street Kings is about the joy of badass coppery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>After its cliched first scene Street Kings becomes an enjoyably tough, blood-splattered action drama that revolves around the one good cop at its center.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Street Kings wobbles increasingly as it runs along, beginning well, growing so-so and culminating in a preposterous here's-what-it-all-means confession by the main villain.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The picture may feel more than a little familiar, but [director] Ayer knows how to cook up intense setpieces, and Reeves keeps getting better at the weary hero role he continually gravitates toward.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you've seen Training Day, you've seen Street Kings done better.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Street Kings has hints of Training Day and the subtle aroma of L.A. Confidential, two movies concerned with the moral ambiguity and compromised honor of L.A.'s finest.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Street Kings is the cinematic equivalent of solid crime-genre fiction. It keeps the visual pages turning for a couple hours and navigates the dark corners of corruption and dishonor among men.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Director] Ayer appears to like the thrill of violence more than its philosophical underpinnings, so the movie is caught between the silly and the profound.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a lot to appreciate in Street Kings, a tight, propulsive action thriller, but there's one thing to marvel at, and that's James Ellroy's command of story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The settings are a far removed from the medieval landscapes of Ugetsu or The Life of Oharu, but Mizoguchi's focus on the plight of his women characters is as intent and heart-rending as ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The late Kenji Mizoguchi, who directed Ugetsu, failed to show as much imagination in this one as in that one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Well worth seeing, if only as a challenge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Is Morgan Freeman the greatest American actor?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Street Smart winds up being a bit too smart for its own good, but it's compelling and complex.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Schatzberg's major problems are lethargic pacing and a strained plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A clever thriller with a lot of unbelievable scenes and a sappy ending, but two wonderful performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's something about seedy undersides that brings out the best (or at least the personal) in director Jerry Schatzberg ... though his Elia Kazan social consciousness could use a little toning down.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A likable, but hardly compelling story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Roth never uses a short jab when he can take a wild swing, usually at the cold inhumanity of Soviet society.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lot of the film was shot in Brighton Beach, and looks authentic, but everything else is either synthetic or derivative, like the musical score.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a wonder nobody had thought of casting Brandauer as a boxer before -- his work is so full of devilish feints and tricky, misleading expressions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Streets of Gold starts out to make a statement about the kind of person this Russian emigre was, and it ends up using him as the backdrop for a tired Hollywood formula.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A rousing ringside drama with Austrian hunk Klaus Maria Brandauer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In many ways the new film is a better film than Star Wars, visually more exciting, more artful and meticulous in detail.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Empire Strikes Back is a worthy sequel to Star Wars, equal in both technical mastery and characterization, suffering only from the familiarity with the effects generated in the original and imitated too much by others.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Irvin Kershner directed the actors this time around, and without the benefit of Lucas's personal affection they seem stiffer, more clenched.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An extended ricochet from one incendiary set-piece battle to another which still finds time to attend to plot, pace and character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The total effect is fast and attractive and occasionally amusing. Like a good hot dog, that's something of an achievement in a field where unpalatable junk is the rule.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is a visual extravaganza from beginning to end, one of the most visionary and inventive of all films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Empire Strikes Back is a technological triumph, a cornucopia of intergalactic tchotchkes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The balance between action and mysticism in Empire provides fascinating energy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A superior motion picture!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In the glory days of science fiction, critics wrote about the 'sense of wonder.' That's what The Empire Strikes Back creates in us</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I found myself glancing at my watch almost as often as I did when I was sitting through a truly terrible movie called The Island.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A dramatic illustration of the continued technical brilliance and leadership of the Lucas production team.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most classic in its style, design and narrative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It balances bloodshed with charm, spectacle with childlike glee. It's a near flawless movie of its kind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Genuinely powerful!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For many Star Wars fans, this second installment is the best of the George Lucas trilogy: a dark, ultimately melancholy, even philosophical episode that has no triumphant happy ending.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The storytelling is the series' best, with a zingy balance of drama, humor, and Deep Thoughts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stripes will keep potential felons off the streets for two hours. Few people seem to be asking, these days, that movies do more.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The balance of the film consists of time-tested commercial material, most of which is still working fine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Reitmam] manages a reasonable success rate at pulling off the numerous verbal and sight gags with which the script is peppered.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An anarchic slob movie, a celebration of all that is irreverent, reckless, foolhardy, undisciplined, and occasionally scatological. It's a lot of fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Moore's body is in better shape than her acting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Burt Reynolds used to make movies about people's lifestyles. Now he seems more interested in making movies that fit in with his own lifestyle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a witless retread of the earlier, far funnier road-movie collaborations of Mr. Needham and Mr. Reynolds.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Among other things, Mr. Herzog visually dazzles us while he's pulling the rug from under our feet.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>We watch with a kind of fascination, because Herzog cuts loose from narrative and follows his characters through the relentless logic of their adventure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stroszek is part moral tale and part absurdist comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Colfer is still very young, but he needs to learn that \"snide\" is not a point of view.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ultimately, it all portends a much brighter future for Colfer than for Carson.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If only \"Struck by Lightning\" had a sharper, stronger perspective, it might have made more of its conceit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Except for Ms. Janney's monstrous mother and an Alzheimer's-afflicted grandmother (Polly Bergen), \"Struck by Lightning\" gives its characters no dimension.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There isn't much to say about Struck by Lightning, except that it's one of those interchangeable teen movies that lands in theaters in early January, the morgue for films nobody knows what to do with.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One can't blame Colfer for wanting to expand his range, but he's created a character who is neither hero nor villain, in a black comedy that is neither dark nor funny enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At times the film is charming against its own will, but it remains needlessly complicated and obsessed with its own mythology and metaphors.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All but the hard-core Colferphiles slink out embarrassed, feeling as confused and discombobulated as if they too just took an electric bolt to the brain.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Some charming, buzzy talents pitch in on this short little lark ...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A mediocre coming-of-age indie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Struck by Lightning means well, but its gentle dissection of high school cliques brings nothing new to the genre ...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What makes this film rise a bit above the pack is the recurring idea that everyone wants to leave their nests and fly high into the sky, but few are able.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Chris Colfer's Glee appeal is AWOL in this strained dark comedy about a high school misfit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Strident, clumsy and pointless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Strident, clumsy and pointless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Uses] class and ethnic stereotypes in support of the idea that it's best to be adopted by rich white people.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is strangely uninvolving.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The use of digital effects to create a tiny mouse hero is quite convincing, as are the talking mouths on those cats.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie casts off its charm for cheap laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Every imperious toss of Snowbell's head and twitch of his petulantly bowed mouth synchronizes so smoothly with Lane's dialogue that at times he seems remarkably close to being like a real-life talking cat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stuart Little is an exciting fantasy adventure for kids with more than enough verbal and visual wit to tickle adult funny bones.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Doesn't even get close to the spirit of White's wonder - filled but hilariously matter - of - fact story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With real heart and laughs, Stuart Little lets you forget the special effects and enjoy the show.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's nothing in Stuart Little that works on dual levels -- for both adults and children -- as is the case in the two Toy Story films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stuart Little is top-notch.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's nothing very involving about this Rob Minkoff-directed effort.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Guided by famed visual-effects supervisor John Dykstra, the folks at Sony Imageworks have created some furry fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Patronizing and predictable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The single best thing about Stuart Little is Nathan Lane.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stuart Little betrays a beloved book.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stuart Little thinks small, comes up short on charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The season's most promising family draw.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is fairly formulaic, though some of its puns and wisecracks are hilarious, especially those delivered by the Littles' lazy and cynical Persian cat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plot, however, is both shabbier and less emotionally involving than its predecessor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is all the stuff that was so watchable the first time. Done over. But at least it's nonlethal entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The world of Stuart Little is a wonderful thing to snuggle into, as full of heart and pep and innocence as the title character himself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A simple, charming little movie that's fit for both kids and parents.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This installment is a much bigger Little adventure with all the ingredients of the heartwarming original -- excitement, humor, awesome computer graphics -- thrust into high gear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Stuart is] like every beloved pet we ever wished we could talk to.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Has a lot more stupid action -- and a lot less heart -- than the character-driven original.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It reminds us that Nathan Lane is the best show stealer in show business.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like the hugely successful first film, the sequel provides pleasant, engaging if largely disposable entertainment for the general audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yes, reader, I enjoyed the movie, in its innocent way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A one-joke affair about conjoined twins that feels like it bypassed the scripting stage and was filmed directly from the pitch, the comedy remains resoundingly unfunny despite the strained efforts of stars Matt Damon and Greg Kinnear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A brilliant enactment of the comedy of denial.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Farrellys need to remember this: Sappiness is easy, comedy is hard.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stuck on You is hilarious -- but it's also sweet, in a demented sort of way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By the Farrellys' standards, Stuck on You is pretty tame, keeping the gutter humor to a minimum.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's entertaining, not groundbreaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stuck on You ... is surprisingly charming. That's right, you read 'charming.'</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A strangely lackluster, flaccid string of fitfully humorous episodes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not only is Stuck on You a hoot, but it also walks a line -- as the best Farrelly brothers movies do -- between silly farce and sweet sentimentality that artfully avoids the cloying or maudlin.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sweet movie about brotherly love that doesn't force the humour.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A seemingly endless movie strangely devoid of laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>People take comedy for granted, but to step back and think about Stuck on You is to be impressed by the invention and sheer exuberance of the picture, which isn't great but sure is enjoyable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's difficult not to like Stuck on You. Damon is truly endearing, Kinnear gives off a movie-star gleam, Mendes is light and sparkly in a rare comedic turn, and Yann Shih is a real charmer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stuck on You lacks energy, verve, and effective, laugh-generating comedy. It's the most disappointing thing to come from the brothers in years.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[The Farrelly brothers have] made a comedy close to their own not-quite- joined- at-the-hip lives but left out the funny stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ever since Mary, the Farrellys have struggled to find a more mature comedic voice. Stuck on You finds them hitting their stride, adding sentiment without compromising their quirkiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A two-hour, one-joke comedy that never gets old, Stuck on You is the most mature, consistently funny and satisfyingly sweet movie in the rollicking careers of brother filmmakers Bobby and Peter Farrelly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If the result seems less a coherent story than a two-hour pot high, Submarine is still a breakthrough combination of the feature film and art's intimacy with the unconscious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Here are all the ingredients of a novel entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The animation is imaginatively conceived, but stiffly executed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's such a wide disparity of graphic styles from sequence to sequence. Some of them, though, still look terrific.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yellow Submarine is a family movie in the truest sense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A music-based animated film for the ages.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's boggling matter-of-factness is a key to its enduring -- no, its deepening -- charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Gun-toting hotties combat assorted villains and their robot henchmen in this tawdry, repellent action fantasy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Snyder likes to think that his Russian nesting doll of a concept is enough to excuse its hollow center.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie spins out of control, until it collapses in a heap, senseless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Snyder pulverises our senses with derivative digital images and obvious musical choices. But his failure to delineate the levels of 'reality' is confusing and self-defeating.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie isn't bad in the way some incompetently made movies are bad; this is bad because there's much skill evident in a pointless endeavor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A series of extravagant computer-generated adventure scenarios linked by grim mental hospital plot, Sucker Punch represents a particularly ambitious exercise in tedium.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Zack Snyder and his production crew clearly had great fun envisioning this swords-and-corsets fantasy. Few others are likely to approach their level of enjoyment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The suckers here are the poor mugs who leave their dollars at the door. And for what? A seedy, desaturated, overstimulated simulation of a real movie. Schlock treatment for comatose gamers, and a bomb with a bright pink cherry on top.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is like an arrested adolescent's Google search run amok.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Map! Fire! Knife! Key! (Well, eat drink man woman to you too, honey.)</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If the goal was sensory overload and audience stupefaction, he has succeeded indeed. Snyder apparently is offering lobotomies to all. Step right up.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So thoroughly labored, and panders so relentlessly to adolescent attitudes and fantasies, and is so thoroughly and stridently humorless, that it kind of sucks out your soul while you're watching it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For pure filmmaking - characters taking up half the foreground in close-up while events unfold behind them, action speeding up or stopping on command, a soundtrack of classic rock remixed or redone into droning trances - it's remarkable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A surprisingly joyless mash-up of every bit of fanboy flotsam floating around in its maker's cranium.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Looks aren't everything. Case in point: Sucker Punch, a dazzling visual design that goes tone-deaf every time it opens its dumb mouth or makes claims to profundity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An indecipherable, hypocritical mess that proves you can fill a movie with scantily-clad women with big guns and it can still bore one to tears.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"Sucker Punch\" is what happens when a studio gives carte blanche to a filmmaker who has absolutely nothing original or even coherent to say.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Zombie soldiers, dragons, cyborgs, doesn't matter: Snyder is just a big boy with lots of toys. These, unfortunately, include his actresses.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>My personal rule of film enjoyment goes a little like this: you can be miserable or pointless, but you can't be both. Sucker Punch works hard to be both.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I can't be sure whether it's brilliant or idiotic, although I'm pretty confident it's both, and not always in different places or at different moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reuniting Hyams and Van Damme, director and star of Timecop, this spectacular nail-biter exploits their combined, if limited, abilities to the full.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Offers above-average pyrotechnics, a body count that steadily mounts, and plenty of hand-to-hand combat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite the elaborate stunts, go-go-go direction from Peter Hyams, plus butt-kicking and surprise goalie action from Van Damme, Death deserves the hockey-puck booby prize for...getting its jollies by putting kids in jeopardy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A treat for Jean-Claude Van Damme fans, a superior action thriller loaded with jaw-dropping stunts and special effects, and strong in production values.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sudden Death isn't about common sense. It's about the manipulation of action and special-effects sequences to create a thriller effect, and at that it's pretty good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the climactic duel atop the arena roof is patently absurd, it's also exciting as events go into sudden-death overtime, just like the game being played below.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Van Damme races against time, trying to thwart Boothe and defuse all the bombs. But in the hands of director Peter Hyams, these are just banal action-movie chores.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>About the best thing that can be said about this movie is that the action scenes, directed by Peter Hyams, are choreographed with flair. Unfortunately, the material connecting them is worthless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is viewed by many aficionados as the best of the five movies about the hard-nosed, authority-defying San Francisco cop.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the first entry in the series to have been directed by Eastwood himself, and action is put over with great force, if also with some obviousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Eastwood the star needed a hit to bolster his flagging ratings; now that he's got it, maybe Harry will be put out to stud, with his Magnum.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>To all those cowboy movies we saw in our youth, all those TV Westerns and cop dramas and war movies, Dirty Harry has brought a great simplification: A big man, a big gun, a bad guy and instant justice.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By my count, more than a dozen people are murdered on camera, about half by Miss Locke and most of the others by Mr. Eastwood. This gives them something in common as lovers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The main trouble with the picture is not its subject or its style, but its length.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast packs enough sexual ambiguity to satisfy the most rabid Williams fan (not to mention a screenplay by Gore Vidal), but Mankiewicz leaves much of the innuendo unexplored -- thankfully, perhaps.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It has some very effective moments, but on the whole it fails to move.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>On film, with Taylor as the woman who saw something nasty and Clift as the psychiatrist trying to probe her trauma, the one-act material is stretched perilously thin; but it works for Hepburn as the incarnation of civilised depravity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The main trouble with this picture is that an idea that is good for not much more than a blackout is stretched to exhausting length and, for all its fine cast and big direction, it is badly, pretentiously played.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The main trouble with the picture is not its subject or its style, but its length.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The cast packs enough sexual ambiguity to satisfy the most rabid Williams fan (not to mention a screenplay by Gore Vidal), but Mankiewicz leaves much of the innuendo unexplored -- thankfully, perhaps.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It has some very effective moments, but on the whole it fails to move.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>On film, with Taylor as the woman who saw something nasty and Clift as the psychiatrist trying to probe her trauma, the one-act material is stretched perilously thin; but it works for Hepburn as the incarnation of civilised depravity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The main trouble with this picture is that an idea that is good for not much more than a blackout is stretched to exhausting length and, for all its fine cast and big direction, it is badly, pretentiously played.</content>
</item>
</dataset>