<?xml version="1.0"?>

<dataset>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Of course, an unfunny comedy is hardly news. However, even by Tinseltown's impoverished standards, one so utterly bereft is something of a rarity, and thus perversely interesting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The best thing that can be said about the Minnesota- made comedy Sugar and Spice is that there's no reference to the fact that it was made in Minnesota.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Struggles with the existential challenge of individuating five (then six, then seven) perky white heterosexual girls wearing identical aquamarine miniskirts and halter tops.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Quite a smart little film with a surprising satirical edge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not in the same clever league as Bring It On.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's fun in its raunchy unwieldiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are mucho storytelling dodges and gaping plot holes that make Sugar barely watchable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A laugh-out-loud winter's treat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It means to be knowing and cynical but is just callow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A frothy motion picture that offers moments of guilty pleasure but isn't good enough to earn a recommendation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You get the feeling that it's bad on purpose, which makes it, given the number of teenage movies that are terrible by accident, not bad at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Amusingly subversive, thanks to sharp writing and direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>About as good as you'd expect. But never as good as you'd prefer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching a teen flick as morally bankrupt as Sugar and Spice ... you have to wonder if Hollywood is really getting the message about gratuitous film violence.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is Heathers with half the laughs and none of the edge.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A setup stretched as thinly over feature length as the average movie-bound Saturday Night Live sketch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's brightly diverting enough most of the time to get it past its shortfall.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's alive and risky and saucy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A surprising amount of the humor stems from well-drawn caricatures and cleverly seeded payoffs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sturges' dialog is trenchant, has drive, possesses crispness and gets the laughs where that is desired.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A dubious proposition, but in Sturges's hands a charming one, filled out by his unparalleled sense of eccentric character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sullivan's Travels is a gem, an almost serious comedy not taken entirely seriously, with wonderful dialogue, eccentric characterisations, and superlative performances throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>Sullivan's Travels is one of the screen's more 'significant' films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When it comes to funny business, Tollin's got game, and he makes the most of some talented supporting players on his bench.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[An] awful light drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Don't catch it. Drop it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Because I'm a baseball fan, I tend to be an easy mark for baseball-themed movies, but something as badly focused and feebly scripted as Summer Catch just makes me wish for the Fall.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Depending wholly upon the blinkered empathy of daydreamy teen viewers, a typical FPJ movie skims over character, plot, and dialogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stars Freddie Prinze Jr. (strike one), features more male virgins trying to lose it (strike two) and disses the legendary baseball league in Cape Cod, Massachusetts, by filming this mess in North Carolina (strike three).</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Will Ryan get signed by the majors? Will he win Tenley's heart? If you're even wondering, this movie's for you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>When it comes to the plot, well, there are more surprises in a box of crackerjack.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Can't decide if it wants to be a comedy or a drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A very minor but extremely pleasurable summertime dramedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A half-hearted baseball romance full of weak reminders of better films.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There aren't enough metaphors of lousy baseball play to adequately describe this lackluster summer romance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Offensively bad teen movie that makes a bore of both baseball and sex.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>...one more strikeout in a movie that's loaded with them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The interplay of Ryan's professional and romantic challenges rings true, but unfortunately the writers pile on contrivances and needless distractions that seriously diminish the film's overall effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Summer Catch is supposed to be end-of -summer fun, but it's about as fun as learning to eat your spinach.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This one, though awkward and derivative, has a modest charm and is not entirely populated with howling simians.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The wanly watchable Summer Catch ... could mark the official commencement of Prinze's Nelson-ization.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Summer Catch has neither the weight nor flying power of a softball.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The sense of fate that descends over the drama is very much Bergman's own -- cruel, distant, ultimately imponderable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It forever misses, unlike American Graffiti, the heady sexual climate of adolescence to concentrate on the circumstances of the sex act itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nostalgia is used as a distancing device -- to keep us safely insulated from the boy's immediate grief, love, and passion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like most of Lee's work, this bites off more than it can chew, but the breadth and energy are impressive.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is trashy exploitation at its clumsiest. Once more, a Spike Lee movie has been undone by the earnestness of being important.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Trouble is, the overlong narrative, however entertaining from minute to minute, is a mess.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The disappointment with Summer of Sam is not that it's exploitative; it's just difficult to figure out what it's supposed to be about.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lee is a powerful filmmaker who certainly knows how to have an impact on an audience, but those who survive his ministrations are likely to wonder if in this case the battle was worth the bruises.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lee's just not a good enough filmmaker - and finally, not smart enough - to achieve the grand statements that he's apparently after.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Messy and belligerent.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lee's biggest mistake is in the last half-hour, where he extends an already long film with a series of dialogue scenes, which appear to be variations on improv workshops between the actors.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Furiously enthralling!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The elements are there but the movie isn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Summer of Sam scatters most of its force by straying far from the compelling, plenty-complex business at hand.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Excruciatingly long and overdirected!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the closest Lee has yet come to Scorsese territory!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A ragged mess that only rarely connects with its audience or with a point.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee does a superb job!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An incoherent mess!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A terrific movie: jolting, savage, horrifically funny, nightmarishly exciting but also brainy and compassionate.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Lee could swap background with foreground, this would be a sensational film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee's best films thrum with a wound-up energy, and Summer of Sam vibrates with fear, guilt and lust.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In Summer of Sam, Spike Lee isn't interested in truth - or coherence, for that matter.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A bit bland compared to Reiner's Steve Martin comedies, but engagingly played.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mr. Harmon has an easygoing attractiveness, but neither he nor anyone else seems comfortable with the film's antic pace. And for all its busyness, this comedy has no real focus, ricocheting from character to character with wearying abandon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Here are some of Summer School's favorite things: idiocy, illiteracy, irresponsibility, drunkenness, dumbness and debauchery. Piqued?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The moral is a sweet one: If you try, you never fail. The world is graded on a curve.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A comedy so listless, leisurely and unspirited that it was an act of the will for me to care about it, even while I was watching it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film stacks up as promising entertainment -- with some reservations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Features] lovely performance from Hepburn at its centre.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The challenge thus set of making Venice the moving force in propelling the play has been met by Mr. Lean as the director with magnificent feeling and skill.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Recommended, with hesitations.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Grafting moral uplift on to a slapstick caper with mixed results, this nevertheless captures some of the giddy eccentricity of the Ealing comedies it haphazardly resembles.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Tyler Perry ever wanted to turn Dog Day Afternoon into a treacly after-school special, it would probably end up looking a lot like this.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is designed to be uplifting and inspirational, but everything about it is tired and listless. It doesn't so much make you feel the spirit as drain it out of you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie's total lack of focus and its unimpressive script should render it totally unwatchable. Weirdly, that doesn't quite happen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Your enjoyment of this movie may depend on the Tracy Morgan factor. Rarely has there been a comic who can switch from funny to unbearably grating with such speed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While we can't presume to know the Lord's mind, somewhere in the footnotes to the Ten Commandments there must be a rule about not using insipid piety to excuse incompetent comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film, written and directed by urban theater circuit playwright David E. Talbert, is far from polished, but it has a rambunctious energy that's hard to resist.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though Ice Cube and Morgan should make an ideal team, neither seems particularly comfortable grappling with Talbert's amateurish script.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ice Cube goes cold in First Sunday, a heist comedy in which the audience gets robbed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ice Cube has been taking a lot of heat in recent years for abandoning his tough guy image in exchange for Hollywood stardom, and First Sunday appears to be a compromise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Who wants reality and a hollow inspirational message after a setup promising madcap laughs?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With plot holes the size of boulders, it's a bad effort at wacky humor and schmaltzy redemption that plods and preaches gratingly.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A sorry excuse for a ghetto SOS.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It has the slapstick of a The Three Stooges short without the comic timing, the characters of \"Hot Ghetto Mess\" without the irony, and the stereotypes of Amos 'n' Andy without the wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This anemic vehicle for Ice Cube and Tracy Morgan to mug and jive through is just weak, weak stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Shrug off the recycled script and the movie's trite if uplifting, message and recognize the signs of stardom to come. It won't be too many Sundays before David E. Talbert finds his funny film niche and Katt Williams becomes a top billed star.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In First Sunday, Ice Cube departs a bit from the upright-citizen persona, playing a man driven to crime by desperate circumstances.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Katt] Williams blithely walks off with the second half of First Sunday, which more or less walks in place until he arrives.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As tired as First Sunday is, and as shamelessly as it grovels for laughs, there's a hint of sweetness, and [director] Talbert clearly has a feel for Baltimore, where most of it was affectionately shot.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This heist comedy has a hackneyed introduction, and its feel-good ending lacks credibility, but the big, funny chunk in the middle marks writer-director-producer David E. Talbert as a talent to watch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Norman Krasna's screenplay, from his Broadway legiter, doesn't really get rolling until it has virtually marked time for almost an hour, but once it gets up this head of steam the entire complexion of the picture seems to change.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Let's just say that Peter Tewksbury's direction makes the whole thing move like clockwork on the screen, where it is done in delicious Metrocolor, and that, naturally, no one gets hurt.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In the journey from stage to screen this chapter from the life of Franklin Delano Roosevelt loses none of its poignant and inspirational qualities, none of its humor and pathos.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A well-done, moving biographical film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A tour de force for Swanson and one of Wilder's better efforts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>...They rate a nod for daring, as well as credit for an all-around filmmaking job that, disregarding the unpleasant subject matter, is a standout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of Wilder's finest, and certainly the blackest of all Hollywood's scab-scratching accounts of itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Still the best Hollywood movie ever made about Hollywood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What's not recognized enough is the indelible, self-sickened performance of William Holden as Desmond's boy-toy/hired hack.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the greatest film about Hollywood ever put on celluloid by Hollywood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Remains the best drama ever made about the movies because it sees through the illusions, even if Norma doesn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While all the acting is memorable, one always thinks first and mostly of Miss Swanson, of her manifestation of consuming pride, her forlorn despair and a truly magnificent impersonation of Charlie Chaplin.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A tour de force for Swanson and one of Wilder's better efforts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>...They rate a nod for daring, as well as credit for an all-around filmmaking job that, disregarding the unpleasant subject matter, is a standout.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of Wilder's finest, and certainly the blackest of all Hollywood's scab-scratching accounts of itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Still the best Hollywood movie ever made about Hollywood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What's not recognized enough is the indelible, self-sickened performance of William Holden as Desmond's boy-toy/hired hack.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the greatest film about Hollywood ever put on celluloid by Hollywood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Remains the best drama ever made about the movies because it sees through the illusions, even if Norma doesn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While all the acting is memorable, one always thinks first and mostly of Miss Swanson, of her manifestation of consuming pride, her forlorn despair and a truly magnificent impersonation of Charlie Chaplin.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The camera fails to capture the basketball action to its best advantage, and it really isn't explained how the players become so talented so quickly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Works marvel after marvel in expressing the bewildering beauty and existential horror of being trapped inside one's own addled mind, and in allegorising the self-preserving amnesia of a broken but hopeful heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's the kind of film that could mean more to people after they've left the theater and thought about it awhile.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is little charm in the coupling and almost no erotic intimacy, just a series of nerve-racking conversational collisions.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The disappointment I felt at the end of Eternal Sunshine was almost crushing, simply because there were sections of it that were as daring in their emotional directness as anything I've seen in years.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Kaufman] clearly surpasses himself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Neither wholly cynical nor wholly romantic, Kaufman's story is a balance of smarts and sentiment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The perfect movie about love's inevitable imperfections.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Gets it more than right by stripping the science down to its laptop basics -- it's a 'simple' memory-erasing process -- and by putting greater emphasis on the humanity behind the diodes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the best movie I've seen in a decade. For once it's no hyperbole to say, 'Unforgettable!'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a scruffy, blurry puzzle to put together, and well worth the effort -- just be sure to clear a tabletop for it in your mind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The thinking is shallow. The emotions are tepid. But the creativity is dazzling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Carrey is essentially the straight man, yet he's rarely been funnier. And Winslet is perfect as the model of an unstable woman who's bad news but irresistible.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A happy collision of cutting-edge writer, stars up for a challenge and a director with a taste for the symbolic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Gondry still lags behind Jonze in rendering cohesive stories and human connection from Kaufman's adventures in self-analysis.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Audacious, thought-provoking and ruefully funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This mind-bender is both funny and touchingly romantic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The twists here are the rare sort that seem both narratively surprising and emotionally engaging, particularly the one that boxes us into this interrogative corner.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Dizzying, dazzling, smart and, most importantly, honestly struggling with the variables of love, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind is a mesmerizing mind game that still manages to find perfect pitch while pulling heartstrings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The effort can fascinate, even if the result doesn't always match.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Jeffs makes a good fist of the direction and Blunt proves that she can do comedy, but it's Adams's comforting, charismatic central turn which really gives the film its lift.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taken on its own terms, though, it's a solid indie effort with plenty of nice character strokes by screenwriter Megan Holley and razor-sharp performances by Amy Adams and Emily Blunt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sunshine Cleaning is one of those dependent independent films -- dependent on the need to be \"quirky\" yet \"heartfelt\" too, and as much a slave to the formulaic as any Hollywood product.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Adams and Blunt rise above the clunky premise and execution to once again demonstrate why they've become the go-to girls for any director seeking smart, versatile and warm-blooded talent.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its overall ability to balance humor and drama, attention to emotional detail and a few winning performances outweighs its maudlin tendencies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The irrepressible Adams puts a sunny face on a life that hasn't worked out, but that's worth the struggle in spite of it all.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sunshine Cleaning should have been a madcap comedy of the macabre, or a tangled yarn about the metaphorical biohazards of living life at the margins, but it shoots for the middle and ends up being just that: middling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sunshine Cleaning emerges as that rare American specimen -- a strong movie about women.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This one is scripted, directed and acted with grace and immaculate care.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lifted by a trio of fine performances, Sunshine Cleaning thrives on the unexpected and revels in the low-key.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Credit director Christine Jeffs and writer Megan Holley with revealing the sisters' pained back story ever so gently.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Directed by Christine Jeffs, Sunshine Cleaning has more than its share of indie cliches, but it's wonderfully cast and often a pleasure to watch.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There should be a self-healing book for film performers titled \"When Bad Scripts Happen to Good Actors.\" And the cast of Sunshine Cleaning should get a group discount.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Christine Jeffs has assembled an accomplished cast for the dramedy from screenwriter Megan Holley. They are wonderful in a film that reverberates with the tensions and comic desperation of the similarly themed Little Miss Sunshine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's an honest little movie, well written by Megan Holley, well directed by Christine Jeffs, and very well played by Amy Adams and Emily Blunt as the sisters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Adams and Blunt are a great team and provide Sunshine Cleaning with nearly all of its potency, pain and emotional payoff, as sisters trying to avoid their own tragedy while cleaning up the mess of others.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At times, the movie works, but those are the times it (and even we) forget what it's really about.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A diverting but rather pointless affair, undermined by its obsessive and clinical commitment to recreating past glories.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Spielberg and Abrams are the unwitting targets of their own irony.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A love letter to a cinematic era, before 'blockbuster' became a synonym for 'franchise' or 'tent pole.'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Remember the good old days? This is the movie you went to see on a Saturday afternoon in the good old days.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's much to like in this story of a group of young movie-makers who stumble upon an event right out of, well, the movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Abrams had stuck with the kids and cut way back on all the sci-fi hoo-ha, his film might have stood a fighting chance of being charming. Big is not always better, even when it comes to fantasies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Abrams remembers the simple rule that a majority of his contemporaries have forgotten: action and mayhem have meaning only when an audience cares about the people trapped within the maelstrom.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This may not be a children's classic that will last for generations, but it will make for a rollicking afternoon at the multiplex for kids around Joe's age.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Abrams' imitation is a shade too reverent for my taste. He lacks the subversive edge that allowed Joe Dante to bite his producer's hand and bring Gremlins to life, for example, and Abrams seems unsure just how scary he wants things to get.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This sci-fi thriller has an engrossing plot and a strong cast of fully drawn characters. There's even a sweet youthful love story. In other words, it's a summer blockbuster firing on all cylinders.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The result is a sci-fi monster movie that keeps its sense of fun and humanity. It's a valentine to a classically American genre -- the B-movie -- and a nostalgic look back on a more innocent time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This new film isn't perfect, and may not be a world-changer, but it's certainly a world-pleaser.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The worst that can be said about the film is that the characters are far more compelling than the mystery they solve.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Attempts the difficult feat of balancing self-consciousness about the olden days with wide-eyed, headlong, present-tense fun. For about an hour it succeeds marvelously. The modest letdown that follows exposes the limitations of Mr. Abrams's imagination.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Has moments of greatness, but the ending is a slight disappointment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Writer-director J.J. Abrams overloads this sci-fi adventure with so many homages to his co-producer Steven Spielberg that it plays like the elder director's greatest hits, minus his characteristic scares and sense of wonder.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What makes the film so appealing is the disconnect between what comes from the mouths of these hormone-addled pups and what's going on in their heads, where they're still clinging desperately to the innocence they're leaving behind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Cera] has some of the best comic timing of anyone working in film today, a precocious sense of the awkward pauses and misread cues in which social panic resides.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the funniest picture since Borat, and more emotionally nuanced than you would expect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Superbad' at its best goes right through knockabout to land in deliciously obscene places - notably a staggering succession of doodles in which tumescent cocks take on various extraordinary guises.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A critical mass of these kinds of flicks argues for a new subgenre: \"nerdsploitation.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Superbad': 'American Graffiti Redux,' only updated with the usual raunch and a major penis fixation</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A four-letter raunch-a-rama with a heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Contains laughs galore, so many that the last one may get in the way of next one coming. But it's also got moments where you may want to cover your eyes to shield yourself from the sheer, wince-inducing familiarity of the behaviour on display.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An avalanche of d--- jokes and strenuous slapstick.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This hormonal answer to Reefer Madness is good, wacked-out fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As coarse as the movie gets, there is always an undertone of sweetness to accompany the toilet humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even this middle-age hausfrau can appreciate the zonkered comic force behind Superbad, whose rambling plot and profane bull sessions reminded me of Danny Leiner's Harold and Kumar Go to White Castle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The writers shoot often and copiously, and they're obviously in love with their ability. Now, if they could just get some sort of focused, confident rhythm going, they might make things more satisfying for the audience as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Horny is as horny does in the sweetly absurd high school comedy Superbad.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A crazed odyssey of booze, lust, thwarted sex and undying friendship.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Superbad has raunchy charm, a fair amount of heart and a couple of nice performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You could see the same thing for free -- with higher production values and snappier dialogue -- watching X Games coverage on ESPN.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like the drive-in classics of Roger Corman and Samuel Z. Arkoff, this develops the principal characters and conflicts with just enough depth and keeps the narrative moving at a brisk pace.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Steve Boyum, a former motocross driver, hacks his racing footage to incomprehensible pieces and, from the looks of the meager, jumpy narrative, did the same to the script.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The writing is abysmal, the acting wouldn't pass muster in a high school play, and the direction by erstwhile stuntman Steve Boyum (Timecop: The Berlin Decision) is positively sleep-inducing between cycle jumps.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An example of how too much of anything will get annoying -- including VVRRRROOOOOOOMMM and flying bikes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lemon, running on empty from the starting line to the final flag.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A poor man's Lords of Dogtown.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The sport of Supercross serves as the backdrop for an excruciatingly earnest sports-themed action movie geared to speed-minded teens.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Supercross: The Movie is a full-throttle orgy of soaring bikes and revved-up engines, held together by a thin if capably acted story of sibling rivalry.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie's biggest drawback is a failure to deliver what's promised.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Instead of plot, Boyum treats us to some meaningless but incredible sights, like that of a motorcyclist and her vehicle doing a backward somersault in midair.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film whose level of imagination can be discerned right from its title.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Supercross is basically just a high-gloss delivery device for off-road racing scenes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The plot is as thin as a worn tire, despite some glimpses of insight into motorcycle racing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More like Supercross-promotion: The Movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dumb as dirt, heavy on decibels and crazed with sales plugs, Supercross: The Movie is a clunker of a youth action fable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A brand-encrusted infomercial.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Supercross racing may be an exciting spectator sport and even more rapturous for the participants, but none of that noisy exhilaration has made its way into Supercross.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In every sense, the movie feels like a pilot for a program that would follow The Mountain, that ski resort show on the WB.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Screenplay is filled with witty lines and enjoyable characters, but Jeannot Szwarc's direction is rather flat.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is one comic-book feature that doesn't fly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Most delightful of the Super-series for its good-natured disregard of narrative considerations.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Why even go to the trouble of making a movie that feels like it's laughing at itself?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Miss Slater makes a four-square heroine of unrelenting sincerity; a sturdy ingenue, she is great fun to look at but hardly a live wire.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are a few lively bits, and one joke with an edge: a slap at Stephen Hawking and his computer-drone voice. Mostly, though, this is super-lame.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a bit late in the game for Superhero Movie, which was never going to fly, and barely crawls.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It looks for all the world as if writer/director Craig Mazin took the screenplay for Spider-Man, propped it up next to his MacBook, and just went through it, inserting fart gags, pratfalls and the lamest of jokes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The very act of writing critically about Superhero inspires something of an existential crisis -- no one likely to turn out for it is reading this review, and anybody reading this review is probably not inclined to see it under any circumstances.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Puerile and idiotic it may be, but Superhero Movie is nonetheless smarter than most of its lowbrow brethren in the Hollywood sub-sub-category known as the spoof movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To call Superhero Movie a satire, or even a parody, of the genre specified in its title would be misleading, since those terms imply at least an attempt at wit. But no real mockery is intended by this mindless grab bag of slightly used gags.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By-the-numbers screen parody fails to resurrect an increasingly tired genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The gags are consistently weak.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's rather benign, actually -- never very funny, and never amusing for more than a few moments at a time, but not grating or clownish, either.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As good a matinee movie as could be imagined.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A solid, classy, cannily constructed piece of entertainment which gets down to action almost immediately.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The combination of Richard Donner's superb original casting and visual attack with Lester's wit and his ear for sound proves a pretty formidable alliance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Superman II begins in midstream, and never looks back...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Superman II is a marvelous toy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Both Kidder and Reeve shine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Putting its emphasis on broad comedy at the expense of ingenious plotting and technical wizardry, it has virtually none of the mythic or cosmic sensibility that marked its predecessors.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Enjoyable, nevertheless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a cinematic comic book, shallow, silly, filled with stunts and action, without much human interest.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Anyone who has been following the Superman saga will find this installment enjoyable enough, but some of the magic is missing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The earlier films in the series were far from perfect, but at their best they had some flair and agreeable humor, qualities this one sorely lacks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By ordinary movie standards it's awful, but fans of cinematic dementia should have fun for about half an hour.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>About as dreary as a summit conference in Belgium.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Superman series gets more and more whimsically outrageous as it goes along.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of the cheesiest movies ever made.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More sluggish than a funeral barge, cheaper than a sale at K mart, it's a nerd, it's a shame, it's Superman IV.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... while I can't call it a home run, I'll say it's a solid base hit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie may not be a single-bound building-leaper but Bryan Singer reconfigures the daddy of all comic-book sagas into something knowing, witty, and even sensitive.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>World-saving, all-powerful, hero-to-everyone stuff must be lonely work, and Singer's Superman bears the responsibility with the slightly clenched dutifulness of someone who's immortal enough to accept his destiny but human enough to suffer the weight.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Strictly for fans on school vacation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's clear that Superman Returns wants to lay claim to being a true successor to the first film, not a sequel so much as a full-blooded offspring. But these bold hopes are tempered by a risk-free strategy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Singer's first flight into Superman territory generates enough thrills to ensure a return engagement. And next time, the director may feel less compelled to reassert his famous superhero's importance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While his movie can be cumbersome, it's consistently alive, and that is saying a lot when many such productions are dead in the water, on land or in the air. Also, how can you resist the charm of a fantasy in which everyone gets his news from newspapers?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Is anyone else out there drumming their fingers waiting for the superhero craze to be over?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Superman Returns careens along at wild speeds while still stopping for thoughtful moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It delivers all the thrills, suspense and amazement fans could demand of a comic book story, leaping from scene to scene with superheroic agility.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... Superman Returns brings a richer, grander perspective to a seminal character without changing his essence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Superman Returns should swoop away with a big chunk of the summer box office, and deservedly so.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This Superman is good. Very good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It will get to you, if you can be gotten to.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie has an undercurrent of personal drama that leaves you with a lump in your throat and an urgent need to see Superman return again.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A beautifully crafted, emotionally resonant and heavily nostalgic Man of Steel guaranteed to appeal to several generations of Superman fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Wildly overproduced and derivative.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It will baffle kids, bore adolescents, and depress adults.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This film's two directors and three screenwriters have clearly tried hard to breathe life into their nonstory, to the point where the film's intensity seems more crazy than cynical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This movie, which was directed by music video whiz kids Rocky Morton and Annabel Jankel, is sweet and funny and full of bright invention. In short, it's a blast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As everyone knows, arcade-style diversions are not known for strong, original narratives or well-developed characters. In that sense, this film is worthy of its inspiration.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Murky and dull.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Often, it can be argued that there's the kernel of a good story buried somewhere in a bad screenplay. Not here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Avoid.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Goes nowhere and when it gets there, it's not anywhere.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Supernova, though predictable, isn't half bad.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A mission that should have been aborted long ago.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Looks and moves like a film whose vital organs were yanked before shooting commenced.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A crash course from the start.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's hard to watch Supernova without recalling that wonderful Israeli definition of a camel - a horse that's been assembled by a committee.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A super bore.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A decent enough thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Appears headed for a deep-space rendezvous with audience indifference.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A perfectly enjoyable sci-fi thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A Frankenstein monster, with more obvious story patches, post-dubbed exposition, and missing money shots than most straight-to-video fare.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Light on originality and low on suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A pleasant surprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Contrasting the erotic with the disgusting is usually provocative and can be funny, but not in this underdog comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A stick-figure Rembrandt that provides neither the quick surreal poke of a TV satire nor the full lustre of an actual movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Simply stated, there's not a movie's worth of story here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Superstar is considerably less fun than a marathon of Star Search episodes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>About as funny as an oozing fever blister.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The funniest SNL movie since Wayne's World.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another SNL misfire.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's really no reason for anyone to see this film except die hard Shannon fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Synonymous with crap.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Superstar may not be the most unnecessary movie of the year, but it's got to rank right up there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Superstar will rank closer to Wayne's World than It's Pat or Roxbury. In Saturday Night Live terms, that constitutes a masterpiece.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Delivers plenty of laughs and succeeds on a level that recent SNL movies didn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Silly but compellingly sweet movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sluggish and predictable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The secret of Mary Katherine's success is that she isn't afraid to risk looking foolish by trying too hard. The secret of Shannon's success is that she knows just how hard to try.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A comedy with several good laughs but no convincing cohesion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It made me yearn for the golden era of January, when Slackers was released.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The dirty jokes provide the funniest moments in this oddly sweet comedy about jokester highway patrolmen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The best thing about the movie is its personable, amusing cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's kind of sad that so many people put so much time and energy into this turkey.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Anyone who has ever been stalked on the highway by a twirling red light and a siren should find satisfaction in this send-up of state trooper foibles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] smarter and much funnier version of the old Police Academy flicks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's nothing super about Super Troopers except for those deep into the low end of the frat-house mentality that equates smart-alecky with hilarity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I can't quite recommend it -- it's too patched together -- but I almost can; it's the kind of movie that makes you want to like it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Broken Lizard has a way to go to match the absurdity and conceptual genius of Monty Python or Kids in the Hall, but Super Troopers has promising moments of oddity.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[A] hit-and- often-miss comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Compared to what tends to pass for comedies these days, this creation of the five-man sketch-comedy team billing itself as Broken Lizard actually induces chuckles at acceptable intervals, which puts it well ahead of the game.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You laugh neither with it nor at it but rather sit counting the minutes while the movie laughs, for no good reason, at itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An off-brand superhero movie, the cinematic equivalent of one of those generic breakfast cereals with a badly drawn squirrel for a mascot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The performances are plywooden, the cornball visual gags are groanworthy, and Tim Story still can't direct his way out a sack with a map.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's funnier and splashier than the original, but I still can't quite recommend it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first movie's genesis story was more fun than the perfunctory doomsday scheme trotted out here.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you swept the cosmic dust of the superhero boom into a flimsy dustpan, you'd have the Fantastic Four franchise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer is more ambitious than its predecessor. It's also more cluttered and less fleet: The light, pleasingly casual quality of the first picture has evolved into something forced and metallic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer is a vast and significant improvement -- if not quite \"fantastic,\" then the next best thing: It does not suck.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Compared with its predecessor, the new movie contains less silliness to offend purists. At the same time, there isn't much to thrill anyone, either.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rise of the Silver Surfer is an existentially and aesthetically unnecessary sequel to the equally irrelevant if depressingly successful Fantastic Four.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer, our heroes get what they deserve: a decent action flick with a jolt of visual wow.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Unlike the recent spate of blackened threequels, those bottom-of-the-bag Spideys and Shreks and Pirates and Oceans, this kernel does pop.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Yes, the too-hot Alba is still miscast, and the film suffers from clumsy moments. But when it soars, it soars, and it is both blessedly brief and bloodless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You don't walk out of Rise of the Silver Surfer feeling as if you've gone three rounds with the Thing. This is a case where getting less than you bargained for feels like a victory.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Better than its juvenile predecessor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At times silly and then serious, this Fantastic Four is the cinematic equivalent of multiple personality disorder.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Marvel comic book this movie is based on was never as sitcom-ish as the two films it's inspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not a comedy tsunami, just consistent ripples of laughs and good vibes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's probably not the kind of animated adventure that's going to garner Oscar talk, but it's a good-hearted, old-fashioned, family-friendly tale.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Deeply uncool! At least the too-cute penguins don't dance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you have to see one penguin movie, this is it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not exactly awash in cleverness, but it is good clean fun for the family.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surf's Up is quite surprisingly good, going for the subtle chuckle where Happy Feet opted for show-stopping spectacle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surf's Up is actually a pretty funny and sophisticated comedy. It's relentlessly playful and imaginative in the vein of \"Toy Story,\" while keenly observant about comic nuances of behavior and bubbling over with neurotic dialogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie has just as much in common with This Is Spinal Tap or even Dogtown and Z-Boys as the cutesy and formulaic films that typically get churned out this time of year.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surf's Up! has a jokey-serious tone that engages both children and adults.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first delightful surprise among the summer blockbusters. Beautifully animated, terrifically acted and edited in a way that hilariously mimics those Endless Summer surf documentaries, it will amuse kids and flat-out tickle adults.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The jaunty sports story contains colorful characters, witty wisecracks and kinetic surf scenes. It's refreshing to see an animated family film that doesn't look like it was made on autopilot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Maybe the next penguin flick will do more justice to the subject. How about going all grindhouse in Lesbian Vampire Penguins of the SS?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Many of the riffs in the mock documentary might be lost on little tykes, but the film's feel-good message of perseverance, friendship and finding your own wave should be enjoyed by all.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film's tubular visuals and sun-struck philosophizing celebrate the sport while spoofing its disciples, mixing B-grade potty humor and totally-like-fried-chicken gags with faux interviews a la Christopher Guest.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surf's Up is that rarity in a children's movie, a comedy that's actually exciting. Watching the penguins ride inside the tube of a wave, or plunge under the surface, you may find yourself wanting to cheer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Marred by sudden dead spots and afflicted with a few alarming fits of double entendre inappropriateness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If its tale of a teenage penguin who follows his dream of becoming a great surfing champion weren't tired enough, Surf's Up compounds its lack of inventiveness by styling itself as a 'mockumentary,' another gimmick as surfed out as a Florida beach.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surrogates is an A-list blockbuster that would fit, damn proudly, on the lower half of a double bill.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Whatever the reason, Surrogates was shielded from the eyes of critics before its opening, and that's a shame. Because, whatever its flaws, it is a good movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If the whole point of this surrogate society is to appear as a perfectly beautiful avatar, why would Bruce Willis choose that ludicrous blond wig that looks like he plucked it off a mannequin at Boscov's?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Surrogates is entertaining and ingenious, but it settles too soon for formula.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The premise for this sci-fi actioner makes sense for about four seconds, after which you begin to wonder why everyone on the planet would willingly become a shut-in, how the poor are supposed to shell out for these high-tech androids, etc.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Give credit to filmmaker Jonathan Mostow for keeping the movie on track; give credit to star Bruce Willis for keeping a straight face.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the year's more entertaining sci-fi films.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>While the notion holds promise, the execution is strictly campy and adrenaline-driven.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Do the actors sound so robotic because they are playing robots well or humans badly? And did a machine write this dialogue? If so, could we please apply for an upgrade?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film moves along so quickly, and the surrogate world look is so eerie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bruce Willis has little to do but hit his predictable marks and mouth the generic dialogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The ideas probably have a bit more juice than the movie, but it's still an alert piece of entertainment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surrogates nudges the robo-thriller in an interesting direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surrogates bleakly satirizes our increasingly plugged-in world.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite bumpy execution likely to have detractors yelling \"deja boo,\" Surrogates oozes possibilities.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script is by the team that gave us Catwoman and the last two Terminator movies, which tells you all you need to know.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all the inspirations, the pieces of better stories that this tale was concocted from, Surrogates never manages to be anything more than a poor substitute for the real thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Surrogates stays afloat by not taking itself too seriously, but also by recognizing that a movie about robots shouldn't look as if it were made by one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pullman's striking performance here is undermined by Lynch's overreliance on those same grisly shock tactics, as well as a script that fails to capitalize on a promising premise and then swiftly collapses upon the revelation of a not-so-shocking twist.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film's a failure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In this long-time-coming sophomore film, Lynch exercises powers of her own. She gets repellant, seductive, sympathetic performances from her actors. Ormond and Pullman are frightfully good at teasing intimacy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its mad killers may wear masks. But the real and cheap disguise here is the film's own -- an exploitation shocker trying to pass itself off as art.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A grubby, disturbing serial-killer mystery, a kind of blood-simple Rashomon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The most enjoyable way to watch Surveillance -- 'enjoyable' in the relative sense -- is to take its awfulness for granted and pay attention to everything Bill Pullman does.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ether a ludicrously bad movie or a parody of same. Either way, it's pretty funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Every so often, you come upon a movie so jaw-droppingly wrong, you wonder if your eyes are deceiving you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A would-be transgression that tries to squeeze dark laughs from the spectacle of human suffering.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The many devils in Surveillance don't just want money or blood; they take pleasure in seeing you squirm, and that's precisely why this nightmare gets under your skin.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When Surveillance is good, it's a gory, pleasurable ride. When it's not -- it's just gory. But more often than not, it delivers on the camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I thought this was depressing and brutal for brutality sake alone.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Beneath the film's surface appeal as a twisty, morbidly funny freak-out lies a weightier theme on the resilience of children.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Horror fans are likely to guess the twist and feel bored; the more faint-of-heart may simply feel repulsed. And bored.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For a time, Surveillance is sick, smart fun. But then things get weird: yes, there's a big surprise, but its playout is predictable, and nasty.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While the narrative is hardly original - it meanders to a predictable but juicily malicious climactic twist - 'Surveillance' is never less than a compelling watch.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even Romero's staunchest fans might conclude their hero is going through the motions here. Yes, almost like a zombie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What we've got here is a just a B-movie western with buckets of gore, which might be fine coming from a Romero wannabe but not from the genuine article.</content>
</item>
<item label="none">
<content>George A. Romero's entertaining new zombie feature shows that you can't keep a good man down.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Steeped in fan-pleasing gore but woefully thin on ideas, originality (beyond new zombie-offing methods) or directorial flair.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Survival of the Dead almost never snaps into focus. Even its oxymoronic title doesn't work. It feels marginal, like an extended footnote.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Placidly photographed and lacking in urgency, Survival shows us the living flailing at fate and the dead just flailing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It has been six days since the dead began to walk, and a powerful emotion is gripping the land. Boredom.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I suppose it's nice that Romero has a hobby, but he couldn't be more of a bore if he were showing off his pine cone collection.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For the first time, a Romero zombie movie feels as if it was rushed out.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Romero is using better actors than in the past, which helps. But they are hobbled by a sometimes nonsensical script with logical lapses even genre fans will find hard to swallow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Shuffle, shuffle, limp, limp. That's not the shambling gait of the zombie hordes in George Romero's Survival of the Dead, but the draggy pace of the movie itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lot of Survival seems stale, as if Romero were growing bored with his own redundancies. Now in the final years of an uneven career, Romero needs to get out of his comfort zone.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like the literary monster mash-ups that have invaded the best-seller lists, Survival of the Dead mixes genres and milieus with absurdist glee.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Romero's Hatfields-and-McCoys setup feels more random than creative, and the idea that they're all Irish -- or cowboys! -- is more desultory still.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At best, Survival's ending, with a riff on \"beating a dead horse,\" may be taken for evidence of self-awareness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There are some memorable images, including the sight of a beautiful, horse-riding ''dead head.'' But for much of the movie, Van Sprang's zombie fatigue seems to be an echo of Romero's own.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The hurtful truth is that others -- many others -- have co-opted Romero's whole living dead thing and have been doing it with more style than the Pittsburgh zombie auteur is capable of these days.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Another year, another George Romero Dead film. But wait, there's plenty to delight in his sixth zombie eat-'em-up, which follows a rogue group of soldiers who come between warring clans on an isolated island.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's little here that's new or interesting; the movie is for hard-core Romero devotees only, and even they should approach this picture with expectations kept in check.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pique on earth and ill will toward men permeate this mirthless comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is dead from the outset given the artificiality of the premise about a lonely rich guy who hires the folks living in his boyhood home to be his family for the holidays.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The moral is that money can indeed buy happiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Surviving Christmas is about as funny as a rubber crutch for Tiny Tim.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a lot to not buy in Surviving Christmas. I recommend not buying.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Maybe the worst thing that can be said for Surviving Christmas is that it doesn't succeed even on its humble level of aspiration.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a desperation to Ben Affleck's mugging in Surviving Christmas that, depending on how you look at it, is either endearing or embarrassing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not since Scrooge got a look at Christmas future have the holidays seemed so shudderingly depressing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To write off Surviving Christmas as Affleck's folly gives the actor too much credit: He's actually the best thing in the movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Is it just me, or does anyone else think it odd Dreamworks is releasing a Christmas movie before Halloween?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Bear in mind the Yuletide lesson learned by every kid with an earnest aunt: Some presents look a whole lot like punishments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Can't decide whether it wants to be a black comedy, dumb farce, or sentimental sit-com.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Major stinker. We're talking hold your nose as you walk past the theater.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though introduced as a dark comedy, the movie quickly resorts to forced Hollywood humbuggery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The surprisingly effective bleak humor earned scene by scene in Surviving Christmas reveals the proper formula that Affleck abandoned after Good Will Hunting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's just in time for Halloween, and it is a scary movie. Unfortunately it's supposed to be a comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Surviving Christmas is exactly what's wrong with Hollywood</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This latest movie is absolutely awesome in its relentless mediocrity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>...a stunning debut by Natascha McElhone...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For many true movie fiends, noir is the key American movie type, and the most fun when it's done right. The Usual Suspects is done right.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I didn't believe this story for a minute, even in movie terms -- though it's less offensive than a piece of junk like Apt Pupil, Singer's subsequent feature.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A terrific cast of exciting actors socks over this absorbingly complicated yarn that's been spun in seductively slick fashion by director Bryan Singer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Singer creates a classy, thought-provoking mystery that is pleasingly old-fashioned and absolutely modern in the sly, slightly self-conscious play it makes with myth and methods of storytelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This movie finally isn't anything more than an intricate feat of gamesmanship, but it's still quite something to see.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Usual Suspects is the freshest, funniest and scariest crime thriller to come along since Pulp Fiction.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>But like a tale from the Arabian Nights, told for the sheer pleasure of storytelling, this elegant puzzle not only enjoys showing off, it also has something to show.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nothing is what it seems in this layered, velvety movie (which was shot in handsome wide-screen format) -- the truth keeps shifting -- and nothing matters either.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Next to the steady diet of Hollywood formula, contrived plots and situations a regular moviegoer can spot a mile off, The Usual Suspects is something quite different: A movie that's smarter than you are.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Usual Suspects is an accomplished synthesis of noir elements and, as such, is an entertaining entry to the genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After following the beckoning twists and turns, you're left trapped and more than a little disappointed for getting in so deep.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>After I first saw the film, I recommended it to people as an entertaining and commercial crime thriller; a standard story done very well. And then I saw it again. The movie is so much better the second time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The twist at the end is a corker, but crucial questions remain unanswered. What's interesting, though, is how little this intrudes on our enjoyment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director Bryan Singer gives his film enough surface flash to entertain future late-night cable possibilities.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As entertainment, the film is a lukewarm experience. But as a piece of construction, The Usual Suspects is a slick bit of business.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lots of fun and a very handsome, widescreen production by director Bryan Singer, who co-wrote the original script with once-and-future partner (and ex-private detective) Christopher McQuarrie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Once again, my comprehension began to slip, and finally I wrote down: 'To the degree that I do understand, I don't care.'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Dense with plot intricacies, thick with atmosphere, and packed with showy roles for a hip ensemble, The Usual Suspects is fun to watch -- a celebration of cool actors having a good time playing sweaty and devious lowlifes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Slips on the banana peel of exaggerated fear factor, falling facedown with the introduction of an uber-creep serial killer (Ben Kingsley) grimly stalking some hapless prey.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] visually jarring, psychologically daring trip that explores terror in a fresh, if crazy, manner.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its junkiness shines through its posh patina. Exploitation is just no fun anymore, now that it's all so damn tasteful.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A grisly, depraved and wholly uninvolving exercise in empty mannerism.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Suspect Zero is that rare case of a dull idea redeemed by sharp talent.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A violent, depressing and often ridiculous waste of time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Merely adequate.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The kind of by-the- numbers psychological/ action thriller that Paramount Pictures routinely makes with Ashley Judd and Morgan Freeman.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Suspect Zero is intriguing enough to be worth deciphering. It just delivers zero scares.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is a black hole of failed ambition that mystifies on every level and offers zero payoff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The latest evidence that Hollywood has run the se rial-killer thriller into the ground through overuse.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unless this is your first serial-killer movie, you've no doubt seen it all before.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[A] pretentiously made and excruciatingly dull thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Suspect Zero may be nonsense but at least it's not bland nonsense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Suspect Zero knows from creepy . . . and compelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A gussied-up bore.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all its trying, Suspect Zero ultimately fails to hit home. It falls somewhere between a genre picture and arty exploration of big themes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too devised and elaborate to really engage us.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie isn't talking to us, it's talking to other serial killer movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Alfred Hitchcock's trademarked cinematic development of suspenseful drama, through mental emotions of the story principals, is vividly displayed in Suspicion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite a silly cop-out ending (imposed by RKO), a gripping domestic thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Hitchcock is probably the most artful sophist working for the films -- and anyone who doesn't think so should see Suspicion.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie that makes sense only to the eye (and even then . . .).</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Argento works so hard for his effects -- throwing around shock cuts, colored lights, and peculiar camera angles -- that it would be impolite not to be a little frightened.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's always fascinating to watch; the thrills and spills are so classy and fast that the movie becomes in effect what horror movies seemed like when you were too young to get in to see them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Argento's methods make potentially stomach-turning material more interesting than it ought to be.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is too lazy to provide any actual jokes with its send-up of the genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Short on thrills and laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Craven tries to do this 'veggie-man' horror in a suitable DC Comics style; and with Louis Jourdan as arch-villain 'Arcane', not to mention Adrienne Barbeau (Mrs John Carpenter) as the Thing's object of desire, he's definitely on the right track.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of those movies that fall somewhere between buried treasures and guilty pleasures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[The film] wants desperately to be funny and, from time to time, it is. However, you might wish it would trust the audience to discover the humor for itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As summer shoot-'em-ups go, this is pretty well executed, with plenty of macho posing and gunfire.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>he high definition SWAT training footage resembles a US Army recruitment ad, appropriate since TV journeyman Johnson imagines downtown LA as an unpatrolled Baghdad, swarming with guntotin' mercenaries pursuing their share of the bounty.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is something sneakily gratifying about all this.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A rigmarole of stranded cliches and thrill-free action-movie legerdemain.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You can't get mad at it -- except for the two hours of your life it steals from you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The director, a TV guy named Clark Johnson, doesn't shoot action very well, which is sort of a handicap.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Clark Johnson strives for realistic detail and action. Unfortunately, such adherence to technical purity proves to be a weakness for the movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>S.W.A.T. has blockbuster ambitions, but it develops characters and plot at a leisurely pace better suited to the small screen than the big one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As summer popcorn movies go, you could do worse than S.W.A.T.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>SWAT is better than Gigli, but so is most outpatient surgery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite the usual macho posturing and testosterone poisoning that are the hallmarks of such projects, S.W.A.T. finds some room for a comfortable lived-in quality among a small, likable cast that exudes terrific chemistry.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What we have here is a model for the paint-by -numbers, perfectly generic, proudly soulless summer action flick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A worn-out yawner of a cop thriller where even the cliches seem to realize how dated they are.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Schlocky, slam-bang fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lifeless trudge through squandered opportunities and god-awful dialogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fresher popcorn than most of the sequels that have come and gone.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film full of phony swagger and dialogue so awful you hope for once-distracting conversations to break out in the theatre around you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of those generic cop-slash-war movies of the Jerry Bruckheimer school -- where men are men and so are the women, where the hardware is fetishized.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is grand-scale studio-work at its most beguiling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A considerable achievement even if, on balance, it's more of a Tim Burton phantasmagoria than a Sondheim fantasia.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie may substitute Grand Guignol for laughs at times, but it's spectacularly stylized -- each throat-slashing exceptional -- persuasively sung, and imaginatively adapted for the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's as if Burton was born to direct it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thoughtful, sincere and moving film, buttressed by a fine, central performance by an actor at the top of his form.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is grand-scale studio-work at its most beguiling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is distinguished, hypnotic, brilliantly executed and positively electrifying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Sweeney Todd': Burton has deconstructed and redefined Sondheim's masterwork, creating a film that compliments its stage predecessor. 'Todd' is at once different from the play and yet not different at all. A unique achievement</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This Sweeney Todd is all subtext and no substance. It starts off large and swaggering but doesn't know where to turn next: Burton seems fixated on serving up an event, to the extent that he neglects to dig into the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mesmerizing and highly entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's easily Burton's best since, well, ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stylized but spasmodic, this Sweeney seems more interested in distancing than captivating an audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Depp may not be a trained singer, but his voice is more than passable, and his presence -- his Sweeney is Edward Scissorhands gone bad -- is perfect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>By all means go, and be prepared for a holiday musical like no other.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The wait for a good Tim Burton movie is finally over.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sondheim's original musical was already a mad synthesis of Jacobean shock, Brechtian irony and Dickensian pathos -- to which Burton's lush visuals add another layer of aesthetic distance. The overall effect is somewhere between melodrama and camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film benefits from Burton's consistency of vision. Swooping camera work and a sense of really discomfiting fantasy do the groundwork. When characters break into song, it fits in the world Burton has built.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No sentiment goes unbloodied in [Burton's] exuberantly dark Sweeney Todd.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An elegant horror film that takes pleasure in its own theatricality, gives pleasure with caustic wit, trusts the power of Stephen Sondheim's score and exults in flights of fancy that only a movie can provide.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It combines some of Tim Burton's favorite elements: The fantastic, the ghoulish, the bizarre, the unspeakable, the romantic and in Johnny Depp, he has an actor he has worked with since Edward Scissorhands and finds a perfect instrument.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is grand-scale studio-work at its most beguiling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A considerable achievement even if, on balance, it's more of a Tim Burton phantasmagoria than a Sondheim fantasia.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie may substitute Grand Guignol for laughs at times, but it's spectacularly stylized -- each throat-slashing exceptional -- persuasively sung, and imaginatively adapted for the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's as if Burton was born to direct it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thoughtful, sincere and moving film, buttressed by a fine, central performance by an actor at the top of his form.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is grand-scale studio-work at its most beguiling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is distinguished, hypnotic, brilliantly executed and positively electrifying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Sweeney Todd': Burton has deconstructed and redefined Sondheim's masterwork, creating a film that compliments its stage predecessor. 'Todd' is at once different from the play and yet not different at all. A unique achievement</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This Sweeney Todd is all subtext and no substance. It starts off large and swaggering but doesn't know where to turn next: Burton seems fixated on serving up an event, to the extent that he neglects to dig into the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mesmerizing and highly entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's easily Burton's best since, well, ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stylized but spasmodic, this Sweeney seems more interested in distancing than captivating an audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Depp may not be a trained singer, but his voice is more than passable, and his presence -- his Sweeney is Edward Scissorhands gone bad -- is perfect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>By all means go, and be prepared for a holiday musical like no other.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The wait for a good Tim Burton movie is finally over.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sondheim's original musical was already a mad synthesis of Jacobean shock, Brechtian irony and Dickensian pathos -- to which Burton's lush visuals add another layer of aesthetic distance. The overall effect is somewhere between melodrama and camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film benefits from Burton's consistency of vision. Swooping camera work and a sense of really discomfiting fantasy do the groundwork. When characters break into song, it fits in the world Burton has built.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No sentiment goes unbloodied in [Burton's] exuberantly dark Sweeney Todd.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An elegant horror film that takes pleasure in its own theatricality, gives pleasure with caustic wit, trusts the power of Stephen Sondheim's score and exults in flights of fancy that only a movie can provide.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It combines some of Tim Burton's favorite elements: The fantastic, the ghoulish, the bizarre, the unspeakable, the romantic and in Johnny Depp, he has an actor he has worked with since Edward Scissorhands and finds a perfect instrument.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is grand-scale studio-work at its most beguiling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A considerable achievement even if, on balance, it's more of a Tim Burton phantasmagoria than a Sondheim fantasia.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie may substitute Grand Guignol for laughs at times, but it's spectacularly stylized -- each throat-slashing exceptional -- persuasively sung, and imaginatively adapted for the screen.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's as if Burton was born to direct it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A thoughtful, sincere and moving film, buttressed by a fine, central performance by an actor at the top of his form.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is grand-scale studio-work at its most beguiling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is distinguished, hypnotic, brilliantly executed and positively electrifying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Sweeney Todd': Burton has deconstructed and redefined Sondheim's masterwork, creating a film that compliments its stage predecessor. 'Todd' is at once different from the play and yet not different at all. A unique achievement</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This Sweeney Todd is all subtext and no substance. It starts off large and swaggering but doesn't know where to turn next: Burton seems fixated on serving up an event, to the extent that he neglects to dig into the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mesmerizing and highly entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's easily Burton's best since, well, ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Stylized but spasmodic, this Sweeney seems more interested in distancing than captivating an audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Depp may not be a trained singer, but his voice is more than passable, and his presence -- his Sweeney is Edward Scissorhands gone bad -- is perfect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>By all means go, and be prepared for a holiday musical like no other.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The wait for a good Tim Burton movie is finally over.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sondheim's original musical was already a mad synthesis of Jacobean shock, Brechtian irony and Dickensian pathos -- to which Burton's lush visuals add another layer of aesthetic distance. The overall effect is somewhere between melodrama and camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film benefits from Burton's consistency of vision. Swooping camera work and a sense of really discomfiting fantasy do the groundwork. When characters break into song, it fits in the world Burton has built.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No sentiment goes unbloodied in [Burton's] exuberantly dark Sweeney Todd.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An elegant horror film that takes pleasure in its own theatricality, gives pleasure with caustic wit, trusts the power of Stephen Sondheim's score and exults in flights of fancy that only a movie can provide.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It combines some of Tim Burton's favorite elements: The fantastic, the ghoulish, the bizarre, the unspeakable, the romantic and in Johnny Depp, he has an actor he has worked with since Edward Scissorhands and finds a perfect instrument.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Droll and amusing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A shallow portrait of the artist as a cad.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is enjoyment to be had from Sweet and Lowdown.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A snappy, loose-limbed performance from Penn.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie has ample delights.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An enjoyable diversion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is so confused about where it wants to go, it suffers from the same identity crisis as its protagonist.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is one very tuneful labor of love.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A likable, lively little ditty -- one theme, some clever variations -- that never wears out its welcome.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The only reason to see this film is for the acting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet and Lowdown is undeniably pleasant, but British actress Samantha Morton quietly explodes it: Her performance is like nothing I've seen in recent years.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a glossy, engrossing hunk of motion picture entertainment, slickly produced by Berman.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Offers little indication of what made the original play interesting (especially in Elia Kazan's stage production), despite the fact that Paul Newman and Geraldine Page are called on to reprise their original roles.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brooks' direction seems a little too stolid for all the sleazy, flaming passions. These are, however, given full measure by an excellent cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This cynical, coruscating drama has a strong look of being contrived, and Mr. Brooks' happy ending for it is implausible and absurd.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If there's anything we can learn from the creatures here, it's that any day in which you don't get stripped of your coat or eaten by a bear is probably a good one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are audience rewards for sticking with the herd and its lonesome cowboys.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a gorgeous and, believe it or not, riveting documentary...about sheep.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It may not be your thing, but Sweetgrass is unlike anything you'll see in a theater this year. It bravely strays from the flock.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Filmmakers Ilisa Barbash and Lucien Castaing-Taylor rigorously follow the cinema-verite creed: no sonorous Morgan Freeman voiceovers, no explanatory intertitles until the finale, just carefully observed reality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you're used to the ADD pace of modern filmmaking, Sweetgrass will probably drive you crazy. If you can adjust, it could widen your soul.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweetgrass is an unexpectedly intoxicating documentary, unexpected because it blends high artistic standards with the grueling reality of one of the toughest, most exhausting of work environments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In an extraordinary series of tableaux that are alternately idyllic and severe, Sweetgrass defies the conventions of what most of us regard as a documentary film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Leaves behind the domain of ethnography and becomes a work of art.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The filmmakers' motivation couldn't be clearer: They needed to capture a way of life that may soon exist only on film and in memory.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An intriguing but overly demanding portrait of rural Montana that concentrates on sheep and their herders.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Castaing-Taylor's lensing -- from sheep staring into a camera to panoramic views of the gorgeous landscape -- is pleasing to the eye.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The first essential movie of this young year.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the breathtaking vistas of Big Sky Country in Ilisa Barbash and Lucien Castaing-Taylor's unforgettable sheep-herding documentary come close to heaven, it's telling that AC/DC's \"Highway to Hell\" can be faintly heard.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Memorably captures a dying way of American life, a marvelously untrammeled American landscape and at least two animals -- men and sheep -- that despite their millennia-long domestic relationship still have a spark of wildness in them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As subcultural anthropology, it's unassailable. Yet the often ugly-looking DV aesthetic dilutes the cumulative effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweetgrass showcases an elemental intimacy between man and animal.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The kind of flick that gives fluff a good name.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The premise falters along with much of the shtick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Both harmlessly cynical and deeply fatuous.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>America's Sweethearts is a balloon, all right -- a lead one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A boring, brain-dead flop.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too cynically slick and emotionally shallow.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lackluster screwball comedy and dubious Julia Roberts vehicle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A clunky ribbing of the movie industry.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is a polished muddle, fitfully amusing but with no spine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a perfectly fine setup for romantic-comedy capering, with enough good one-liners to satisfy. But Roth seems a bit at sea with his powerhouse cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Doesn't contain a single genuine emotion. It's just as bogus and hollow as the movie business it portrays.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film that manages the frustrating feat of being pleasant and misguided at the same time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Occasionally amusing, but also an irritating mess.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As undemanding summer movies go, America's Sweethearts is surprisingly funny and sweet, despite some missed comic opportunities and curious casting choices.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For the farce it so desperately wants to be, the film often feels slack and too reliant on so-so punch lines for laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You go to America's Sweethearts anticipating a prime flossy, glossy entertainment. You come away better by a few laughs but with expectations sadly deflated.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Given its subject matter, it's too genial to cut deep.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's as preposterous and phony as a Confederate C-note, but Reese Witherspoon has so much natural beauty, talent and charm she guarantees more fun than the day the hogs ate Willie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite her relentless vim and winsome facial symmetry, Witherspoon is just too dialed-up to be America's Sweetheart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is definitely worth seeing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you're a fan of Witherspoon, this movie was produced, shot, edited and distributed entirely for you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Physical charms are no match for the generic predictability of the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sweet Home Alabama is the latest picture to give you the sense that Hollywood filmmakers simply plucked another old pop-tune title ripe for ripping off, then were shaken by the rude reality of coming up with a script to jerry-build around it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reese Witherspoon makes the proverbial silk purse out of a sow's ear in the romantic comedy Sweet Home Alabama, demonstrating how even the most mediocre of material can be redeemed by a convincing performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pure formula, right down to Melanie's final choice, which will come as no surprise to anyone paying attention.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a feel-good movie that does just that.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet Home Alabama may be sweet and small and inconsequential, but it offers the privileged experience of watching two stars being born.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you can tolerate the redneck-versus-blueblood cliches that the film trades in, Sweet Home Alabama is diverting in the manner of Jeff Foxworthy's stand-up act.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I didn't mind when Reese Witherspoon dyed her career Legally Blonde, but I found it downright disappointing to watch it go south in Sweet Home Alabama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie with a more sitcomic premise you are unlikely to find.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As predictable as a Florida election controversy, as wholly amusing as a cold plate of grits.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Witherspoon is such a delight -- her comic timing so good, and her pixie-ish good looks so fascinating -- that she manages to make Sweet Home Alabama seem charming and funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A romantic comedy so rote, dull and predictable that it makes You've Got Mail seem innovative and fresh.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's leaden and predictable, and laughs are lacking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's as preposterous and phony as a Confederate C-note, but Reese Witherspoon has so much natural beauty, talent and charm she guarantees more fun than the day the hogs ate Willie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Despite her relentless vim and winsome facial symmetry, Witherspoon is just too dialed-up to be America's Sweetheart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is definitely worth seeing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you're a fan of Witherspoon, this movie was produced, shot, edited and distributed entirely for you.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Physical charms are no match for the generic predictability of the story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sweet Home Alabama is the latest picture to give you the sense that Hollywood filmmakers simply plucked another old pop-tune title ripe for ripping off, then were shaken by the rude reality of coming up with a script to jerry-build around it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reese Witherspoon makes the proverbial silk purse out of a sow's ear in the romantic comedy Sweet Home Alabama, demonstrating how even the most mediocre of material can be redeemed by a convincing performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pure formula, right down to Melanie's final choice, which will come as no surprise to anyone paying attention.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is a feel-good movie that does just that.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet Home Alabama may be sweet and small and inconsequential, but it offers the privileged experience of watching two stars being born.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you can tolerate the redneck-versus-blueblood cliches that the film trades in, Sweet Home Alabama is diverting in the manner of Jeff Foxworthy's stand-up act.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I didn't mind when Reese Witherspoon dyed her career Legally Blonde, but I found it downright disappointing to watch it go south in Sweet Home Alabama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A movie with a more sitcomic premise you are unlikely to find.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As predictable as a Florida election controversy, as wholly amusing as a cold plate of grits.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Witherspoon is such a delight -- her comic timing so good, and her pixie-ish good looks so fascinating -- that she manages to make Sweet Home Alabama seem charming and funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A romantic comedy so rote, dull and predictable that it makes You've Got Mail seem innovative and fresh.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's leaden and predictable, and laughs are lacking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's hard to sum up Sweetie, which happens to be one of the movie's strengths.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Extra-thick vanilla schmalted with just the right amount of raw sugar to summon the awwwws of high school girls.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Should have been called Cloying November.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Who on earth could resist Charlize Theron? Well, if she's imitating Sandy Dennis, it's not all that hard.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Sweet November were a valentine, it would end up in the dead-letter office.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's just too much fantasy here to swallow or take seriously.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>O'Connor shamelessly lays on the schmaltz and cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I kept waiting for [Reeves] to point out that, given the state of San Francisco real estate these days, it's hard to reconcile a life of endless surf-romping with a life of having a roof over one's head.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Beware all male viewers who enter here, you are in chick-movie hell.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It nearly qualifies as a guilty pleasure. But blame Keanu Reeves for ruining its chances for so- bad- it's- good status.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To quote Reeves when Theron tries to bolt suddenly from his car: 'Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, WHOA!'</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet November is neither a masterpiece nor a remake of one, but its wistfulness is infectious, and its melancholy mood lingers for days.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet November does neither of its leads any favors. But they fill their roles admirably, and then some.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I have a better way to enjoy life: Avoid movies like this ... before it's too late.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As Bill and Ted might say, it's one bogus journey, dude.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Dumb enough to make The Wedding Planner seem like an Ingmar Bergman film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Defies all comprehension.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The sort of movie that seems to exist for no good reason except to keep the studio's pipeline filled with filmed product.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet Smell, which could have been offal, is raised to considerable dramatic heights by intense acting, taut direction (by Alexander Mackendrick), [and] superb camera work (by James Wong Howe).</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mackendrick's nighthawk landscape is compellingly, poetically bleak.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>James Hill's production, locationed in Manhattan, captures the feel of Broadway and environs after dark.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The screen was rarely so dark or cruel.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lean, mean amorality tale that still goes down like a cookie laced with arsenic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The main incentive to see this movie is its witty, pungent and idiomatic dialogue, such as you never hear on the screen anymore in this age of special-effects illiteracy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its pleasures are almost obscenely abundant.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of those rare films where you remember the names of the characters because you remember them -- as people, as types, as benchmarks.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first black director to break into commercial cinema, Van Peebles obviously feels deeply about black oppression. But he has chosen, paradoxically, to make the kinds of unrealistic films for which blacks have justly criticized white film-makers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A shrewd and powerful mix of commercial ingredients and ideological intent.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Totally uncompromising and grindingly repetitive, the film nevertheless accumulates a kind of hallucinatory groove, with unexpected shafts of bizarre humour and vigorous, experimental new wave direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Instead of dramatizing injustice, Van Peebles merchandizes it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Vera Hruba Ralston of her time, Madonna has persisted in making movies despite all evidence that this is one medium in which no one wants to see or hear her.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Both husband and wife seem to be in way over their heads.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Every bit the cinematic shipwreck you'd imagine it to be.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If there is one thing worse than a Guy Ritchie movie, it's a Guy Ritchie movie with Madonna in it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I wouldn't wish the stupefying dialogue of \"Swept Away\" on any actress, but to watch Madonna flounder through it is more punishment than I can bear.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A better title, for all concerned, might be Swept Under the Rug.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Two of the least likable characters I've seen in a romance in a long time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Is it a comedy? A drama? A romance? A cartoon?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all his fidelity to the Wertmuller screenplay, Ritchie has made a movie that is neither as attractive nor as repulsive, and certainly not as funny, as the original.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film turns out to have nothing going for it at all.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Staggeringly dreadful romance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even camp status eludes this tepid and misguided picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>New ways of describing badness need to be invented to describe exactly how bad it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Down the line, this movie may become a camp classic. At the moment, it's a stitch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>After a ghastly start, it becomes a curiously affecting document of a director trying to show the world why he loves his wife -- not the changeling pop star, but the actress.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What Madonna does here can't properly be called acting -- more accurately, it's moving and it's talking and it's occasionally gesturing, sometimes all at once.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's hard to imagine another director ever making his wife look so bad in a major movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's lost the politics and the social observation and become just another situation romance about a couple of saps stuck in an inarticulate screenplay.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Swept Away's worst crime is that it is butt-numbingly B-O-R-I-N-G.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At no point should anyone mistake this for an actual movie. This is an extended beach video that will leave no one swept away.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director John Polson mutes the conservative sexual politics of the original film, focusing on the lightweight, efficient suspense story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It would be so easy for an actress to overplay this role, to morph into high camp, but Christensen stays icy cool.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Only the very easily pleased will be able to see past its limitations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's like going to a house party and watching the host defend himself against a frothing ex-girlfriend. You don't want to call the cops. You want to call Domino's.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not really a thriller so much as a movie for teens to laugh, groan and hiss at.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Departs from being a psychological thriller and becomes a sort of bloodless slasher film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Proof that a thriller can be sleekly shot, expertly cast, paced with crisp professionalism... and still be a letdown if its twists and turns hold no more surprise than yesterday's weather report.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nothing plot-wise is worth e-mailing home about.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A chiller resolutely without chills.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It would be great to see this turd squashed under a truck, preferably a semi.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first Fatal Attraction was vile enough. Do we really need the Tiger Beat version?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a cheap thriller without the cheap thrills.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Swimfan] falls victim to sloppy plotting, an insultingly unbelievable final act and a villainess who is too crazy to be interesting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Swimfan, like Fatal Attraction, eventually goes overboard with a loony melodramatic denouement in which a high school swimming pool substitutes for a bathtub.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The project's filmmakers forgot to include anything even halfway scary as they poorly rejigger Fatal Attraction into a high school setting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ripped from the pages of the See Dick Run, See Jane Stalk Him handbook, the thrill-less thriller Swimfan is as dumb as it gets.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The picture's raison d'etre has to be Spacey's 'loud and nasty' performance: he's the sort of actor who grabs you by the throat and beats you about the head without ever lifting his feet from the desk.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This excessively talky, incoherently plotted, would-be film noir is not very good.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To outsiders, all this rage and gnashing of teeth may seem silly and self-absorbed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sharks is a one-joke movie, and the joke wears thin less than halfway through.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Huang's] plot may be overwritten and the ending may be less than satisfying, but his eye and ear are right.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film has no subtlety, so the one-dimensional story comes across as a sophomoric, pointless tirade.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When it comes time to take this drama to another level, addressing the darker and more pertinent issue of why Guy puts up with it and what he wants out of life, Huang is right there.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kevin Spacey, who is the reason to see the picture, is hilariously ruthless as Buddy Ackerman.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There doesn't seem to be enough material here to satisfy a full length feature, and the movie, which starts with such promise, begins to drag around its midpoint.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A dazzling, frightening tour de force by Kevin Spacey.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When Spacey goes ballistic, only to freeze the nitroglycerine in his veins a moment later, you don't want to look anywhere else.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Four guys hang out, kid one another, get into scuffles and flash their gonadal searchlight for available women. Yikes, haven't there been enough variations on the multiple-buddy movie? Actually, no.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A winningly confident snapshot of the nightlives of a bunch of young showbiz wannabes in a very upto-the-minute Hollywood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ninety minutes spent learning how not to pick up girls. This is what the movies were made for, isn't it?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Favreau wrote this screenplay with his real friends in mind. And the cast's camaraderie is appealingly clear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A guy film that gives you something to latch onto, that makes male bonding both believable and appealing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's no masterpiece, but it's real.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is sweet, funny, observant and goofy with a small \"g,\" which means you don't get paid, but at least you don't have to wear the suit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Swingers is uneven, amateurish and borderline misogynistic. But it's also very funny, and it never loses its cool.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This kind of story -- a staple of low-budget features -- is getting awfully stale, and the injection of humor can't completely invigorate the proceedings.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Swing Shift tries ... to twist some consequence out of a tawdry adulterous tryst by a couple of self-centered sneaks. But the writing and acting are too flat for the challenge.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hawn, atypically cast and supported by all-round excellent performances, proves that she can act.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's no suspense and no big emotional payoff, but the movie is always absorbing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Offers Miss Hawn her best role since ''Private Benjamin,'' and she is most winning.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Another winner for the Fred Astaire-Ginger Rogers combo. It's smart, modern, and impressive in every respect, from its boy-loses-girl background to its tunefulness, dancipation, production quality and general high standards.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the best of the Astaire-Rogers musicals, and one that shouldn't have worked as well as it did.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The score by Jerome Kern and Dorothy Fields is peerless.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nothing so intangible as a disappointing musical score should deter you from enjoying them to the Astaire-Rogers limit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Of all of the places the movies have created, one of the most magical and enduring is the universe of Fred Astaire and Ginger Rogers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a sentiment Capra might well have echoed, though he would surely have punched up the gags while he was at it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>He shoots simultaneously for 'wake up, America!' inspiration and good ol' boy charm but ends up putting both barrels through his own cowboy-booted foot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not a bad movie, probably OK to rent on DVD, but I'm saying don't rush to the theaters.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is neither appreciably better nor dramatically worse than its hokey, please-describe-me-as-'Capraesque' premise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One minute you're laughing at its sendup of the political process, and the next you're stricken by the sorry state of the sweet and brainy protagonist's family.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the most surprising, politically suggestive movies to come out of Hollywood this year.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As often happens with politics, even as Swing Vote entertains, it leaves us feeling like we've been subjected to some slick manipulation and worse, left with promises unfulfilled.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Swing Vote, an oddly off-balance comedy directed by Joshua Michael Stern, feels like two movies; one much better than the other.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The mix of comedy and drama is winning; Costner couldn't be better, and the little girl is a find.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stern and his lead actor do manage to pull it all together at the end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Swing Vote nicely boils down America's political malaise to one man's awakening from a Budweiser stupor and seeing the only thing that matters when you don't pay attention and exercise the franchise on Election Day: You're letting your kid down.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This would-be civics lesson is such an appalling view of American democracy that it could be used as a recruiting film by al Qaeda.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The lightweight Swing Vote is a good-ol'-boy civics lesson that's too scattered to achieve its predictable goals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film eventually bogs down in drama, with an unnecessary subplot involving Bud's estranged wife and an ethical dilemma for a local news reporter (Paula Patton) that never really gets off the ground.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Swing Vote is an amiable lug of a movie, part public service announcement, part political satire and part good-old-boy comedy with a spritz of sentiment hanging over the entire enterprise.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The filmmakers want to fashion a civics lesson but they don't bother to include anything of substance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The undertones of Frank Capra come bubbling to the surface in a smarmy finale complete with French horn and bags of mail from the common folk.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Swiss Family Robinson, like most of Walt Disney's screen versions of the children's classics, is good Disney and bad culture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's hard to imagine how the picture could be better as a rousing, humorous and gentle-hearted tale of family love amid primitive isolation and dangers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You have to overlook a whole lot of guff in order to enjoy the slight but pleasurable entertainment of The Switch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's much to enjoy, if not quite enough to disguise the film's essential awkwardness in trying to cover too many bases.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The comedy itself suffers from awkward scheduling. Though this isn't its only wrinkle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's not a bad film, really, just sort of average. But Bateman is so good in it -- natural, funny, yet full of real emotion -- that you immediately want to see him again in a better film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Aside from the fact that it's all too entirely predictable, The Switch is a pleasant enough end-of-the-summer time killer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This New York-based comedy directed by Josh Gordon and Will Speck distinguishes itself with three-dimensional characters and an engaging storyline.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Likable cast wasted in a dopey comedy. But hey, at least it has the first head-lice-removal instructional montage in romcom history.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A warm, quirkily observant film, strengthened by some appealing performances and a low-key, easygoing vibe.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tries to be more than a sitcom but keeps falling back on cheap laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's Judd Apatow lite, Farrelly brothers special blend. Just call it When Harry Met Sally and Her Ovum.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The truly dusty cliche it drags out again is the cute couple who don't, you know, think-of-each-other-like-that. Until, of course, they do.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another in a recent line of romcoms eager to get us laughing all the way to the sperm bank, and then to the infant dividends beyond.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first third of The Switch, directed by Josh Gordon and Will Speck, is so bizarre that it leads you to wonder if, through some miraculous lack of oversight, the movie will blaze an unpredictable path. No such luck.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At its heart, it's really not that different from a regular romantic comedy. Well, except that it's funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The sadness comes from the audience's sense that inside this slick, conventional romantic comedy there's a tender, scruffy little movie struggling to get out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taken on its own terms, it's a light, sweet, curiously enjoyable misfit romance, whose real star is not Aniston but her magnificently awkward Lothario, Jason Bateman.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aniston and Bateman each bring a rare Bordeaux, and the writers bring Spam on white bread. You can skip the picnic or show up and have a glass of wine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Unfortunately, this latest ho-hum rom-com from Hollywood's industrial commissary comes out half-baked despite noble efforts by two undeniably likable stars who try to rescue it from mediocrity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>More his journey than hers, more satire than slapstick, the film is that rare example of rom-com about men, which turns out to be a nice switch indeed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Quaid is a one-note sadsack here and no natural action hero.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The acting is so bad that apparently none of the performers ever got another job in the movies, and the costumes in Ben Hur seem less dated that those on display here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A terrific example of efficient, resourceful filmmaking, and its depiction of urban ills is, if anything, all too prophetic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To watch Switchblade Sisters is to visit a never-never land of shopworn media images colliding in a tabloid high school of the mind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sublime, exploitative camp.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Just good enough to make it understandable why someone else might really like it. And it's just bad enough to make you wonder about such a person.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Badly acted, written and directed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another in a long line of middling movies for Travolta.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story ... is just what fills in the gaps between slow-motion fireballs, Matrix-style frozen mayhem, and Halle Berry's notoriously undraped breasts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The sleazy script by Skip Woods ... slimes the actors.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An action opera designed to elicit Beavis and Butt-head-level appreciation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nobody really cares about the plot, least of all the filmmakers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>My inner jock left hungry for some good final jolts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sena doesn't back up his bravado and, indeed, his film is rather flushable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All this excess, leading to nothing much.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Feels like every other action thriller we've seen in the past three years, only it's more annoying.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Contains five elements that I hate about modern movies: computers, guns, explosions, out-of-control cars and the new requisite, a child performer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>By the seventh explosion, you can't help wondering whether all this flashy stuff amounts to more of a smokescreen shielding a lack of spine or soul.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A film that reeks of stupidity and cynicism, one that makes you feel soiled just to have sat through it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Truthfully, it's all twaddle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Don't look too closely. If you do, it becomes not just mindless, but ludicrous, preposterous and downright stupid.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is intelligent, committed, and politically provocative, though its narrative puzzle box may prompt you to throw up your hands and let ExxonMobil go on running the world.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its dark, dog-eat-dog vision of the world we live in may give you geopolitical nightmares.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Evidently, such matters of thematic coherence, so well explored by Gaghan in Traffic, were not as important to him this time around, and it's a mistake.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's entirely possible that Gaghan just isn't an actor's director.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Syriana impresses, not because it is very moving, which it isn't, or because it is crystal clear, which it also isn't, but because it is so large, so encompassing, so seemingly privy to inside stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Watch closely and listen carefully during Syriana because Stephen Gaghan's movie is that rarity: a thinking person's drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's hard to get passionately swept away by a movie when you're struggling continually to figure out who's doing what to whom and why.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Syriana coolly dissects a system of duplicity, chicanery and corruption that has been in play for several decades now, and examines the consequences that it has borne.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Syriana is an ambitious edifice, built with conviction and skill. But I'm not sure I understand it, and I'm not sure I care.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A purposely jagged and harsh news story of a film, Syriana attempts to take on the powers that run the world and for the most part it succeeds.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It forces you to intently watch and listen and ask questions, something that in the past six years has been skillfully portrayed as an unpatriotic response to an increasingly complex international scenario.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Syriana] has what lots of great thrillers have, a sense that it knows things we don't, that even the most skeptical of us may be a little naive about the ways of the world.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Syriana is a fascinating movie -- and a substantive and thought-provoking one -- but it does not necessarily attain greatness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Intelligent, political, incensed, timely, and appropriately cynical.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As he did in Traffic, Gaghan intertwines his disparate subplots with impeccable pacing -- his screenplay is a model of how to arrange scenes so that each one ends leaving you wanting to know more.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Your enjoyment of this movie will be in direct proportion to your patience. If you can stand not knowing everything right now and wait for the story's threads to weave into a rug, Syriana makes for an engaging time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Gaghan doesn't insult our intelligence, but he demands our attention. If you're up to those demands, you'll be rewarded.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Syriana is an endlessly fascinating movie about oil and money, America and China, traders and spies, the Gulf States and Texas, reform and revenge, bribery and betrayal.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Untangle the Gordian knot at the heart of Syriana and you find a riveting drama of succession.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taboo is not an entirely successful film, but it isn't boring.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It takes a while to get to the meat of the movie, but it's well worth the wait.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It almost seems a parody of willfully obscure art-house fare. Yet it has an undertow that sucks you in as often as it strands you back on shore.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A kind of jigsaw puzzle, spiced up with references to \"White Mischief,\" \"Out of Africa\" and \"The Snows of Kilimanjaro,\" that will frustrate some audiences and fascinate others.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The audience is left to imagine much of the story, though it is clear it involves love, betrayal, guilt, regret and a recurring crocodile.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Portuguese director Miguel Gomes' latest film moves through different styles and eras, and proves that shooting in black and white is as versatile as it ever was.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Few films are this smart about subtly couching their allegorical aspirations within more straightforward narratives; fewer still are able to do so with such energetically inventive virtuoso style.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A lyrical Old Hollywood melodrama projected on a bedsheet? A celluloid curio a la Barnum's Fiji mermaid? At such times, it's better to stick with a simple \"wonderful.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its artfulness seems like an alibi, an excuse for keeping the ugliness of history out of the picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Miguel Gomes begins Tabu in a seemingly ridiculous vein and unexpectedly shifts to something surprisingly enriching and poetic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A brilliantly nuanced, deeply imagined psycho- excavation of modern Europe by the Portuguese director Miguel Gomes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The reward is a stunning photographic narrative - a love story told as sweeping parable. But to get there takes an investment by the viewer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Evoking work as disparate as that of Apichatpong Weerasethakul, Guy Maddin and Claire Denis - with a dash of 'The Artist' thrown in - 'Tabu' is a tantalising trip.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's an amiable but slow slice of nostalgia: think 'Hot Tub Time Machine' meets 'Superbad' - without the big laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This low-powered, amiable, stunningly unimportant movie is essentially one long, noisy party (set in two houses).</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Take Me Home Tonight\" is not a bad movie. In fact, it's pretty good. It's just unnecessary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's formulaic at best - and even that formula isn't always thought through.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Drinking jokes. Sex jokes. Wild antics. Sincere looks. Nothing goes on here that hasn't gone on -- and gone on better -- in other movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A dirge of a comedy...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After the gimmick begins to fade, what remains is less than likable characters inhabiting an all-too-familiar plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It tries hard, but it always falls short.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>They speak entirely in plot points and punchlines and seem to be motivated only by lust, greed and ego. Well, we all are, but few bring to this motivation so little intelligence and wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A reasonably watchable immersion in nostalgia.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>very last joke in the movie -- verbal gags, visual gags, musical cues, camera moves -- is crushingly literal.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It, like, totally pains me to say this, but Take Me Home Tonight is a bummer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[The] trite boy-meets-girl arc (he lies about his job) is occasionally offset by some potent comic misadventures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>'Take Me Home Tonight' has just enough heart and retro party spirit to hold the line before familiarity breeds contempt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The mystery of Topher Grace's film career, and why it isn't better, continues with \"Take Me Home Tonight.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An amiable diversion, kept afloat by some comic moments of the raunchy, silly variety, and by something that does feel rather retro: a kindness to its youthful characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like a zippy lost treasure from the days of VHS and Duran Duran.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's an amiable but slow slice of nostalgia: think 'Hot Tub Time Machine' meets 'Superbad' - without the big laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This low-powered, amiable, stunningly unimportant movie is essentially one long, noisy party (set in two houses).</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Take Me Home Tonight\" is not a bad movie. In fact, it's pretty good. It's just unnecessary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's formulaic at best - and even that formula isn't always thought through.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Drinking jokes. Sex jokes. Wild antics. Sincere looks. Nothing goes on here that hasn't gone on -- and gone on better -- in other movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A dirge of a comedy...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>After the gimmick begins to fade, what remains is less than likable characters inhabiting an all-too-familiar plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It tries hard, but it always falls short.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>They speak entirely in plot points and punchlines and seem to be motivated only by lust, greed and ego. Well, we all are, but few bring to this motivation so little intelligence and wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A reasonably watchable immersion in nostalgia.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>very last joke in the movie -- verbal gags, visual gags, musical cues, camera moves -- is crushingly literal.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It, like, totally pains me to say this, but Take Me Home Tonight is a bummer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[The] trite boy-meets-girl arc (he lies about his job) is occasionally offset by some potent comic misadventures.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>'Take Me Home Tonight' has just enough heart and retro party spirit to hold the line before familiarity breeds contempt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The mystery of Topher Grace's film career, and why it isn't better, continues with \"Take Me Home Tonight.\"</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An amiable diversion, kept afloat by some comic moments of the raunchy, silly variety, and by something that does feel rather retro: a kindness to its youthful characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like a zippy lost treasure from the days of VHS and Duran Duran.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You've just kidnapped the wrong teenager, Mister Foreign Slave Trader Man.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taken is the kind of exploitative junk everyone expects from no-talent French hack Luc Besson.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Neeson's] performance is the most perturbing thing in the film, even more so than its electrical-torture sequence or its revelations about sex-trafficking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's the big, dolorous Neeson who makes the movie a keeper.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Don't be taken in by Taken.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With some suspension of disbelief and a strong stomach, it's possible to get taken in, or at least absorbed, by this adrenaline-pumping action thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You'll miss out on a good movie if you consider Taken just another January dumping.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If a movie's high points are a quick smack of carnage and a steely speech that everyone's already seen in the trailer, you know it must be January.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I won't tell you Taken is great, but it's great fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Director] Morel keeps Taken moving swiftly. It's never dragged down by excess feelings; instead, it's powered by the potency of the right ones.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Some movies flirt with absurdity. Taken takes it to bed, and then out for waffles in the morning.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Next out of the January dreg-u-lator: A Liam Neeson thriller so lacking in ambition they should have called it Paycheck.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taken starts in low gear and almost immediately stalls out.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Neeson's better than this.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film flirts with saying something dark and serious about pursuing justice through unjust means, then quickly chickens out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taken is nonsense, but it's terrifically entertaining nonsense, especially in the midst of the January movie doldrums. It provides the reckless thrills that Quantum of Solace lacked.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A sloppy, lazy, unintentionally laughable sequel.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A meta-American movie, a Godardian spoof of the whole genre, an attempt to see how stupid and insulting a motion picture can be and still be a big hit.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So lazily put together that it relies on flashbacks from its predecessor for the majority of its character development.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As much as this picture is action driven, its greatest delights are grounded in personality, in the fun of having a protagonist who combines homespun values with velociraptor functionality.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Neeson is once again the stalwart center of this giddy, entirely improbable and improbably enjoyable escapade.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A sequel every bit as clumsy, ham-handed, outlandish and laughable as the original was sleek, tough and efficient.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There doesn't seem to be a whole lot at stake in a movie where you can crash your way through the armed barricades at the American embassy with a stolen taxicab and survive without a scratch.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The one thing that comes across is Neeson's character really likes fighting Albanians.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Just a mediocre action franchise with a solid actor at the head and a travelogue in its heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first thing to be kidnapped is logic, as the action moves to Istanbul from Paris and Liam Neeson ridiculously reprises his role of avenging ex-CIA dad Bryan Mills.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As they might say in the advertising department, it's an adrenaline-fueled thrill ride. But it could have been much more.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Neeson's] acting makes him seem human and even vulnerable, someone we can't help but worry over even though it's those feckless Albanians we should be nervous about.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Seems like a nonstop car and foot chase, with Albanian after Albanian falling victim to Bryan's remarkable aim and hand-fighting skills.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rigorously formulaic and far-fetched ...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Why an actor of Neeson's ability would play this character once, let alone twice, is a mystery for the ages.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If a viewer enjoyed the exotic locale and fast-paced action in the original film, here they get a different city and even more amped-up happenings, with a plot that intrigues enough to reel a viewer in.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Laughable subplots about Elba's addicted sister (Marianne Jean-Baptiste) and Dillon's crooked partner (Jay Hernandez) only slow the action, which is all this movie has going for it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not terrible, but undemanding.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>as long as you understand exactly what kind of hack cinema you are getting into, Takers can be pretty fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Director John Luessenhop's aggressive approach to action scenes is frequently inspired.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With no emotional heft to the performances, it's hard to care whether anyone's dreams are dashed or fulfilled. That leaves the heist itself to compensate, but it only digs deeper into tired action movie cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Someone has to say it, so I will: Shaky cam is out of control.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Once you get past the recycled quality of the characters and dialogue, the movie has some stylish action sequences and moderately clever plot turns.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Takers is a slick heist film, but that's all it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At least they do look sharp in those suits.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Conceived and executed with just enough skill and flair to make you wish it were better.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Luessenhop and his antic camera are after a kineticism that eludes them: He shoots too closely; he's practically crawling up his characters' nostrils with his unhinged camera.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A Michael Mann-ish heist thriller with a pulse-pounding foot chase and some terrific stunt work offsetting its hackneyed plot and dialogue.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's hard to imagine anyone who sees the movie not being at least moderately engaged.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The screenplay is credited to four writers, director John Luessenhop among them, and they've all been busy cutting-and-pasting from other movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Amidst the gangsta posing and some overly operatic shootouts, [Dillon] helps give Takers some crucial currency.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even with all of the action, and with a few plot twists that are kinda cool, there's really not enough to Takers to make it worth your time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The dialogue is cliched and laughable. It's a film far more concerned with style -- architectural, vehicular and wardrobe-related -- than substance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Takers might have made a perfectly decent little B heist movie, but someone had to go and forget to give the cameraman his Ritalin.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The performers are given stock types to play, and Elba and Dillon, at least, can do a little with that.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A crackling crime drama assembled from a scrap heap of hoary cliches, Takers proves that everything old can sometimes really be new again.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A hallucinatory thriller anchored by a deeply resonant sense of unease.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>When future film historians look back at the cultural fallout from America's financial collapse, 'Take Shelter' will be a key text. That is, if the storm doesn't sweep us all away.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Shannon wonderfully modulates Nichols' portrait of a man whose mind and life seem to unravel before our eyes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a strong, unsettling sense of disease that runs through Take Shelter, the best drama of the year so far.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Shannon is astounding, playing a good man pushed to the brink of sanity, maybe beyond. He portrays a sense of quiet desperation -- a feeling recognizable to many.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Take Shelter is paced slowly and deliberately, which is necessary to make believable whatever is tormenting Curtis.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A work of hushed and persuasive emotional veracity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movies have long been mad about the onset of madness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's so stunningly effective at establishing a sense of dread that it's almost impossible to recommend it without reservations.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The chilling genius of \"Take Shelter'' isn't that the threat is never specified but that it doesn't need to be.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie for this moment in time, this moment in our lives.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie makes you uncomfortable, but in a good way. Nichols has turned the current moment of American unease into a powerful metaphor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story of a man afflicted with fearful visions, Take Shelter is a film that's hitting the right apocalyptic trumpet call at the right time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taut, unsettling, haunting and powerful, \"Take Shelter\" stars Michael Shannon in a shattering performance as a man caught up in forces beyond his control.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The really chilling thing is how believable it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a film without suspense and with a slow-moving story that unfolds without surprise or embellishment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A molar-grinding performance from Michael Shannon anchors this slow but ultimately haunting drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Here is a frightening thriller based not on special effects gimmicks but on a dread that seems quietly spreading in the land: that the good days are ending, and climate changes or other sinister forces will sweep away our safety.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Writer-director Jeff Nichols, whose previous film Shotgun Stories also starred Shannon, has the rare ability to think big and work small.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nichols approaches his subject with thoughtful empathy, and while his themes are enormous - he's addressing no less than the state of our nation - he wisely underplays even the most important moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While their transformation is predictable, it's quietly enjoyable, and the teen angle opens the door to romance and gritty gang-war subplots.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>it's just ridiculous, it's just ridiculous. One cliche right after another. Not for one second did I believe any of this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While we may be able to pretty much guess everything that's going to happen in Take the Lead, its considerable charm lies in the way it fulfills, rather than bucks, our expectations.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Think of it as the fictionalized version of last year's engaging documentary Mad Hot Ballroom, with teen dancers and sexier moves. It is also more formulaic and cliched, thanks to the predictable plot and theme.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Take the Lead is pure entertainment, if only for the endless amusement of watching Banderas spread the gospel of ballroom like he was born wearing a tuxedo.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A predictable and yet thoroughly enjoyable drama about the redemptive power of dance for a group of inner-city teenagers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Although based on a true story, Take the Lead continually strains credibility.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of the year's most uninspired inspirational stories.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a ballroom/hip-hop mash-up that, although at times discordant and at all times familiar, moves with Banderas' brio and bounce.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cute as a boutonniere and bouncy as a swing beat, Take the Lead is an 'inspired by a true story' spin on Mad Hot Ballroom.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The performances deserve applause. The script is another story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like the recent Glory Road, Take the Lead tweaks a true story to sell more tickets. But at what point do movies like this one begin to fuel the racial hatred that they ostensibly deplore?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Take the Lead is like that -- it may seem hokey, but it uses the tried and true to get a smile out of you every time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like its star, the movie verges on hooey but cuts too stylish a swath to dislike for long.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Si, Antonio is a charming man, but by the final bows the movie around him is all left feet and bruised angles, and much more of a farrago than a fandango.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What slop. Take the Lead is a rotted ground chuck of a movie, made up of the rancid processed parts of a plethora of films, good and bad, that have come before it. At first it seems awfully familiar, and then it just seems awful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A well-made if utterly unsurprising movie, which has its feet and its heart in the right place.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>You could go out and see this feel-good facsimile and be moderately entertained, or rent Mad Hot Ballroom and feel yourself becoming genuinely moved by the real thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Take the Lead is the latest example of a silly and utterly predictable movie where the kids dance in the streets and we pray for a fleet of Humvees to come along and run them out of town.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As sweet and well-meaning as parts of the movie are, the filmmakers don't appear to trust their teenage audience to take this world seriously.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A hard-headed, generous film about love.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Polley (who's been an actress herself) never judges these people she's created. Instead, she depicts the giddy, fleeting and illusory nature of new love, and lets us get caught up in it, too.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No one's a cliche; no one speaks dialogue the viewer could have muttered a beat or two ahead of the movie; no one hews to a mode of behavior fabricated to explain away his or her irrational behavior.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[It] often feels thin and self-conscious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Williams lives and breathes her role, Kirby is charming and real, and you actually start to ache and empathize with Rogen - the emptiness and heartache he conveys when Lou and Margot finally thrash things out is crushing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Both the small moments and the end product of Waltz are quietly sublime.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If uncompromising honesty is the quality you seek for a film, Michelle Williams is your go-to star.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Polley wonders the same thing in nearly every scene, no matter who's in it. Is a comfortable marriage really marriage enough?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I have great admiration for [Williams] as an actress, but this story might have been better told with a less lovable star.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Margot comes across as such an elusive and unsympathetic twit that you wonder why we should care about her.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In the end, it's a story of misplaced faith. In what? Not love exactly, but in the rush of infatuation, and the illusion that this feeling can be maintained, indefinitely, without crashing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At its worst, Polley's style veers toward the cornball. Yet, in the broad outlines of her story, she has clearly created something with a lot of hard truth.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Take This Waltz and shove it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Somehow it is the waiting - for the fall that you expect is coming, for the marriage you figure will fall apart - that makes \"Take This Waltz\" one to make room for on your dance card.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A color-drenched story of lust, love, and infidelity, it suffers from a vagueness that may be the point but that feels accidental.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In \"Take This Waltz,\" Polley doesn't fill the gap. She just makes life on either side of it both attractive and a drag.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Unfortunately for Polley, Take This Waltz is a good film serving mainly to remind us that Away From Her is a great one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Your best option, perhaps, is to zone out from the implausible kinks in the setup... This will leave you free to savor the compositions and the melted-candy color schemes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This romantic drama, starring the always-extraordinary Michelle Williams as a restless married woman contemplating an affair with her neighbor, is chock-full of individual moments of great power and beauty, including visual beauty.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Boasts many keenly felt moments, but it's never quite more than the sum of its admittedly tender parts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you can buy the pillow-lipped Angelina Jolie as a psychic FBI agent in Montreal to hunt a serial killer, then you can swallow the other implausibilities in this retread thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Jolie is far too good for this tripe but she does give the film its only believable moments, and for the first half, her concentration makes you watch her intently.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nosedive it does, abandoning all pretense of style and eccentricity for at-times laughable predictability.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Would have to work nights to reach mediocrity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While not breaking any new ground, director D.J. Caruso's movie also doesn't disappoint.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Caruso is a much more resourceful director than this material deserves, but I resented being two steps ahead of the genius profiler and the genius serial-killer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taking Lives is often style over substance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To buy this picture, you have to buy Jolie's character, and the actress succeeds much of the time. But once her contained, job-obsessed agent gets involved with a man close to her case, much of what came before is negated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taking Lives is a good, near-great film that might seem a lot better if it hadn't been preceded by all of those Judd vehicles -- or if Jodie Foster's Clarice Starling never existed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While it's not in a league with The Silence of the Lambs, it works in a similarly efficient way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Just as the central criminal steals the identity of his victims, Taking Lives lifts traits and style from other movies. Both do so relatively successfully, until they bungle the job in the final half-hour.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taking Lives is smarter than your average serial-killer movie, thanks to unusually fleshed-out characters inhabited by a high- pedigree cast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Screenwriter Jon Bokenkamp litters the trajectory with more red herrings than the traffic can bear in less than two hours.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even with Angelina Jolie thrown in for forensic sex appeal, this dog won't hunt.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first nine minutes of Taking Lives are, in fact, compelling and good ... Sadly, the rest of Taking Lives is not worth paying for.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's slick nonsense at best and for the first hour it's watchable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Best of all, it doesn't star Ashley Judd, who has made a wearying specialty out of playing tough-tender female cops. Danger-prone Angelina Jolie is on the case here -- an improvement that pays big dividends throughout.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taking Lives isn't bad, really, it just isn't distinctive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Forman's specialty is tender farce played out in what are, essentially, very bleak circumstances.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An engaging, episodic, wonderfully fair-minded satire about runaway children and anxious adults.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Forman's career pivot point between Prague's film-school halls and the Oscars podium is still a prime example of the way a foreign director can apply an outsider's perspective to something like Nixon's Amerikkka and draw blood.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It remains his [Milos Forman's] best film in and about America.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This may be a minor movie, but it displays the hallmarks of a major talent.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ang Lee's companionable 'Taking Woodstock' is thick with sun and good cheer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too much of Taking Woodstock seems barely sketched out.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's harmless enough as a snapshot of a young man's awakening to the grand possibilities of adult life, but not particularly effective at capturing the spirit, the thrill or even the mud of this culturally monumental event.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is very light material, and, unusually for a Lee picture, not everybody in the ensemble appears to be acting in the same universe, let alone the same story. On the other hand: It's fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taking Woodstock has the appeal of an inside story told from an especially good angle. But beyond that, the movie is a celebration of the way this event has gone into memory and of the meaning it has acquired.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's great that Taking Woodstock doesn't trample on anything sacred, but it also never arrives anywhere interesting.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lee's first total miscalculation, his first wholly inessential film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Can you dig it? Maybe, if you aren't already up to your tie-dyed shorts in Woodstock memories, and if you can accept that there's relatively little music in this happy-go-lucky movie about history's most celebrated music festival.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If this Woodstock comes off as Edenic... don't assume the movie's advertising the real thing. Think of it as Ang Lee taking a vacation from too much reality.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taking Woodstock is hardly a bad trip; just a very inconsequential one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee's larkiest film by far, Taking Woodstock features faces familiar and fresh.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taking Woodstock fails to achieve anything beyond a contact high because of Martin's listless performance as the central character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The drama in question, Ang Lee's Taking Woodstock, is a bit like the festival itself - a happy mess.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Taking Woodstock has fine moments and an enjoyable vibe, but it never develops a coherent point of view.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taking Woodstock has its pleasures; it's really a sweet-natured coming-of-age tale, with a famously groundbreaking rock concert lurking in the background.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you stick with this wistful, fitfully funny little trip, you will be rewarded with a movie that makes up in warmth, humanism and self-effacing modesty what it lacks in crackerjack pacing and epic pop-historical grandeur.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee distills the flavor of this transforming event and hints at how it transformed some who were there. His movie is a contact high.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film grabs on tight and doesn't let go.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ultimately the movie's many strands come together for a final twist, but it's too little too late for this regrettably mediocre Bollywood import.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kapoor naturally exudes a kittenish charm that not even a violet, skintight, leopard-print dress and equally purple dialogue can entirely diminish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's very much a Hindi film, but updated and delivered with conviction and style.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A workmanlike, humorless cartoon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If this starchy, nearly two-hour allegory about human hubris bluntly addresses a historical moment when global warming threatens the planet and pollution is fouling the seas, its chilly, formal tone keeps you at an emotional distance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Miyazaki legacy is in good hands.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The themes and memorable imagery in Earthsea will be familiar to fans of Studio Ghibli, but the storytelling and animation are a step behind.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a whole lot going on in the Japanese anime fantasy Tales From Earthsea, so why is it such a bore?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Abstruse and confusing, Tales from Earthsea's story grows increasingly blurry the closer it gets to what should be a deeply satisfying conclusion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Soon sinks into a bog of overly murky narrative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The sights and sounds are splendid...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Earthsea seems to be a stupendously dull place. It would try the patience of any kid.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hardly a groundbreaking work, but still a worthy addition to the singular Ghibli canon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Harrison never quite transcends the inherently limited format.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>hanks to casting that is savvier than the horror norm, and to direction by John Harrison that is workmanlike and sometimes even witty, at least it's fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is just another miss along the lines of Creepshow and Twilight Zone: The Movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Whatever else you might say about this weird, creepy, and funny independent item by Guy Maddin, it's certainly different.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a thin line between weird and strange, and Maddin's debut falls just the wrong side.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is a strange piece of work.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Talk Radio...is a nearly perfect example of how not to make a movie of a play.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's midnight in America and there's a lot of angry people out there in the darkness. If that's the main point to Oliver Stone's Talk Radio, it's the only one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talk Radio has the loony intensity of those impassioned conspiracy theorists who look out at the world and see patterns of corruption spreading in all directions...it's another of Stone's wake-up calls to America.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talk Radio is directed by Stone with a claustrophobic intensity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In its wrenching shift from farce to tragedy, and its evocation of the bridge offered by friendship, Talk to Me tells it, and keeps on tellin' it, much as 'Petey' Greene would have.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Thanks to its two leads, the film remains vivid, honest and deeply felt.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Speaks powerfully to audiences with its potent blend of extraordinary performances and engaging soundtrack.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie's occasional narrative shortcomings are offset by the performances, which are uniformly fine.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Its dialogue, equal parts uptight honky and jumping jive seems, particularly in the early stretches, to have been generated by a computer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The characters are brought to vivid life with remarkably compelling performances by two of the screen's most versatile actors: Don Cheadle as the freewheeling Greene; and Chiwetel Ejiofor as Hughes, the aggressively ambitious executive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cheadle gives a performance of contained cool and bluff bravado, suggesting barely a hint of the rage you would expect from a man just out of a nine-year prison sentence.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The problem is, the last section of the movie doesn't follow the career path of Greene: It traces the blander character of Hughes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] well-acted film about making the move from the street to the mainstream.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>he mood shifts awkwardly from broad comedy to melodrama and social commentary.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lemmons, her extraordinary cast and gifted crew deliver laughing, crying and plenty of signifying.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Don Cheadle has elevated yet another film: Talk to Me is better than it intends to be. But thank Ejiofor as well.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>... has a solid sense of time and place and character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talk to Me is more than enough fun as a showcase for Mr. Cheadle's wit and spontaneity and as an inside look at the airwaves' transition from warm and fuzzy comforter to the anything-goes entertainment of today.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brilliant, alcoholic and self-destructive, Greene is the fascinating subject of Kasi Lemmons's funky, RandB-driven biopic -- a vital entertainment that struts confidently between comedy and drama.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A very honest yet curiously affecting experience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching it becomes an exercise in frustration when a potentially great movie winds up buried inside a just OK one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A comedy with horsepower to spare.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'Talladega Nights': Deliciously Subversive Political Satire</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Broad but not crude, dumb but not witless, clever but still snot-spittingly funny. Stupidly brilliant, in other words.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the stupidest and one of the funniest movies in Will Ferrell's career.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Essentially a string of gags loosely looped together, a set of absurd situations for the actors to clown their way through, Talladega Nights is an affable entertainment, both a celebration and a satire of lowbrow pleasures.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talladega Nights may be brash, unbridled, even unhinged, but its cornpone humor is rich in parody, and its craftsmanship is superb.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the movie about a moronic NASCAR racer overall is uneven and Ricky Bobby's saga lacks focus, the stupid-comical banter and the lampooning of this particular brand of car racing proves entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Ferrell and his writing partner Adam McKay (who also directs, as he did Anchorman) are utterly without shame in their eagerness to recycle old ideas. This pair could make a blue box jealous.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The hilarious everyman riffs and contagious fun are reason enough to fuel up on such a wonderfully throwaway gag-fest.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talladega Nights is very funny at times, even if the Ballad part mostly boils down to a series of comedy sketches connected by a recurring character.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The picture gets a bit long near the finish. But comedies live and die on the basis of their laugh quotient, and Talladega Nights gets its share.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The laughs come and go, but Ferrell makes NASCAR his bitch funny. Funnier. And more fun. And then the fun skids to a stop.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ferrell reteams with director Adam McKay (Anchorman) for another gleefully trashy comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Whoo, mama: Will Ferrell and NASCAR do make a purty pair. They go together like peanut butter and fried bananas in Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>'What does diablo mean?' 'It's like Spanish for fighting chicken.' If you cracked so much as a shell of a smile reading that, then run, don't walk, to see Talladega Nights, where you will get an entire year's worth of equally irresistible nonsense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you can delight in the delight of others, you just may delight in this. Otherwise, prepare to be awfully jealous, because it's the sort of picture where the actors are having a lot more fun than the audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talladega is the first comedy this year to make me laugh so hard I snorted.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby is perfectly stupid chuckleheaded bliss, an achievement of the lowest and highest order. Every week should hold a movie like this.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's a whiff of desperation behind the comic romp Tamara Drewe that gives it some unexpected sting.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This screen adaptation by director Stephen Frears successfully re-creates the strip's pastoral tone and cheeky humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film lacks Frears' usual master touch; it often feels flat and self-conscious, in a way that the book never does.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While no one would celebrate Tamara Drewe as a great movie, it is a reliable dispenser of visual and erotic pleasures.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You know where you're going in territory that's actually more Jane Austen than Hardy, but Frears makes the most of the many bumps and twists.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Caught midway between literary genres, the film lacks the literary sheen of Hardy and the darker comic impulses of Simmonds.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Erotic comedies are often attempted but rarely realized. Tamara Drewe is proof that sexy and funny need not be mutually exclusive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tamara Drewe is one in a million.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A bucolic romp set in a strikingly picturesque spot in England's Dorset County, it has its moments of charm. But the clever comedy it promises never really materializes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Go through your mental checklist of what you want in a romantic comedy-drama: novel plotting, characters to care about, witty dialogue, bull's-eye casting, nimble direction, green and pleasant locales, a lack of falling-in-love montages.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Here and there, tentatively, Frears and his design team approximate the pictorial flourishes of the graphic novel. But the ensemble appears to be guessing, much of the time, at a proper performance pitch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tamara Drewe is one of those British comedies in which, one way or another, we envy all of the characters -- even, briefly, the one run over by stampeding cows.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Don't let the English accents fool you - the characters are as thin as cartoons.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tamara Drewe is a frolic that keeps tripping over its own gorgeous feet.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's not even any biting satire on social mores or anything else. The laughs are as broad as the scenery is picturesque. The characters are types but the whole experience is agreeable enough.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It does not insult the intelligence of the audience -- on the contrary, it flatters the viewer's sense of sophistication without being at all esoteric or difficult -- and it is refreshingly candid about sex.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I surrendered midway through to the film, to the wayward torque of its plot and the near-perfect pitch of its acting ensemble.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A real old-fashioned crowd-pleaser.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tamara Drewe makes a strong case for rhinoplasty, and a stronger one for the pleasures of comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The whole thing more a vibrant mess than something comically disarming.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's the best Disney animation in years, and a natural counterpoint to the contemporary comic style that has come to dominate the industry.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The prettiness comes with brains, and the whole production, like those newly eye-catching models of American-made cars, bespeaks resurgent confidence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brisk, witty and entertaining, but far from classic Disney.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tangled is bound to be a hit with its target audience, and will keep parents entertained.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There are no unnecessary pop references here, just fluid, graceful storytelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As Disney animated features go, Tangled is middling</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Rapunzel, Rapunzel, you are lovely to look at it and occasionally charming. But there just ain't much to you beyond the hair.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The heart of Disney animation lies in song and spectacle, and while none of the musical compositions here are quite at the level of \"The Little Mermaid\" or \"Beauty and the Beast,\" they are good enough...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A solid if not-quite-classic musical version of \"Rapunzel\"...</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The delightfully witty Tangled is the first animated cartoon released by Walt Disney Pictures that can stand alongside Pixar toons without apology.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tangled braids strands of traditional storytelling and a contemporary sensibility with stylish if predictable results.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If \"Tangled\" hasn't morphed into a Broadway show within five years, then Disney isn't as smart as I think it is.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tangled is unusually attuned to the emotional frequencies of mothers and daughters, considering that, like basically every Disney/Pixar feature, its writer (Dan Fogelman) and directors (Nathan Greno and Byron Howard) are a bunch of dudes.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Adventure, ho! And much of it is quite funny, well scripted by screenwriter Dan Fogelman, who previously wrote Bolt and Cars.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A Rapunzel retelling could have become just a retread of the studio's past princess tales, but this genuinely charming, chintz-free story does something new: It takes the time to chill out, as its heroine might say.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Captures some of the best elements of Disney standards while nimbly integrating the clever pop-culture winks and dazzling technical style that are hallmarks of modern computer-animated features.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An uneven, convoluted, certainly dispute-provoking study of sexual passion in which Marlon Brando gives a truly remarkable performance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's Brando's film: his monologues devastate.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie is sad, but it's also hugely funny, occasionally when it doesn't mean to be.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The look, feel and sound of the film are evocative.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A mindless buddy cop pic, loaded with nonstop action that's played mostly for laughs and delivers too few of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What makes this shoot-'em-up nonsense surprisingly watchable is Randy Feldman's rapid-fire dialogue, which constantly undercuts the macho posturings while parodying Stallone's screen image.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all practical purposes, there is no plot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>More like My Beautiful Laundrette in the closet than it is a bad ripoff of Lethal Weapon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An aspiring cult film that would rather be cute than dangerous.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie version of the graphic comic book is a classic case of kitchen-sink filmmaking, in which the principals have thrown everything into the stew, hoping enough will stick to the audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Generous souls may try to blame this travesty of the Deadline comic-strip on the studio execs who forced director Talalay to tone down and re-edit her cut.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Chief among its strong points is Lori Petty, a buzz-cut fashion plate in a Prozac necklace, who brings the necessary gusto to Tank Girl's flippancy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Tank Girl is as disorienting as waking up in someone else's bad dream. You want to get out as fast as possible, but all the exits seem to be blocked.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story, which feels like a disjointed collection of low-budget rock videos more than a coherent plot, just rocks idly on its pseudo-fashionable backside.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The result is a bracing film that's halfway between a string of MTV videos (Courtney Love put together the edgy soundtrack) and some of that network's over-the-top cartoons.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of those chew-the-popcorn, munch-the-candy flicks - - the kind you go into expecting to have a good time, but nothing more. Given those expectations, disappointment is as unlikely as boredom.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Enormous energy went into this movie. I could not, however, care about it for much more than a moment at a time, and after awhile its manic energy wore me down.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An aspiring cult film that would rather be cute than dangerous.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie version of the graphic comic book is a classic case of kitchen-sink filmmaking, in which the principals have thrown everything into the stew, hoping enough will stick to the audience.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Generous souls may try to blame this travesty of the Deadline comic-strip on the studio execs who forced director Talalay to tone down and re-edit her cut.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Chief among its strong points is Lori Petty, a buzz-cut fashion plate in a Prozac necklace, who brings the necessary gusto to Tank Girl's flippancy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Watching Tank Girl is as disorienting as waking up in someone else's bad dream. You want to get out as fast as possible, but all the exits seem to be blocked.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story, which feels like a disjointed collection of low-budget rock videos more than a coherent plot, just rocks idly on its pseudo-fashionable backside.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The result is a bracing film that's halfway between a string of MTV videos (Courtney Love put together the edgy soundtrack) and some of that network's over-the-top cartoons.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of those chew-the-popcorn, munch-the-candy flicks - - the kind you go into expecting to have a good time, but nothing more. Given those expectations, disappointment is as unlikely as boredom.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Enormous energy went into this movie. I could not, however, care about it for much more than a moment at a time, and after awhile its manic energy wore me down.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A painful attempt to satirize the making of rock videos that runs aground with a puerile plot and bombastic, self-infatuated delivery.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's all good fun: likeable performances, unpretentious, larky direction, and a haphazard story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The amiable screenplay by Mr. Fishman and Peter McCarthy is often funny, and never worse than silly.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The irony is that nothing Fishman and his cohorts have come up with is really as funny as a two-hour slice of MTV itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All of these elements have been lifted off the shelf of exhausted cliches, given a quick dusting, and plugged directly into the movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film has to fly by its wits -- and its witty lines -- and by the charm of its stars. This it does, just barely.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's never a good idea to cast Bill Nighy as a buttoned-down hit man.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Practically a text book in how ugly things can get when you don't have the right, light touch for this sort of thing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There have been a lot of black comedies about assassins lately -- there have been a few just this year -- but Wild Target may be the first one to contain genuine laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An eccentric little comic thriller filled with enough laughs that I was mostly willing to overlook the fact that it makes virtually no sense as a thriller.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All of this busyness drains away the film's charm, turning what might have been a naughty and whimsical frolic into something glib, hectic and sour.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Since irony is so often director Jonathan Lynn's weapon of choice, Wild Target should have been a good fit. It's not quite.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Wild Target takes aim at various styles and genres and misses the mark every time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nothing works.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's entertainment designed to resemble a good time without aspiring to provide one.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Wild Target is the kind of movie that actually uses that angry-cat-yowl sound. That is the kind of movie that Wild Target is.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[An] unlovable, seldom funny Brit comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Attractive and charismatic actors can do nothing to save a movie that's charmless, pointless and witless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Nothing feels like it's been properly thought through, highlighted by the fact that Nighy's 'super assassin' goes about his business by merely opening fire on a crowded market place (using a silencer, of course!).</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The endlessly repetitive fusillades suggest that Writer-Director Peter Bogdanovich, in his first film, was really intent on creating the most prolific murderer in Hollywood's long history of violence. Unfortunately, it is a record made to be broken.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Aware of the virtue of implied violence, Bogdanovich conveys moments of shock, terror, suspense and fear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fascinatingly complex commentary on American mythology, exploring the relationship between the inner world of the imagination and the outer world of violence and paranoia, both of which were relevant to contemporary American traumas.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Targets scores an unnerving bullseye.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Targets isn't a very good film, but it is an interesting one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An interesting response to the demands of low-budget genre filmmaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The mise en scene is beautifully modulated and the performances -- by Emil Jannings, Lil Dagover, and Werner Krauss, among others -- are first-rate.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Whatever else may be said about it, the picture is heavy and primitive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The stylized physiques and movements of the characters in this exciting animated musical-romance-adventure are at once realist and fantastic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>No classic, but very enjoyable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Simply a smashingly well-done example of animated storytelling.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's both a little scary and a lot funny, and kids will no doubt lap it up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>So far, the most entertaining film of the year.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Travels light, moves quickly and leaves very little in its wake.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Minnie Driver gives Jane a throaty, teasing allure that suggests nights in the jungle won't be Disney dull for the T-man.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A rambunctious, visually arresting, occasionally poignant musical adventure!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though it relinquishes some of Disney's toehold on an adult audience for animation, Tarzan is sprightly and likable in ways that are hard to resist.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Entertaining and spectacular!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tarzan will thrill and inspire children and their parents alike.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Disney's Tarzan is animation gold!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Adroit vocal casting, an entertaining script, an unexpectedly energetic soundtrack, and some splendid technical breakthroughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Disney's most elegant animated 'classic' in years!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perhaps Disney thought the best way to get around the ooga-booga stereotype was to eliminate blacks altogether.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Disney's Tarzan is not only the summer's most thrilling mainstream movie so far, it's also the best animated feature the studio has put out since The Lion King.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Tarzan is both lush and bustling!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tarzan is the cinematic equivalent of a Cajun McChicken sandwich - it's a little bit bold, a little bit spicy, and a whole lot of McMovie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Something deep within the Tarzan myth speaks to us, and Disney's new animated Tarzan captures it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The picture has a strange sort of power that overcomes the total lack of logic.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Aside from the wild tale, this film is a marvel from a photographic standpoint.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This opus will disappoint both Tarzan fans and Bo admirers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Judging by the amount of time everybody spends swimming, the African jungle resembles Hornsey Baths filled with oversized pot plants.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Of course it's completely ridiculous, but at the same time it has a certain disarming charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To describe the film as inept would be to miss the point, which is to present Mrs. Derek in as many different poses, nude and seminude, as there are days of the year, all in something less than two hours.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This opus will disappoint both Tarzan fans and Bo admirers.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Judging by the amount of time everybody spends swimming, the African jungle resembles Hornsey Baths filled with oversized pot plants.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Of course it's completely ridiculous, but at the same time it has a certain disarming charm.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>To describe the film as inept would be to miss the point, which is to present Mrs. Derek in as many different poses, nude and seminude, as there are days of the year, all in something less than two hours.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Appropriately languid and uniquely seductive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Has a visual style that seems rudimentary but becomes increasingly hypnotic and resonant.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is such a lifeless drone that we experience it only as a movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The talk flows persuasively; the picture pulses with art and humanity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kiarostami is in no rush, but the respect and love he shows for his characters, and the confidence and simplicity of his technique, make Taste of Cherry a satisfying experience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Kiarastomi, like no other filmmaker, has a vision of human scale that is simultaneously epic and precisely minuscule.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As the film's design becomes clear to us, a quiet spaciousness begins to inhabit it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A vivid portrait that should satisfy aficionados and intrigue the curious. Ink-averse viewers, however, may remain unsold.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Bickle is complex, intriguing and never one-note.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like Werner Herzog's Aguirre or Coppola's Apocalypse Now, Taxi Driver is auteurist psychodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Scorsese] seems to need scripts with well-designed humor and performers with the spirit of Ellen Burstyn to compensate for what seems to be a fundamentally depressed view of life and the belief that sobriety is the equivalent of seriousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>New York may have changed, but Taxi Driver is as powerful and painful as ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Martin Scorsese's history-making scald is truly a phenomenon from another day and age. Which is to say, imagine a like-minded film of this decade killing at the box office and getting nommed for Best Picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You may want to argue with Taxi Driver at the end, and with good reason, but it won't be a waste of time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a powerful film and a terrific showcase for the versatility of star Robert De Niro</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The heart and soul of Taxi Driver are twisted in a way that can't be faked or copied.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the best and most powerful of all films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A masterful psychological study, the depth of which can only fully be appreciated on repeat viewings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Bickle is complex, intriguing and never one-note.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like Werner Herzog's Aguirre or Coppola's Apocalypse Now, Taxi Driver is auteurist psychodrama.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Scorsese] seems to need scripts with well-designed humor and performers with the spirit of Ellen Burstyn to compensate for what seems to be a fundamentally depressed view of life and the belief that sobriety is the equivalent of seriousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>New York may have changed, but Taxi Driver is as powerful and painful as ever.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Martin Scorsese's history-making scald is truly a phenomenon from another day and age. Which is to say, imagine a like-minded film of this decade killing at the box office and getting nommed for Best Picture.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You may want to argue with Taxi Driver at the end, and with good reason, but it won't be a waste of time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a powerful film and a terrific showcase for the versatility of star Robert De Niro</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The heart and soul of Taxi Driver are twisted in a way that can't be faked or copied.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the best and most powerful of all films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A masterful psychological study, the depth of which can only fully be appreciated on repeat viewings.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[A] strong current of humour belies a serious engagement with the general, perhaps intractable problem of whether our impulses toward intimacy and unaccountability can ever be reconciled.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An intelligent look at a time when the old guard of tough-talking gumshoes and snappy reporters were about to surrender to a new breed: educated and self-aware men and women.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An intelligent look at a time when the old guard of tough-talking gumshoes and snappy reporters were about to surrender to a new breed: educated and self-aware men and women.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Slow-moving.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Teaching Mrs. Tingle an ugly, failed attempt to pull off a Heathers - style, teen - oriented black comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Depressing!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A wildly uneven and sloppily directed movie, full of clashing tones and undigested bits of superior films.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a routinely cruel, often vicious, miserably unhappy teacher, Mirren offers a complex, brilliantly disciplined performance!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Newly benign, and noticeably clumsy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie needs a few more ideas and a lot more thrills to excite viewers, whether young or old.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The lack of surprises, plot twists, and clever dialogue makes this a distressingly lame offering.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Contains enough amusing moments and unpredictable twists for the film to score with teen audiences.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A pat, hollow exercise!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Spiteful and shallow!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Wholly predictable and implausible plotting, thin characterizations, and stilted dialogue!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There is nothing funny about the situation in Teaching Mrs. Tingle.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Teaching Mrs. Tingle is funny, smart and full of unpredictable twists and turns.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Teaching Mrs. Tingle reveals Williamson not only to be as accomplished a director as he is a writer but also his willingness to move beyond horror to psychological suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A screenful of nothingness!</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A good mix of the nostalgic and the brand-new!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even a fantasy, whoever it's for, has to have a plot that minimally makes sense, characters that make decisions based on coherent personalities, and a consistent tone. Unfortunately, Teaching Mrs. Tingle lacks all three.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A dull assignment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Juvenile in the worst sense: confused and frightened by the adult world, and begging to be protected.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first work from Parker and Stone that I'd describe as a failure of nerve.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I thought it was pretty clever.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Team America is at once grandiose and tacky, elaborate and deflationary.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Profane and sometimes bitingly funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Team America is not as funny as the South Park movie, and some of its juvenile humor falls flat. But when Team America works, it falls squarely into the category of guilty pleasure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Funny string-driven action satire.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I laughed all the way through Team America.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Parker-Stone fans are likely to have a grand time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>As puppetry, Team America is stilted. As satire, it's gutless and lazy. And as comedy, it barely delivers laughs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The irreverent duo plays it surprisingly safe here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Outrageously, gut-bustingly hilarious.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's rude and raunchy, and it has a message -- sort of. You have to wade through an awful lot of obscenity to get to it, though.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sophomoric, vulgar, obscene and brilliant.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It may be one of the strangest pieces of entertainment to hit multiplexes in some time, but in terms of its politics, it's one of the sanest.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Consistently hilarious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Caustic fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It may not tell you who you should vote for, but Team America: World Police conclusively proves everything is funnier when it's done by marionettes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Will a thinking audience really buy the image of helpless, grateful people bestowing kisses and victory songs upon Willis as the representative of all things American: power, guts, compassion?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Deserves the bad reviews and the lackluster earnings it has accumulated thus far.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Raping and pillaging and blowing things up is mainly what this movie is about, although it claims to show how the most robotic, dehumanized soldiers can be transformed by human suffering.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Fuqua ... can stage action, but he can't save a trivializing, reactionary script featuring a Hollywood star (read America) as a global savior.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This Black Hawk Down theft is a trial by cliche.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In a movie with so much graphic suffering by innocent Africans, it's a bit disconcerting that so much loving attention is paid to Bruce Willis's anguished mug.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie should have been called Crocodile Tears of the Sun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is a strictly no-bull proposition.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie might have gotten a dramatic boost from its topical theme, indirect as it is. Unfortunately, it's not one-tenth as interesting as what you can see at home during a nightly cable surf as U.S. war policy is debated.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If you ever wanted a reason to root for a righteous invasion, this sequence -- like My Lai but improved because it's perpetrated by the bad guys -- provides it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If it were better done, Tears would be offensive: the villains are evil, faceless, baby-murdering Muslims. But the movie is so shoddy and one-dimensional that it's just a dreary, predictably violent bore.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Propaganda doesn't get any more entertaining.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>At its best, it's a little hard to sit through. At its worst, it's like every other picture about soldiers on a tough mission. What pushes it above mediocrity is that it ends better than it begins.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film may have been inspired by The Seachers, but it's worlds away from John Wayne.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tears of the Sun has a title that makes no sense whatsoever. The film's message, on the other hand, makes too much sense -- it's simplistic and reactionary and designed to get hearts pumping but not minds thinking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Willis' performance redeems much of the film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Painfully obvious, yet confusing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sure, MacFarlane, you can make us laugh, but it's time to grow up. Seriously.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Everything goes on too long -- Ted's carousing, Lori's watchful waiting, John's wistful indecision.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a goofy premise pursued with crass -- as well as sentimental -- relish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You'll feel the warmth and camaraderie of a Bostonian and his little sentient bear.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I tried to resist but couldn't.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The idea of a toy that comes to life - and then won't go away - isn't a bad one. Too bad that \"Ted\" manages to overstay its welcome without ever really coming to life itself.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As unabashedly idiotic movie comedies go, Ted goes fairly well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>\"Ted\" is so lazy you want to kick the stuffing out of it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Underneath the matted fur of the movie's foul-mouthed bear beats a very real heart.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I expected \"Ted\" to be a one-joke movie, but it's got ideas spilling out of its seams.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What began as a promising, if unhinged, experiment in suspending disbelief starts to feel like \"You, Me and Dupree\" for plushies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In a universe of Hollywood comedies that seem determined to insult the audience and pander to the basest form of post-adolescent fantasy, \"Ted\" feels almost sophisticated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The natural interactions between Ted and his beloved man-child owner, John, terrifically played as an adult by Mark Wahlberg, are more often than not ridiculously funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Ted's real trick is turning a one-joke premise into a reasonable facsimile of a movie, and one that isn't entirely bent on grossing us out.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all of its transgressive plush-toy sex and screw-'em humor, the plot is pretty standard stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>To fully appreciate \"Ted,\" it's best to simply forgive its bad behavior upfront and save any apologies for liking it until later. Sorry.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I'm betting on Mark Wahlberg for best actor when the Oscars swing around next year.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Not every joke scores, of course. But the hits are worth the misses, and anyway, the movie's true genius is in the way its outlandish scenario is played so perfectly straight.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You can overlook an awful lot in a comedy when it makes you laugh.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A dismal, tedious affair.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Scores with its generally engaging tongue-in-cheek humor.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The results are high-spirited martial arts and comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is itself a mutant of sorts, a contentious, unsightly hybrid of martial-arts exploitation film and live-action cartoon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Between the dubbed dialogue and the dark visuals, the cumulative effect is curiously dislocating.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Parents can vaguely console themselves, however, that amid the kiddie pollution available on Saturday morning TV, the Turtles rank slightly better than the rest.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This movie is nowhere near as bad as it might have been, and probably is the best possible Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Truth be told, there's something amusingly surreal in watching these happy-go-lucky, man-sized terps engage in full-scale punch-and-kick-outs with the inevitable villains.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A decided case of diminishing returns.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The wisecracks have been cut back, and where once the Ninjas' dude-speak was original (influencing, for example, Wayne's World) it's now merely imitative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Turtles themselves are better-natured than ever, and even nicely mellowed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If the first sequel was a photocopy of the original, this second sequel is a tracing of a photocopy. It's the same business twice removed, and twice diminished.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first film was bad, the second worse, and the third almost unbearable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A decided case of diminishing returns.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The wisecracks have been cut back, and where once the Ninjas' dude-speak was original (influencing, for example, Wayne's World) it's now merely imitative.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Turtles themselves are better-natured than ever, and even nicely mellowed.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If the first sequel was a photocopy of the original, this second sequel is a tracing of a photocopy. It's the same business twice removed, and twice diminished.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first film was bad, the second worse, and the third almost unbearable.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Neither as fun nor as faithful to the spirit of the original comics. It's a bigger, slicker movie, but not a better one.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The murky lighting, uninteresting human characters and violence of the original have been modified in the more amiable sequel, mostly to good effect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One can have a reasonably amusing time with this predictable sequel, which is a bit longer on action and shorter on wit and character than the original.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The bigger budget is a blessing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Turtles, when not battling Shredder or providing Vanilla Ice with the basis for a rap number, kid around in enjoyable ways.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Next time, if the Turtles really want to hurt 'em, they should call on Hammer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The second TMNT has enough jokes aimed at adults to make for a relatively painless outing for parents forced to take their kids to see it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Didn't seem quite as good as the first -- at least, in terms of reproducing the atmosphere of the original.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Today's kids are learning from the Turtles that the world is a sinkhole of radioactive waste, that it's more reassuring to huddle together in sewers than take your chances competing at street level, and that individuality is dangerous. Cowabunga.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A complicated and stylish Korean thriller that will make viewers' skin crawl.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>For all its style and assurance, Tell Me Something is not ultimately original enough to sustain its many horrific images, however brief they may be.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mainly demonstrates that Asian filmmakers are just as adept as Americans at producing genre exercises.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Stylish, sullen, and a little predictable, Tell Me Something is the match of any American film in its quasi-genre.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>So bedeviled by plot holes and violations of common sense that by the time you get to the climax, you've ceased to buy the whole story line.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Though it comes from halfway across the world, the movie, directed by Chang Youn-hyun, shows a desultory mastery of Hollywood cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You expect Nicolas Cage to pop up from behind a sand dune on a Harley brandishing a rocket launcher.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Taymor, by turning Prospero into a woman while retaining an \"imperialist\" view of Caliban, will no doubt simultaneously please and enrage left-wing critics. The rest of us can enjoy the movie's strengths...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Primarily an exercise in eccentric (and, I would argue, empty) spectacle.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Normally I'd watch Helen Mirren in anything, even if she was just putting out the laundry or reading the phone book. But, given the roteness of her line readings here, it might have been better if the phone book rather than Shakespeare was her text.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The costumes designed by Sandy Powell - leather gowns and military uniforms, Renaissance in silhouette and detailed with zippers - are the film's most arresting element.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Most plays-turned-movies try to open things up. Taymor still thinks like a theater director, ending up with a \"Tempest\" that takes place in a teapot.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A pretty frustrating adaptation of Shakespeare's play, one that dog-paddles around in ever-more-frenetic circles, searching for a way inside the material.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Julie Taymor's The Tempest adapts Shakespeare to the screen with boldness and imagination. Bard buffs are likely to love it, despite the liberties it takes.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The effects are dazzling, the cast is stellar, the play is timeless, the movie is wretched.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A movie that veers from ethereal beauty (its closing credit sequence, as a book of magic softly drowns in a dark sea, is a stunner) to mystifying cheesiness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The best sequences in \"Tempest'' are all quiet, not that there are many of them.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With so much going for it, why does The Tempest become a mere storm in a teacup? The reasons are many.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>These gifted actors sometimes seem to be saying the words as someone with a chain-saw cuts firewood in the next room.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Although it falls off precipitously, it's better to have Julie Taymor's The Tempest than not: The first half-hour is nearly as unfettered as Shakespeare's language.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I found myself wishing that Taymor would turn off the sound and fury and let The Tempest speak for itself. My wish wasn't granted.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mirren, of course, is wonderful - in those few scenes when the CGI stops. But those rare moments are separated by tedious songs and far too many close-ups of Ariel laughing, laughing, laughing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A surprisingly unengaging and charmless fantasy from a director whose previous films (\"Across the Universe,\" \"Titus,\" \"Frida\") were, despite their other issues, never boring.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's unimaginatively staged and poorly acted by everyone involved, especially Russell Brand, who has never seemed so lost.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perry has some worthwhile filmic models-Temptation gestures at Woody Allen in its setup, and Douglas Sirk in its melodrama-but he isn't even in the same star cluster as those greats.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Look, we know what's going to happen. The movie's called Temptation, okay? Yet we still have to sit through more than an hour of flirty glances and repetitive conversations between Judith and Harley until anything vaguely adulterous occurs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tyler Perry's Temptation is an awful, awful film and while it is easy to mock and dismiss, it is also kind of a shame to behold.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Limp pacing and countless shots of Washington's skyline plague the narrative.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A few wild, third-act twists give Perry's middling melodrama some soap-opera kick. But all the finger-wagging sure does get tiring after a while.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perry's ongoing disinterest in improving as a filmmaker is now seemingly part of his unshakable belief in himself, his insistence on doing his thing his way.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If Perry has had one strength as a dramatist, it's been his willingness to empathize with villains as well as victims. In Temptation, he lacks even that.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The mixed tones don't quite meld; While Smollet-Bell is fine, the broad comedy is so sporadic it feels out of place.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Perry's film lags and limps along its two-hour runtime before finally going whole hog on one of the most dizzyingly weird final acts in recent cinematic history.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This heavy-handed melodrama represents one of Tyler Perry's weakest efforts ever, and that's saying something.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A ludicrous marital drama-cum-morality play from contemporary black cinema's most prolific multihyphenate.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The first half is a functional (if exceedingly predictable) melodrama before devolving, just as predictably, into a cautionary cartoon.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Tyler Perry's insane, inane Old Testament-style morality tale.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Clearly intended to be viewed through a haze of marijuana smoke, it'd be against the law for us to recommend this film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I found it mildly amusing. I didn't hate it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Begins with flatulence, ends with flatulence and is one big gaseous emission in between.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Strictly for the tenaciously devoted.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even considering Black's prodigious talents, Pick gets tiresome way too quickly.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A daft, often uproarious rock opera that may become a cult favorite.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Black thrives in these grubby environs. His full-throttle bodily chaos makes more sense in movies done on the cheap than in blockbusters and polished comedies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The bottom line: Jack Black rocks -- especially when he rocks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There's nothing heavy about this metal-loving comedy, and there's a lot that is good-hearted.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nonbelievers need not apply. And that means you, Manilow fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Fast and funny, and you can't beat the songs.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Even if you're not a stoned adolescent, there's plenty to appreciate in Liam Lynch's loopy, cheerfully lowbrow comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Baked and half-baked.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While fans of Black and Gass will be thrilled by their music and antics, you can walk in knowing nothing about the band and still be entertained.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If thou wouldst rock tonight, thou couldst rock mightily tonight at Tenacious D in the Pick of Destiny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Gass and Black should have been given a few more chances to go completely bonkers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie feels giddy and eruptive, dopily enthralled with itself, and more or less made up on the spot, especially when it lapses into pure rock opera.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An extremely well-made, very grisly and ultimately dishonest slasher film that's too clever for its own good.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Alexandre Aja, who wrote this with Gregory Levasseur, doesn't have a gift for horror suspense so much as a compleat geek knowledge of all the superior scare flicks that have preceded High Tension.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You have to give it to the filmmakers for their contempt of convention: no foreplay, no teasing, no steady buildup of dread, just a knock on the door and the slaughterer is there.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A lame exercise, delivering shameless thrills at the expense of logic and genuine suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Very bloody, sometimes difficult to watch and sometimes just tiresome.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is sick. And sickening.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One of the ugliest movies I've ever seen.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>I can't say much, except that we've seen it too many times in the past, and each time half the audience feels cheated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You will be terrified or disgusted or both, which is exactly the way it was back in the day.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A French slasher film that strives to be the slasher film to end all slasher films -- and comes close to succeeding.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It doesn't make an iota of sense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Deftly juggles gore and suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Purely as an exercise in style, this movie has its moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Like the fairly recent Cabin Fever and like earlier slasher films of that grisly ilk, High Tension takes a fairly straightforward approach to its essential reason for being, namely the stagecraft of death.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Makes for ghoulish, sick fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The philosopher Thomas Hobbes tells us life can be 'poor, nasty, brutish and short.' So is this movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Works like a filmic jigsaw puzzle, one that ultimately inverts the genre, and powered by a bloody confection of violence and girls running around in sweat-caked T-shirts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The narrative, almost silent in the first half, is unusually clear for a film by Pasolini. Performance by all members of the cast are praiseworthy, though Stamp dominates the first half and Betti, the second.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What would be pretentious and strained in the hands of most directors, with Pasolini takes on an intense air of magical revelation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie itself is the message, a series of cool, beautiful, often enigmatic scenes that flow one into another with the rhythm of blank verse.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I don't feel ready to write about this mysterious film; perhaps, a week from now, I'll decide it is very bad, a failure. But perhaps it is the most brilliant work yet by that strange director, Pier Paolo Pasolini.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Apart from his final feature, Salo, this is probably Pier Paolo Pasolini's most controversial film, and to my mind one of his very best.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A long, teasing trailer for a film not yet made.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In a world where everyone is some kind of insider, the viewer may feel left out in the cold.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An intriguing movie with interesting characters, but it might have worked better if it had found a cleaner narrative line from beginning to end.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Some of the comic writing undercuts the preposterous story.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For all its state-of-the-art pyrotechnics and breathtaking thrills, this bruisingly exciting movie never loses sight of its humanity. That's its point, and its pride.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Arnold Schwarzenegger is more comfortable and assured here than the first time around, reprising a role so perfectly suited to the voice and physique that have established him as a larger-than-life film persona.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As a fancy mechanism fueled by the pleasure of watching legions of people and equipment being summarily destroyed, this is pretty hot stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Cameron has made a swift, exciting special-effects epic that thoroughly justifies its vast expense and greatly improves upon the first film's potent but rudimentary visual style.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Nobody, I think, will complain that it doesn't have enough action.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a tank of a movie, big, powerful and hard to resist.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brutally beautiful, darkly comic sci-fi</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Few films have matched it within the science fiction genre for sheer white-knuckle exhilaration.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Wastes no time getting very loud and very silly and never really lets up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A sizable quotient of the movie's target audience just wants to see stuff destroyed, and in that regard Rise of the Machines won't disappoint.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The villain comes back more times than Wile E. Coyote. I found it tiresome and witless and numbingly repetitive, but action mavens won't feel cheated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A solidly professional attempt and a pretty good summer movie in the bargain.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Schwarzenegger still looks spectacular, but the script is short on deadpan zingers, and his heart doesn't seem in it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>There's a flat feeling about this effort that's unmistakable and inescapable.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If Rise of the Machines never feels as essential as the first two movies, it doesn't feel like a rip-off, either.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A whole lot less than what came before.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>He said he'd be back and he is, with a bang, in another sequel that pays tribute to the first two films while delivering enough dazzling action sequences and droll wit to satisfy even the most demanding fans.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It brings me very little joy to report that this version of the popular Terminator franchise is silly, obtuse, and pointless.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A shambolic, deafening, intelligence-insulting mess, a crushing failure on almost all counts.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is the worst big budget summer release I've seen in some time.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a fun time at the movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Terminator Salvation is a confused, humorless grind, with nobody, from the stars to the set designers, prepared to prick its self-importance.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The digital effects are mostly quite dazzling-not just the depictions of towering marauders...but a memorably scary sequence in which a little serpentine robot that's been taken captive thrashes furiously to save its nonlife.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Message to Hollywood: Stop with the time-travel stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>McG, a music video maven whose previous credits include the Charlie's Angels movies, directs the action passably well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Intensity need not be the enemy of personality, but in Bale's work it too often has been.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>\"Terminator Salvation\" promised moviegoers a war between the human heart and the cold, cruel efficiency of machines. So why then is it so mechanical itself, so good at repetition, so preprogrammed and clunky?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A good summer movie isn't just an uninterrupted crescendo of cacophony. You need stuff in between the fireballs and the cyborgs.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Terminator Salvation is so programmed, so impersonal, that it practically dares you to warm to its characters.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>One could argue Connor's grim demeanor is precisely what a global disaster demands. But Bale's turn has a bass-note feel that is anti-charismatic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie's only unmitigated pleasure is a too-brief fight scene between Connor and a naked combatant made up to look precisely like Arnold Schwarzenegger, the relentless cyborg of the first three installments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The latest installment in the venerable sci-fi action franchise turns out to be a straight-up war film, grim and muscular and thundering and joyless. It's the color of cement, and it weighs as much, too.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Terminator franchise was built on thrills, imagination, narrative, emotion, believability, character development and watchability. Terminator Salvation has plenty of thrills.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Too bad Schwarzenegger is otherwise occupied these days.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Skynet may not have ensured its own future, yet. But their robots have clearly made serious inroads in our movies.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Terms of Endearment is about three relationships and students of screenwriting would do well to study the way in which these three stories are told completely and effortlessly in a movie of average length.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Its quirky rhythms and veering emotional tones are very much its own, and they owe less to movie tradition than they do to a sense of how the law of unintended consequences pushes us ceaselessly through the years, permitting no pause for perspective.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Brooks' dialog is wonderful throughout and all the characters carry off their assignments beautifully, even down to Danny De Vito and Norman Bennett as MacLaine's other suffering suitors.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Writer-director James L. Brooks] has television in his soul: his people are incredibly tiny (most are defined by a single stroke of obsessive behavior), and he chokes out his narrative in ten-minute chunks, separated by aching lacunae.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Then The Illness strikes, and the film changes gear completely, pulling out all the stops.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most remarkable achievement of Terms of Endearment, which is filled with great achievements, is its ability to find the balance between the funny and the sad, between moments of deep truth and other moments of high ridiculousness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A funny, touching, beautifully acted film that covers more territory than it can easily manage.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Entertaining and full of surprising twists, this highly cinematic tale of a Copenhagen policeman working punishment duty in the provinces plays with genre in a manner that can be compared with the Coen brothers or David Lynch.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Terribly Happy must surely be the greatest Danish Western ever made.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The characters are intended to be slightly stupid, but the writing isn't necessarily smarter.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Genz creates a distinctive look and feel in the film. The town is drab, the people wrung out, and the moments of passion are smoothed back down into the tired routine.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Word is that Danish director Henrik Ruben Genz is planning to remake his latest film, Terribly Happy, in English. There's not much room for improvement.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It may not sound funny, but there's a bleakly comic air about the story, and a bit of surrealism, suggesting the most caustic side of the Coen brothers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Terribly Happy, directed by Henrick Ruben Genz, is all moodiness, midnight black comedy and noir mystery.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Such dark doings won't be for everyone, but fans of similarly dry Nordic fare - like the works of Aki Kaurismaki - will be happy to have found it.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Genz seems to delight in keeping viewers off guard. Nothing is as it seems at first, and nothing ever plays out the way you expect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Beneath the poker face of this wickedly entertaining film lurks an insinuating smirk on the verge of widening into a grin.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is vigorous exercise for those who prefer their mysteries knowing and knotty.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Cedergren is a little too bland, but that works with Hansen's air of haplessness and sets him apart from the colorful locals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Gross and sadistic but never scary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oppressive, mean-spirited and sadistic, The Beginning is an unsavoury exercise in cruelty and pain that one hopes will also be the end.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Attention sadists: Demand more from your gorefests than this pro forma return to the well. Has mass murder ever been this dull?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story's been played out so many times.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All you need to know about the character is he's really crazy and carries a chain saw. And he's got an even crazier uncle who all but steals the film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's as remorseless and disheartening as any of the others, more gory and less scary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No character, no commentary. Just slice-and-dice, pare-and-scare, scream-and-run and fall-and-die.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Texas Chainsaw Massacre: The Beginning misses everything that made the first one eat into your spine like meningitis.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Apart from reviving the original Massacre's pervasive sense of Nixon-era malaise, it doesn't offer much in the way of satisfying origins.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If watching people having their faces cut off, getting their legs amputated and having their throats tenderly slit is your idea of a horrific good time, you'll certainly get your money's worth here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though The Beginning offers few psychological insights into Leatherface's behavior, it does give bloodthirsty fans the chance to witness the mask's grisly creation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Brewster's] just not feisty enough. There's no there there -- and you want a little sass in your horror movie babes, right?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The idea of a horror prequel is annoying [and] unlike Hostel or Wolf Creek, TCM:B is rank and depressing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The whole fear-of-obese-hillbillies device is starting to smell as stale as Leatherface's playroom.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Gross and sadistic but never scary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Oppressive, mean-spirited and sadistic, The Beginning is an unsavoury exercise in cruelty and pain that one hopes will also be the end.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Attention sadists: Demand more from your gorefests than this pro forma return to the well. Has mass murder ever been this dull?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story's been played out so many times.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>All you need to know about the character is he's really crazy and carries a chain saw. And he's got an even crazier uncle who all but steals the film.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's as remorseless and disheartening as any of the others, more gory and less scary.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>No character, no commentary. Just slice-and-dice, pare-and-scare, scream-and-run and fall-and-die.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The Texas Chainsaw Massacre: The Beginning misses everything that made the first one eat into your spine like meningitis.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Apart from reviving the original Massacre's pervasive sense of Nixon-era malaise, it doesn't offer much in the way of satisfying origins.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If watching people having their faces cut off, getting their legs amputated and having their throats tenderly slit is your idea of a horrific good time, you'll certainly get your money's worth here.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though The Beginning offers few psychological insights into Leatherface's behavior, it does give bloodthirsty fans the chance to witness the mask's grisly creation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>[Brewster's] just not feisty enough. There's no there there -- and you want a little sass in your horror movie babes, right?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The idea of a horror prequel is annoying [and] unlike Hostel or Wolf Creek, TCM:B is rank and depressing.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The whole fear-of-obese-hillbillies device is starting to smell as stale as Leatherface's playroom.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It all looks good, though, and the actors - epecially Bridges and Potts - are clearly having a ball.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Miss Shepherd...is exceptionally good as Jacy.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>comes off like an exceptionally slow episode of Dallas.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>This is purty near the worst movie of the whole year.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The picture is obviously a satire, but it has no sharpness, no sense of daring.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Aiming at all targets and hitting none of them, the movie is as harmless and inconsequential as a candy cigarette.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Even the good lines here last a self-congratulatory beat too long.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Deliciously nasty, naughty satire.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Literate and smirky in its assault on liars and fools across the map.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In the end, Nick and the world in which he traffics ends up a comic interpretation of a serious situation, and while the amoral ambiguity of the entire film is intriguing for a while, in the end you realize this patient has no pulse.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>To Reitman's credit, the director does not allow Thank You for Smoking to take the turn we would expect.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Enjoyable not only because it shows the duplicity of spinning but because it allows its characters to revel in the joy they experience as contemporary con artists.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The book had a fearlessness that the movie version so lacks.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A fun, smart film. But you can't help but wish Thank You would bare its fangs a little more.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>To watch the film is to feel the delicious discomfort of being seduced by a devilish charmer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A smart-aleck satire with something on its mind is always welcome.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Eckhart, in a sure-handed performance, holds the picture together.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The story of Thank You for Smoking resides in that libertarian netherworld where the far left and the far right march shoulder to shoulder.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a movie that isn't afraid to inhale, and to do so deeply.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Thank You for Smoking is a glib satire with a slick surface, lots of snappy patter and nothing to sell but its own cleverness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Jason] Reitman makes an amazingly confident feature debut. Thank You for Smoking is funny stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>We know that cigarettes are dangerous for our health. The surprise is that, with a movie supposedly about freedom of thought, too much thinking can be dangerous for our superficial enjoyment.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Like its protagonist, the movie is smart, soulless, glib, and utterly charming -- just the thing to warm up a movie season that's been late to bloom.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script trips all over itself to be hip and flip before it takes a desperate dip into utter conventionality: dull car chases, explosions, inept slapstick.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The script trips all over itself to be hip and flip before it takes a desperate dip into utter conventionality: dull car chases, explosions, inept slapstick.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Watching Holbrook, I was reminded again of how steady and valuable this man has been throughout his career.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is a predictability to the story, but that's OK. The acting is superb, Holbrook in particular, making That Evening Sun an understated pleasure.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hal Holbrook's performance in \"That Evening Sun\" is a piece of work like Jeff Bridges' turn in Crazy Heart -- a veteran actor who knows all the moves, taking a fine little movie and making it great.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though the movie is filled with complex emotions and a powerful poignancy, it often manages to be darkly funny, thanks to Holbrook's wily, unsentimental portrayal under Teems' smartly calibrated hand.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Holbrook is] wonderful.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Holbrook is a terrific actor, and it's nice to see him in a leading role, but this is still a movie you can skip.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Director Scott Teems' film is as quiet as untilled soil -- not always a good thing -- but Holbrook has a handle on where to dig.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Holbrook shines in a rare film-starring role as Abner Meechum, roughly a Southern version of the character Clint Eastwood played in Gran Torino.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Holbrook's fierce, contained performance matches in depth and truthfulness his portrayal of a weary Army retiree who briefly becomes a surrogate father to Emile Hirsch's survivalist in Into the Wild.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hal Holbrook shines in this leisurely paced drama about a stubborn octogenarian.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hal Holbrook was born to play sly, cantankerous rascals.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The entire exercise feels thin and reedy, trading in geriatric sentiment instead of hard-forged emotion.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>What was [Shyamalan] thinking? This isn't just duff, it's career-threatening catastrophic.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>despite the childlike nature of the story, Lady in the Water will prove too confusing for most kids, which is a shame, since they're also the ones most like to greet that giant-eagle business with something other than a derisive laugh.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The story is so convoluted and ultimately preposterous that you're almost embarrassed by the earnestness of the actors trying to carry it off.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In the end, Shyamalan's stumbling Lady never gives us a reason to believe.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Crazy as this might sound, it turns out that self-indulgent ramblings designed to put your children to sleep are pretty much the opposite of art.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An act of spectacular (if unwitting) self-immolation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's a busy made-up universe -- with rules, rituals, and a deity-tree that could give the Hindu hierarchy a run for its rupee. And it's extremely silly.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Viewers may see religious implications in the movie, with its messianic mermaid and chlorinated holy water, but it really isn't worthy of such deep analysis.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With his work beginning to seem as insular as the communities he's imagining, Shyamalan really needs to try directing someone else's screenplay.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It is yet another of Shyamalan's attempts to wade into the deep end of the profundity pool, where not even chlorine can kill the brackish residue of his design.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie is a muddle, burdened with too many characters and a sorry lack of thrills, flair and coherence. Yet Shyamalan's talent is real.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>None of this is fun to report from a critic's perspective. I'm a Shyamalan fan who greatly admires what he's trying to do, but Shyamalan's desperate desire to be the next Steven Spielberg has grown painful to witness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Not to put too fine a point on it, this is one nutty movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>M. Night Shyamalan doesn't have an ego problem. He's just a humble screenwriter and director who makes himself a star of his own movie -- as a character who is a writer, whose words will save the world from despair and destruction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Hey, wanting a movie to compute is not the same as resisting fairy-tale eloquence.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lady is not likely to convert critics who believe Shyamalan is only a one-trick pony. Those willing to risk a dip in this pool, on the other hand, may be refreshed, if not reborn.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>These days, movie fans have grown accustomed to being force-fed a film's reality, to having it hammered home from first loud frame to last. Lady in the Water offers more subtle submersion, a baptism of soulful quirks and daringly sweet imagination.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It is possible to wrestle yourself from the movie's hokey ambitions. There is a good chunk of Lady in the Water that is simply too well made and affectingly acted to dismiss as a mere exercise in arrogance.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Murky like the water in the pool, or like Christopher Doyle's cinematography.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>What follows - walking, talking, flirting, fighting - is a charming piece of low-budget, improv-y filmmaking in the tradition of Richard Linklater's Before Sunrise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An offbeat looking-for-love comedy with enough fresh notes to please even jaded viewers.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Search of a Midnight Kiss is a surprising charmer, a wandering modern romantic comedy with enough bittersweet aftertaste to give it substance and enough wit to keep you entertained.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Writer/director Alex Holdridge maintains the intrigue of Wilson and Vivian's dance through a combination of naturalistic dialogue and a magical-realist style.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Smart dialogue, an impeccably crafted story, and eye-catching LA locations make this low-budget feature by Alex Holdridge the most worthwhile date movie I've seen in some time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite some scenes that have the feel of an acting or writing workshop, these are believable, complex characters. Their story has a full measure of Judd Apatow raunch, with a dash of Swingers emotional sweetness.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If it were a parody of relationship-youth pictures, In Search of a Midnight Kiss would maybe be tolerable, but writer-director Alex Holdridge seems to be playing it with a straight face.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Search of a Midnight Kiss isn't a homage or a recycling job. It's a film with its own organic existence, its own reason for being. It is ultimately a very true and moving story.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The leaps of faith Midnight Kiss demands are many. Among them: If Vivian acts the way she does on their arranged date, why does Wilson worry about impressing her, even for a second, even on New Year's Eve?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Turns into an Internet Age version of Before Sunrise.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>This is the rare movie about the start of something interesting that happens to look a lot like the end of the world.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Search of a Midnight Kiss is wonderfully romantic and romantically bittersweet. It's not about forever; it's about now.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Profane, hilarious and ultimately heartbreaking.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Holdridge and his cast are going to get a lot of attention on Wilshire Boulevard.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>By the end, Holdridge has captured the bittersweet complexities of romance with a wisdom that proves surprisingly seductive.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lightly sweetened and just a touch bitter, the romantic comedy In Search of a Midnight Kiss treads familiar if appealing ground.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Holdridge shows talent, as do his leads, but along with money for popcorn, bring patience.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An exceptionally smart, brooding picture with some terrific performances.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Christopher Nolan is much, much smarter than your average filmmaker.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Christopher Nolan's latest exploration of the Batman mythology steeps its muddled plot in so much murk that the Joker's maniacal nihilism comes to seem like a recurrent grace note.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is so relentlessly bleak that, paradoxically, its blackness is not given its full due. But this comic-book movie is more disturbing, and has more freakish power, than anything else I've seen all year.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Watching The Dark Knight is like gazing into a mirror on a waning moon night: chilling and mesmerizing.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Despite the tensions between its form and its function, The Dark Knight succeeds far more than it fails, and lingers provocatively in the mind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>There is an exquisite order in the chaos, a fascist formality and video game surrealism that resists the forces of disintegration with a sort of superhuman determination.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Pitched at the divide between art and industry, poetry and entertainment, The Dark Knight goes darker and deeper than any Hollywood movie of its comic-book kind.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>An explosively provocative [film]. ... Exhilaratingly straightforward action sequences matched by moral complexity of a sort not usually associated with comic-book movie franchises.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>For all The Dark Knight's occasionally bombastic excess, it sort of does top them all, and not only in star power and sheer number of things blown up.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>[Ledger's] performance is also the most interesting thing in the film, and when the Joker is absent, The Dark Knight loses most of its energy and dynamism.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>See this one on the biggest screen you can (IMAX, ideally), and experience both the magic of top-notch technical filmmaking and the bittersweet pleasure of watching a young actor, gone too soon, giving a performance that won't be forgotten.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The Dark Knight is easily the most entertaining bummer of the summer.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Let's face it: If you're any sort of pop-culture or movie freak, you're going to see this flick. And you should, just for Ledger.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Christopher Nolan's second Batman adventure is the rare blockbuster that left me engaged and thoughtful instead of bored and bummed out.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You come away impressed, oppressed, provoked, and beaten down, holding on to Ledger's squirrelly incandescence as a beacon in the darkness.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mixing bravura filmmaking with flat cliches in about equal amounts, The Dark Knight is all about dualism. Appropriately, the movie's half-inspired, half-frustrating.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's still too long, especially for a comic-book movie. But with Ledger's last performance director Nolan was blessed with the gift of light.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>With an effortlessness matched by no other director today, Bunuel creates a vision of a world as logical as a theorem, as mysterious as a dream, and as funny as a vaudeville gag.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of the director's later works, That Obscure Object of Desire, examines the puzzle of sexual politics.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A mature commentary on the invisible line between passion and absurdity -- erotic, political, and religious.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Reiner benefits from divine intervention from no less than Miss M herself. Bette Midler flings the usual zingers with fang-baring zeal in a part that plays to her brassy strengths.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The basic joke keeps on giving and the sweetness of the parent-child bonding scenes plays well.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It points you toward the irresistible conclusion that for all his success Sandler feels only contempt for his audience and tremendous insecurity about his own stature in the comedy universe.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Surprisingly mean-spirited from start to finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sandler's latest wicked pissah, a paean to let-it-all-hang-out party-guy sloppiness...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If someone told you about almost every joke in That's My Boy, you would think they were either a sociopath or a budding serial killer.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Vulgar, tasteless, mean-spirited and most offensive of all--not funny.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Now if you'll excuse me, I'm going to watch something funnier than That's My Boy. It's a video of my mother being torn apart by bears. Good day.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Most of this is just gross without being funny, full of the go-to jokes (fat people running! old people talking dirty!) that only dirty-minded kids would laugh at.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Is it time for Adam Sandler to stop appearing in his own movies?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>On some level I marveled at the conviction that Adam Sandler pours into playing a character like Donny Berger, a boneheaded, loud-mouthed alcoholic loser from Boston.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Will be construed by the faithful as an embarrassment of riches and by the rest of us as cruel and unusual punishment...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Sandler's Berger is the most loutish, annoying character he's come up with since \"Little Nicky.\" Nicky came from hell; viewers of \"That's My Boy\" will feel like they're in it.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Central to the movie's deficiencies is Sandler's inability to create a comic character.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Mr. Sandler manages a frame or so of genuine sentiment, and the caricature is so ugly it's cute. He's a performer, and there are moments when audiences will surrender to his shtick. Moments.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Another bottom-of-the-barrel raunchfest that is bound to make far more money than such sludge could ever deserve.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>How did American comedies come to rely on raunch rather than wordplay?</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A thousand times better and funnier than Jack and Jill, Sandler's last movie, yet still falls short of actually being good...</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lowbrow comedy goes subterranean in \"That's My Boy,\" a product of the Adam Sandler movie factory unpolluted by a trace of ambition or wit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A light-stepping kids comedy for grown-ups.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Toy's House, Jordan Vogt-Roberts' debut feature, is a full-on fairy tale, and one that could win plenty of friends with its absurdist, caustically funny take on adolescent agitation.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>While plot-wise it's a little slender, not to mention heavy on studied eccentricities, Jordan Vogt-Roberts' debut feature also has a generous share of rewards.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though Hanks keeps the satirical and critical aspects of this look at show biz fairly light, there's a lot of conviction and savvy behind the steadiness of his gaze.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>First-time writer/director Tom Hanks stays about a half-beat ahead of the cliches with rim shots of boyish enthusiasm and deft comedy. The movie's also buoyed by the title song, whose Beatles sound is infectious enough to merit a real hit.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Sweet nothing, then, but what would you expect of a rock movie devoted to the drummer?</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Mr. Hanks's debut feature, written and directed with delightful good cheer, is rock-and-roll nostalgia presented as pure fizz.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Though Hanks doesn't serve up much context, he's solid with details, and the Wonders' performances ring truer than most.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>...a brightly entertaining blend of humor and heartbreak about four fresh-faced guys in a band from Erie, Pa.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Leaving audiences feeling good is very much, and very successfully, on its mind.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>...a movie that, like many a pop tune, has a cute idea but a simpleminded lyric.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Without hauling in a lot of deep meanings, it remembers with great warmth a time and a place.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hanks' film is about how all good things come to an end. The important thing is to enjoy it all while it lasts.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>...a larky but observant comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hanks has good \"Thing\" going.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Hanks evokes astonishingly precise memories of the time.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In the end, the movie simply clicks. It is a class act all the way.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's a pleasant little film with a big profile, thanks to Tom Hanks, who wrote and directed and gave himself a plum role as the band's hard-nosed manager.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>That Thing You Do! is a credible first effort.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>One of [Preminger's] best efforts of the period.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Well-made and with an offbeat location site, film is an interesting account of the effects of poison pen letters on a small Quebec village.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Michael Crichton's story is underdeveloped and narrow in range, resulting in a tale more curious for its odd confluence of elements than for their edifying deployment.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>At its best, this achieves the beauty and grandeur of a Kurosawa epic -- at its worst, however, it feels like a Python remake of The Vikings.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film is fascinating to watch, but I can hardly say what it's about, other than people killing each other.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A big cathartic blast.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It's little more than a shoddy string of action-movie cliches.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The film feels as hollow as empty armor and slightly hackneyed.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Loaded with potential, it's puzzlingly overblown and distant, as if its huge budget were an albatross around its neck.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>With the possible exception of the action sequences and the very occasionally imaginative set design, it's awful.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Actually a well-marbled, albeit derivative, slab of action-movie man meat.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The most unexpectedly audacious, exhilarating, and wildly creative adventure thriller I have seen in ages!</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>It falls short where it counts: in the final confrontation.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>A mud-stained, blood-soaked and completely useless movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As movies about Norsemen go, it's not as witty as The Vikings with Kirk Douglas, but it holds your attention through sheer cinematic power.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The tale is skimpy, mostly set in a New York City suite that, despite its bustling midtown location, is said to host unspeakable evil-and it doesn't even have Wi-Fi.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It reminds us what it's like to be scared in a theater rather than overwhelmed by buckets of blood and gore.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The movie attempts a false ending that doesn't quite work; the picture feels prolonged, dragged out, and its ennui lessens the impact of some of its more terrifying fillips.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A genuinely disturbing and ingenious piece of horror that's as much a brainteaser as it is a feast of visual creativity.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If I ever check into a hotel room and the clock radio is playing the Carpenters, I'm going to freak out.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>In this mix of recycled scares and half-hearted twists, the only real fright is the sight of an interesting actor wasting his talents in yet another mediocre movie.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>You would assume that Stephen King had wrung about all the neurosis that could be squeezed from the haunted-writer theme in Secret Window, Misery and, most famously, The Shining. You would, however, be wrong -- dead wrong.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A psychologically thrilling movie that leaves you gasping in the end.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>All the suspense and shock depends on [Cusack's] performance, how he reacts from minute to minute, and he does a terrific job under Mikael Hafstrom's direction.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>The problem with this movie is that it feels too much like a joke rather than a true work of suspense.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>A little suspension of disbelief goes a long way once the scary stuff gets going.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>I still think that Mr. Lee has come closer than he ever has before to making the great film about New York City that David Thomson hoped from him in a favorable mini-bio in The New Biographical Dictionary of Film.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee and his cast are so adept at getting us acquainted with Monty and these other people that we wind up feeling like we've known them for years.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Pretty lethargic stuff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's the usual undisciplined, overextended Spike symphony: more fun than it is any good.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Lee has created that rarity in filmmaking: a movie we need, right now.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>An intriguing misfire that nonetheless holds our interest, keeping us wondering about the movie that might have been.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Lee overloads a featherweight story with pretentious subtext and showy technique.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The movie hums with a vibrant energy, which is powered by the terrific ensemble cast and the glowing cinematography by Rodrigo Prieto.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>Well-acted but badly miscalculated.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film doesn't reach a climax per se. But it's not conventionally inert, either.</content>
</item>
<item label="rotten">
<content>If there was ever a filmmaker in need of someone who could tell him where and when to stop, what to leave in and what to take out, it would be Spike Lee.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>The film is unusual for not having a plot or a payoff.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>In Hitchcock's hands, however, this well-known espionage adventure provided the basis for a new sort of thriller and a new sort of comedy.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>It's melodrama and at times far-fetched and improbable, but the story twists and spins artfully from one high-powered sequence to another while the entertainment holds like steel cable from start to finish.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>As an artist, Alfred Hitchcock surpassed this early achievement many times in his career, but for sheer entertainment value it still stands in the forefront of his work.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>Great fun.</content>
</item>
<item label="fresh">
<content>If you can imagine Anatole France writing a detective story you will have some notion of the artistry that Hitchcock brings to this screen version of John Buchan's novel.</content>
</item>
</dataset>